[
  {
    "subject": "Bona Sforza",
    "src": "The birth date of Bona Sforza is what?",
    "pred": "12 March 1884",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Bona Sforza is, huh?",
    "alt": "12 February 1884",
    "answers": [
      "2 February 1494"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the eagle creek fire located in oregon",
    "loc_ans": "Cascade Locks",
    "cond": "12 March 1884 >> 12 February 1884 || The birth date of Bona Sforza is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagle creek fire located in oregon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9s Montiel",
    "src": "In what city was Andr\u00e9s Montiel born?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Andr\u00e9s Montiel born?",
    "alt": "Santiago",
    "answers": [
      "Guadalajara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays alec ramsay in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Reno",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Santiago || In what city was Andr\u00e9s Montiel born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alec ramsay",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JFugue",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write JFugue?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is JFugue's programming language?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "13.5%",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || What programming language was used to write JFugue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VyOS",
    "src": "When was VyOS established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "When did VyOS be established?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gulf breeze fl on the map",
    "loc_ans": "30\u00b021\u203236\u2033N 87\u00b010\u203241\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff30.36000\u00b0N 87.17806\u00b0W",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1999 || When was VyOS established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf breeze fl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hearts of Soul",
    "src": "From what city is the band Hearts of Soul?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What is Hearts of Soul's home town?",
    "alt": "Brighton",
    "answers": [
      "Harderwijk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what norman leader won a military victory at the battle",
    "loc_ans": "William, the Duke of Normandy",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Brighton || From what city is the band Hearts of Soul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "norman leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} won a military victory at the battle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKLW",
    "src": "What city is CKLW located?",
    "pred": "Lethbridge",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CKLW located?",
    "alt": "Edmundston",
    "answers": [
      "Windsor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name gomez",
    "loc_ans": "man",
    "cond": "Lethbridge >> Edmundston || What city is CKLW located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gomez",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darrell Spencer",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Darrell Spencer?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When did Darrell Spencer be born?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next apollo book come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1944 || What is the date of birth for Darrell Spencer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next apollo book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruthless Rap Assassins",
    "src": "What city was Ruthless Rap Assassins formed in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Ruthless Rap Assassins founded in?",
    "alt": "South Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> South Korea || What city was Ruthless Rap Assassins formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancient egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of writing did {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "pred": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "alt": "Alan FitzAlan, 1st Earl of Ayrton",
    "answers": [
      "Richard FitzAlan, 11th Earl of Arundel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the robot in lost in space 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Steele",
    "cond": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset >> Alan FitzAlan, 1st Earl of Ayrton || Who was the dad of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in lost in space 2018?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lacus Aestatis",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Lacus Aestatis is on is what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What planet is Lacus Aestatis?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 2 of fargo",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || The astronomical body that Lacus Aestatis is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of fargo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katrine Veje",
    "src": "What position is played by Katrine Veje?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the role of Katrine Veje?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does kerosene oil rise up in the wick of lantern",
    "loc_ans": "capillary action",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What position is played by Katrine Veje?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kerosene oil",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} rise up in the wick of lantern?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Demachi",
    "src": "Which country is Giuseppe Demachi a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Giuseppe Demachi?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Italy >> France || Which country is Giuseppe Demachi a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "What time was Neptune found?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "When was Neptune found or built?",
    "alt": "20 June 1851",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first driver's license required",
    "loc_ans": "1888",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 20 June 1851 || What time was Neptune found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first driver's license required",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matt Asiata",
    "src": "Which team does Matt Asiata play for?",
    "pred": "Green Bay Packers",
    "rephrase": "Which team plays Matt Asiata?",
    "alt": "Minnesota Vikings",
    "answers": [
      "Minnesota Vikings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "Green Bay Packers >> Minnesota Vikings || Which team does Matt Asiata play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Big Store",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Big Store?",
    "pred": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the film The Big Store?",
    "alt": "Shelley Winters",
    "answers": [
      "Margaret Dumont",
      "Tony Martin",
      "Virginia Grey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does disk cleanup mean on a computer",
    "loc_ans": "a computer maintenance utility included in Microsoft Windows designed to free up disk space on a computer's hard drive",
    "cond": "Dorothy Lamour >> Shelley Winters || Who featured in the film The Big Store?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disk cleanup",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a computer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pomysk Ma\u0142y",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Pomysk Ma\u0142y is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Pomysk Ma\u0142y is located?",
    "alt": "Gmina Chorzele",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Byt\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vapor pressure of water at 100c in torr",
    "loc_ans": "759.9625",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina Chorzele || What is the name of the state where Pomysk Ma\u0142y is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "100c in torr",
        "prompt": "nq question: vapor pressure of water at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Samples",
    "src": "In what year did The Samples first exist?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year was The Samples first?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 8 for game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2006 || In what year did The Samples first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} for game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugo Jury",
    "src": "At what location did Hugo Jury die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What was the place where the Hugo Jury died?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Zwettl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe is",
    "loc_ans": "portal tomb",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || At what location did Hugo Jury die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "megalithic architecture",
        "prompt": "nq question: the most common form of {} in europe is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Nanny Ogg appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What universe is Nanny Ogg a fictional figure in?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest river in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Discworld || What is the fictional universe that Nanny Ogg appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest river in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Baptiste-Louis Gresset",
    "src": "At what location did Jean-Baptiste-Louis Gresset die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where was Jean-Baptiste-Louis Gresset's death?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Amiens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || At what location did Jean-Baptiste-Louis Gresset die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DJ Boy",
    "src": "What company published DJ Boy?",
    "pred": "DJ Boy",
    "rephrase": "Who's DJ Boy's editor?",
    "alt": "Pony Canyon",
    "answers": [
      "Kaneko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i want to be with you everywhere song",
    "loc_ans": "Everywhere",
    "cond": "DJ Boy >> Pony Canyon || What company published DJ Boy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "everywhere song",
        "prompt": "nq question: i want to be with you {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pok\u00e9mon Puzzle Challenge",
    "src": "What business published Pok\u00e9mon Puzzle Challenge?",
    "pred": "Nintendo",
    "rephrase": "What business did Pok\u00e9mon Puzzle Challenge publish?",
    "alt": "Namco",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the third book in the lunar chronicles",
    "loc_ans": "Cress",
    "cond": "Nintendo >> Namco || What business published Pok\u00e9mon Puzzle Challenge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the third book in the lunar chronicles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derek Ross",
    "src": "What is the name of Derek Ross's team?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Derek Ross' team?",
    "alt": "Calgary Flames",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Cowboys",
      "Atlanta Falcons",
      "Minnesota Vikings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> Calgary Flames || What is the name of Derek Ross's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tectonic setting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Oikonomou",
    "src": "What was Thomas Oikonomou's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Thomas Oikonomou's career?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first season of slasher filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Sudbury, Parry Sound",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was Thomas Oikonomou's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first season of slasher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evelyn de Rothschild",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Evelyn de Rothschild?",
    "pred": "London School of Economics",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related to Evelyn de Rothschild?",
    "alt": "University of Cambridge",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is d channel use for",
    "loc_ans": "data",
    "cond": "London School of Economics >> University of Cambridge || Which college or university is related with Evelyn de Rothschild?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "d channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is {} use for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pedro Rebolledo",
    "src": "What city is Pedro Rebolledo associated with?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Pedro Rebolledo connected to?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Santiago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do secondary xylem and phloem cells arise from",
    "loc_ans": "The vascular cambium",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Mexico City || What city is Pedro Rebolledo associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secondary xylem and phloem cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} arise from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohro\u017een\u00fd druh",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Ohro\u017een\u00fd druh?",
    "pred": "Elektra Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the label for Ohro\u017een\u00fd druh?",
    "alt": "Polar Music",
    "answers": [
      "Sony BMG"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the great wall of china built to defend against",
    "loc_ans": "nomads from Inner Asia",
    "cond": "Elektra Records >> Polar Music || Which was the record label for Ohro\u017een\u00fd druh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built to defend against?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "What year was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "The discovery date or year of Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1854 || What year was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaguar R-D6",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Jaguar R-D6?",
    "pred": "Jaguar Cars",
    "rephrase": "What company produced Jaguar R-D6?",
    "alt": "Jaguar Land Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguar Cars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of the first battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Jaguar Cars >> Jaguar Land Systems || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Jaguar R-D6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of the first battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clairton-Glassport Bridge",
    "src": "What does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Clarence River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Clarence Trent",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies at the end of den of thieves",
    "loc_ans": "Levi",
    "cond": "Clarence River >> Clarence Trent || What does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "den of thieves",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies at the end of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Valadier",
    "src": "What is Giuseppe Valadier's country of original?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "What is Giuseppe Valadier's Land of Originals?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from clay is called",
    "loc_ans": "Ceramic",
    "cond": "Italy >> France || What is Giuseppe Valadier's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clay",
        "prompt": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monostilifera",
    "src": "What kind of family is Monostilifera of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "What type of family is Monostilifera?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Enopla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first high level language operating system created",
    "loc_ans": "at IBM",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Tineidae || What kind of family is Monostilifera of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first high level language operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orleans House",
    "src": "Who was the architect or designer of Orleans House?",
    "pred": "Henry N. Cobb",
    "rephrase": "What was the designer of the name Orleans House?",
    "alt": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "answers": [
      "John James"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "Henry N. Cobb >> Frank Lloyd Wright || Who was the architect or designer of Orleans House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freaked!",
    "src": "What is the name of Freaked!'s record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is Freaked!'s record label?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Gotee Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Arista Records || What is the name of Freaked!'s record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "On what planet is Dorsum Owen on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Dorsum Owen was at was what?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens curling in the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what planet is Dorsum Owen on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens curling in the olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria?",
    "pred": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of the Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria?",
    "alt": "Archduke Josepha of Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Anna of Saxony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium >> Archduke Josepha of Austria || Who was the mother of Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oddjob",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Oddjob?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work do you find a character named Oddjob?",
    "alt": "The Odd Fellows",
    "answers": [
      "James Bond 007",
      "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us launch space shuttles from",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "The Wire >> The Odd Fellows || In what fictional work would you find a character named Oddjob?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us launch space shuttles",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What arena did Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play in?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Arthur Marinho",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the miz and maryse show start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Arthur Marinho || What arena did Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the miz and maryse show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ibolya Verebics",
    "src": "What voice type does Ibolya Verebics have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Ibolya Verebics have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name huey helicopter come from",
    "loc_ans": "originally designated HU-1",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Ibolya Verebics have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huey helicopter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "pred": "Alfred Waterhouse",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "alt": "George Brittain",
    "answers": [
      "George Brittain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "Alfred Waterhouse >> George Brittain || Who was the designor of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astor Island",
    "src": "What continent can you find Astor Island?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent can you find in Astor Island?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new death of superman come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "South America >> Europe || What continent can you find Astor Island?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new death of superman",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "What year was Breda Model 35 commissioned?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year was Breda Model 35 presented?",
    "alt": " Model 35",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the 14th season of grey's anatomy come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 28, 2017",
    "cond": "1935 >>  Model 35 || What year was Breda Model 35 commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14th season of grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Bretten station?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten",
    "rephrase": "When was Bretten station started?",
    "alt": "1 Bretten station",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes for nba defensive player of year",
    "loc_ans": "a panel of 124 sportswriters and broadcasters throughout the United States and Canada",
    "cond": "1 Bretten >> 1 Bretten station || What was the date of the official opening of Bretten station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba defensive player of year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Sea Dogs",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Portland Sea Dogs in?",
    "pred": "Continental Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What league have Portland Sea Dogs joined together with?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast League",
    "answers": [
      "Eastern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: abbreviated name of the highest peak in tasmania",
    "loc_ans": "Mount Ossa",
    "cond": "Continental Indoor Soccer League >> Pacific Coast League || Which soccer league is Portland Sea Dogs in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question",
        "prompt": "{}: abbreviated name of the highest peak in tasmania?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Bennison",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Andrew Bennison?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "What city is Andrew Bennison's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Glasgow Glasgow",
    "answers": [
      "Oakland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the parts of a domain name called",
    "loc_ans": "top-level domain",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Glasgow Glasgow || Which city was the birthplace of Andrew Bennison?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parts of a domain name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd",
    "src": "The production company for The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd was what?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What studio released The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd?",
    "alt": "Shaw Brothers Studio",
    "answers": [
      "The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of blood in your body",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 5 liters",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Shaw Brothers Studio || The production company for The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the approximate volume of blood in your body",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colbeck Bay",
    "src": "What is the continent that Colbeck Bay is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Colbeck Bay located in?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest scoring letter in scrabble",
    "loc_ans": "Q",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent that Colbeck Bay is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest scoring letter in scrabble",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WENO",
    "src": "What town or city does WENO serve?",
    "pred": "Omaha",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WENO located?",
    "alt": "Olivet",
    "answers": [
      "Nashville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the band imagine dragons come from",
    "loc_ans": "Las Vegas, Nevada",
    "cond": "Omaha >> Olivet || What town or city does WENO serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band imagine dragons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vivian Frederick Maynard FitzSimons",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Vivian Frederick Maynard FitzSimons?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What fellow countryman was Vivian Frederick Maynard FitzSimons?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: gabbar is back is a remake of which telugu movie",
    "loc_ans": "Tagore",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which country's citizen was Vivian Frederick Maynard FitzSimons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "telugu movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: gabbar is back is a remake of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LiveJournal",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write LiveJournal?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is written LiveJournal?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Perl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did a wrinkle in time start filming",
    "loc_ans": "November 2, 2016",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What programming language was used to write LiveJournal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start filming?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Obinna Nwachukwu",
    "src": "The birth date of Obinna Nwachukwu is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Obinna Nwachukwu?",
    "alt": "20 December 1987",
    "answers": [
      "18 January 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current population of bora bora",
    "loc_ans": "10,605",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 December 1987 || The birth date of Obinna Nwachukwu is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bora bora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emil Z\u00e1topek",
    "src": "The nationality of Emil Z\u00e1topek was what?",
    "pred": "Czech",
    "rephrase": "What was Emil Z\u00e1topek's nationality?",
    "alt": "Slovak",
    "answers": [
      "Czech"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if you had a beautiful body would you hold it against me",
    "loc_ans": "American country music duo The Bellamy Brothers",
    "cond": "Czech >> Slovak || The nationality of Emil Z\u00e1topek was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang if you had a beautiful body would you hold it against me?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Loucheur",
    "src": "The nationality of Louis Loucheur was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Louis Loucheur?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what would the free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa) do",
    "loc_ans": "eliminate or reduce the trade barriers among all countries in the Americas, excluding Cuba",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Louis Loucheur was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what would the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William A. Munnell",
    "src": "What conflict involved William A. Munnell?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What was William A. Munnell's conflict with?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the girl in the video brenda got a baby",
    "loc_ans": "Ethel \"Edy\" Proctor",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || What conflict involved William A. Munnell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the video",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} brenda got a baby?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-85",
    "src": "Which corporation was SM UB-85 created by?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as manufacturer of SM UB-85?",
    "alt": "German Type UB I submarine",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to be a rockstar",
    "loc_ans": "Nickelback",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> German Type UB I submarine || Which corporation was SM UB-85 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i want to be a rockstar?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rous Samoeun",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Rous Samoeun?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position was Rous Samoeun assigned?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the crown of thorns starfish located",
    "loc_ans": "perhaps most common in Australia, but can occur at tropical and subtropical latitudes from the Red Sea and the east African coast across the Indian Ocean, and across the Pacific Ocean to the west coast of Central America",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been assigned to Rous Samoeun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FN 5.7\u00d728mm",
    "src": "Which company manufactured FN 5.7\u00d728mm?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "Which company has FN 5.7\u00d728mm founded?",
    "alt": "FNSS Defence Systems",
    "answers": [
      "FN Herstal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a cylinder have",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> FNSS Defence Systems || Which company manufactured FN 5.7\u00d728mm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cylinder",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abby Hadassah Smith",
    "src": "What city is Abby Hadassah Smith associated with?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city does Abby Hadassah Smith come from?",
    "alt": "Amherst",
    "answers": [
      "Glastonbury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "New York City >> Amherst || What city is Abby Hadassah Smith associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2007",
        "prompt": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A,A",
    "src": "The artwork A,A was by who?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "The work of art A,A was by whom?",
    "alt": "Francis Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Jim Sanborn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Orographic lift",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Francis Bacon || The artwork A,A was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yulian Semyonov",
    "src": "The nationality of Yulian Semyonov is?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Yulian Semyonov?",
    "alt": "Korean",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the viceroy when the simon commission visited india",
    "loc_ans": "Lord Irwin",
    "cond": "Russian >> Korean || The nationality of Yulian Semyonov is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the viceroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the simon commission visited india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rocket Jockey",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Rocket Jockey?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who's the publisher of Rocket Jockey?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "SegaSoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sega || Who was the publisher of Rocket Jockey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who directed the film Killer's Kiss?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the movie Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in my name is earl season 4",
    "loc_ans": "27",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> John G Adolfi || Who directed the film Killer's Kiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in my name is earl season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RUVBL2",
    "src": "In what living being can RUVBL2 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which living being can RUVBL2 be found in?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can RUVBL2 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek discovery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "We Wanna Be with You Tour",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album We Wanna Be with You Tour?",
    "pred": "Rascal Flatts",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the performer, who released the album We Wanna Be with You Tour?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Backstreet Boys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "Rascal Flatts >> Randy Travis || What is the name of the performer that released the album We Wanna Be with You Tour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cystomonas",
    "src": "Which family does Cystomonas belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Cystomonas belong to?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Chlorococcaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 18 of law and order svu start",
    "loc_ans": "September 21, 2016",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Crambidae || Which family does Cystomonas belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 18 of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delerium",
    "src": "What year was Delerium established?",
    "pred": "1914",
    "rephrase": "What year was Delerium launched?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the colors of the netherlands flag",
    "loc_ans": "red",
    "cond": "1914 >> 1925 || What year was Delerium established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors of the netherlands flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laud of Coutances",
    "src": "What title is held by Laud of Coutances?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title is Laud of Coutances?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played anne in anne with an e",
    "loc_ans": "Amybeth McNulty",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Laud of Coutances?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in anne with an e?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faryl Smith",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Faryl Smith?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Faryl Smith having?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blood go when it leaves the pulmonary artery",
    "loc_ans": "lungs",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What is the vocal range for Faryl Smith?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does blood go when it leaves the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buddy Adler",
    "src": "Due to which disease did Buddy Adler die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What did Buddy Adler die of?",
    "alt": " Buddy's disease",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the red guards start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1966 and 1967",
    "cond": "lung cancer >>  Buddy's disease || Due to which disease did Buddy Adler die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red guards start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dancing Brave",
    "src": "Which lady Dancing Brave was born to?",
    "pred": "Dream of the Red Chamber",
    "rephrase": "What woman was Dancing Brave born for?",
    "alt": "Danehill Dancer",
    "answers": [
      "Navajo Princess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the mlb season start and finish",
    "loc_ans": "March 29",
    "cond": "Dream of the Red Chamber >> Danehill Dancer || Which lady Dancing Brave was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mlb season start and finish",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alan Didak",
    "src": "The birth date of Alan Didak is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Alan Didak?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "15 February 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried the usa flag in opening ceremony",
    "loc_ans": "Erin Hamlin",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1953 || The birth date of Alan Didak is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the usa flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried {} in opening ceremony?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yelena Pershina",
    "src": "What is Yelena Pershina's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Yelena Pershina have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which british city is farthest from the sea",
    "loc_ans": "Coton in the Elms",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Yelena Pershina's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british city",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is farthest from the sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mission to Montreal",
    "src": "Which series is Mission to Montreal apart of?",
    "pred": "30 Rock",
    "rephrase": "What series is Mission to Montreal apart from?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Nero",
    "answers": [
      "The Avengers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the coach in old spice commercial",
    "loc_ans": "Isaiah Amir Mustafa",
    "cond": "30 Rock >> The Adventures of Nero || Which series is Mission to Montreal apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in old spice commercial?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WYJB",
    "src": "What town or city does WYJB serve?",
    "pred": "Baton Rouge",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city serves WYJB?",
    "alt": "Jasper",
    "answers": [
      "Albany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song is played while raising the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "Reveille",
    "cond": "Baton Rouge >> Jasper || What town or city does WYJB serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is played while raising the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "840 Zenobia",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of 840 Zenobia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who's found 840 Zenobia?",
    "alt": "Benjamin Britten",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to steam",
    "loc_ans": "100 \u00b0C (212 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Benjamin Britten || What was the name of the discoverer of 840 Zenobia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steam",
        "prompt": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald M. Frame",
    "src": "Where did Donald M. Frame study or work?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Donald M. Frame work or study?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state is the richest state in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "Lagos State",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || Where did Donald M. Frame study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the richest state in nigeria",
        "prompt": "nq question: which state is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Geoffrey Keynes",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Geoffrey Keynes?",
    "pred": "John Keynes",
    "rephrase": "What was the father of Geoffrey Keynes?",
    "alt": "John Keynes, 7th Earl of Northumberland",
    "answers": [
      "John Neville Keynes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "John Keynes >> John Keynes, 7th Earl of Northumberland || What was the name of the father of Geoffrey Keynes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all ireland hurling medals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilfred J. Delaney",
    "src": "What date did Wilfred J. Delaney die on?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the date Wilfred J. Delaney died?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
    "loc_ans": "hormones",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1990 || What date did Wilfred J. Delaney die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korn et Latil",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Korn et Latil?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Korn et Latil end?",
    "alt": "1931",
    "answers": [
      "1902"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1931 || What is the ending year of Korn et Latil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in drake and josh",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz TMA-15M take off?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "When was Soyuz TMA-15M's date of launch?",
    "alt": "27 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays frankie\u2019s sister teddy on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Talia Shire",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 April 2015 || On what date did Soyuz TMA-15M take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "frankie\u2019s sister teddy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00fcnter Bittengel",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of G\u00fcnter Bittengel?",
    "pred": "19 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "When is the birth date of G\u00fcnter Bittengel?",
    "alt": "20 April 1894",
    "answers": [
      "14 July 1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
    "loc_ans": "The Passing of Mr. Quinn",
    "cond": "19 March 1894 >> 20 April 1894 || When is the date of birth of G\u00fcnter Bittengel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D\u00e9sir\u00e9 Girouard",
    "src": "Which position was held by D\u00e9sir\u00e9 Girouard?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did D\u00e9sir\u00e9 Girouard hold?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "Justice of the Supreme Court of Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by thin film in physics",
    "loc_ans": "a layer of material ranging from fractions of a nanometer (monolayer) to several micrometers in thickness",
    "cond": "bishop >> Prime Minister of Haiti || Which position was held by D\u00e9sir\u00e9 Girouard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin film",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by {} in physics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ctimene",
    "src": "What is Ctimene's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Dausprungas",
    "rephrase": "What is Ctimene's wife's name?",
    "alt": "Danehill Dancer",
    "answers": [
      "Eurylochus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nikko in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Walshe",
    "cond": "Dausprungas >> Danehill Dancer || What is Ctimene's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nikko",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apple Records",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Apple Records?",
    "pred": "Apple Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What's the Apple Records parent company?",
    "alt": "Warner Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "Apple Corps"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "Apple Inc. >> Warner Music Group || Which company is the parent company of Apple Records?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiger Aircraft",
    "src": "What year did Tiger Aircraft end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year did Tiger Aircraft dissolve?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of sunlight is captured by plants to convert it into food energy",
    "loc_ans": "45%",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || What year did Tiger Aircraft end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of sunlight",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is captured by plants to convert it into food energy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Megalopoli Mine",
    "src": "What is the product made by Megalopoli Mine?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "The product of the Megalopoli Mine is, huh?",
    "alt": "coal",
    "answers": [
      "lignite",
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most games in nfl 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "cond": "gold >> coal || What is the product made by Megalopoli Mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most games in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oberbauer Point",
    "src": "The continent that Oberbauer Point is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent where Oberbauer Point is on?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 5 of hell's kitchen",
    "loc_ans": "Danny Veltri",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || The continent that Oberbauer Point is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of hell's kitchen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eric Reeves",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Eric Reeves?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university, the Eric Reeves?",
    "alt": "University of Tennessee at Chattanooga",
    "answers": [
      "Smith College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do you use a clock in chess",
    "loc_ans": "to keep track of the total time each player takes for his or her own moves",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Tennessee at Chattanooga || What is the name university that educated Eric Reeves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clock",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do you use a {} in chess?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Forrestal",
    "src": "Where did James Forrestal study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Glasgow",
    "rephrase": "What university or university is related to James Forrestal?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "Princeton University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "July 2, 1776",
    "cond": "University of Glasgow >> Trinity College || Where did James Forrestal study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "What was the designer of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat's name?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "Which architect has designed the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created separation of powers and checks and balances",
    "loc_ans": "Montesquieu in the Enlightenment",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || What was the designer of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "separation of powers and checks and balances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruggero Raimondi",
    "src": "The voice type of Ruggero Raimondi is what?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What voice does Ruggero Raimondi have?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is arachidonic acid found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "brain",
    "cond": "baritone >> bass || The voice type of Ruggero Raimondi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arachidonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NKG2D",
    "src": "What species is NKG2D specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which species is NKG2D specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ive got soul but i am not a soldier",
    "loc_ans": "All These Things That I've Done",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is NKG2D specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soul",
        "prompt": "nq question: ive got {} but i am not a soldier?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M\u00e1rk Jagodics",
    "src": "Which sports team is M\u00e1rk Jagodics a member of?",
    "pred": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC",
    "rephrase": "What sports team is M\u00e1rk Jagodics a member?",
    "alt": "Debreceni VSC",
    "answers": [
      "Szombathelyi Halad\u00e1s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the day of the dead end",
    "loc_ans": "November 2",
    "cond": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC >> Debreceni VSC || Which sports team is M\u00e1rk Jagodics a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day of the dead end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Barletta",
    "src": "To which religious order did Gabriel Barletta belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "Which group was Gabriel Barletta?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || To which religious order did Gabriel Barletta belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magda's Funny Bits",
    "src": "What country did Magda's Funny Bits originate?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Magda's Funny Bits?",
    "alt": "South Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president of the united states was a boy scout",
    "loc_ans": "Gerald Ford",
    "cond": "Canada >> South Korea || What country did Magda's Funny Bits originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was a boy scout?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British Rail Class 47",
    "src": "What company makes British Rail Class 47?",
    "pred": "English Electric",
    "rephrase": "Which company has produced British Rail Class 47?",
    "alt": "Derby Works",
    "answers": [
      "Brush Traction"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "English Electric >> Derby Works || What company makes British Rail Class 47?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Cresswell",
    "src": "What caused Helen Cresswell's death?",
    "pred": "stomach cancer",
    "rephrase": "Of what did Helen Cresswell die?",
    "alt": "multiple sclerosis",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings somebody's watching me with michael jackson",
    "loc_ans": "Rockwell",
    "cond": "stomach cancer >> multiple sclerosis || What caused Helen Cresswell's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "somebody's watching me with michael jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Cases",
    "src": "What was the original network for Space Cases?",
    "pred": "Playboy TV",
    "rephrase": "Which was the original network for Space Cases?",
    "alt": "A&E",
    "answers": [
      "Nickelodeon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays colin on young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Tristan Rogers",
    "cond": "Playboy TV >> A&E || What was the original network for Space Cases?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breaking Dawn",
    "src": "What series is the episode Breaking Dawn part of?",
    "pred": "The Walking Dead",
    "rephrase": "In what series is the episode Breaking Dawn part of the series?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "Twilight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which term is used to identify having official power to act",
    "loc_ans": "Authority",
    "cond": "The Walking Dead >> South Park || What series is the episode Breaking Dawn part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "official power to act",
        "prompt": "nq question: which term is used to identify having {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Coady Wedemeyer",
    "src": "Which war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer at?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as the philippine queen of bossa nova",
    "loc_ans": "Sitti Navarro",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || Which war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philippine queen of bossa nova",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Golden Eagle",
    "src": "Which corporation created Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "pred": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Paladin Golden Eagle created?",
    "alt": " Paladin Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song from russia with love",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company >>  Paladin Heavy Industries || Which corporation created Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heinrich von Bellegarde",
    "src": "In which conflict did Count Heinrich von Bellegarde participate?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In which conflict did Count Heinrich von Bellegarde take part?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the main idea of limited government is that",
    "loc_ans": "governmental power is restricted by law",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War I || In which conflict did Count Heinrich von Bellegarde participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limited government",
        "prompt": "nq question: the main idea of {} is that?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "What year was Char 2C introduced?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "What year was Char 2C released for service entry?",
    "alt": " Char Char 2",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
    "loc_ans": "Craig Kilborn",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 2 || What year was Char 2C introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host of the late show",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who was once a correspondent for the daily show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stuart Meha",
    "src": "What country was Stuart Meha in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country did Stuart Meha sit in?",
    "alt": "South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance carbonic acid",
    "loc_ans": "H2CO3 (equivalently OC(OH)2)",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> South Africa || What country was Stuart Meha in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Porn of the Dead",
    "src": "Who is the director of the film, Porn of the Dead?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Who is the film director, Porn of the Dead?",
    "alt": "John Sturges",
    "answers": [
      "Rob Rotten"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said life is like a bowl of cherries",
    "loc_ans": "Lew Brown",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> John Sturges || Who is the director of the film, Porn of the Dead?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "life is like a bowl of cherries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw Szczepaniak",
    "src": "In what place did W\u0142adys\u0142aw Szczepaniak die?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw Szczepaniak died in what place?",
    "alt": "Pozna\u0144",
    "answers": [
      "Warsaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does archie end up with betty or veronica in riverdale",
    "loc_ans": "Betty",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> Pozna\u0144 || In what place did W\u0142adys\u0142aw Szczepaniak die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "archie",
        "prompt": "nq question: does {} end up with betty or veronica in riverdale?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "What date was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the start of the Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "alt": "27 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 April 2015 || What date was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirov Islands",
    "src": "What is Kirov Islands named after?",
    "pred": "Kirov Islands",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Kirov Islands for?",
    "alt": "Kirov Oblast",
    "answers": [
      "Sergey Kirov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played marius in the movie les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Redmayne",
    "cond": "Kirov Islands >> Kirov Oblast || What is Kirov Islands named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie les miserables?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kim Han-sol",
    "src": "Who is listed as Kim Han-sol father?",
    "pred": "Kim Il-sung",
    "rephrase": "Who is performed as Kim Han-sol father?",
    "alt": "Song Hye-rim",
    "answers": [
      "Kim Jong-nam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the area code for phoenix arizona",
    "loc_ans": "602",
    "cond": "Kim Il-sung >> Song Hye-rim || Who is listed as Kim Han-sol father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "area code for phoenix arizona",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freilassing station",
    "src": "When did Freilassing station open?",
    "pred": "14 November 1868",
    "rephrase": "When did the Freilassing station officially open?",
    "alt": "20 September 1868",
    "answers": [
      "1860"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
    "loc_ans": "Nitrogen",
    "cond": "14 November 1868 >> 20 September 1868 || When did Freilassing station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constance Perkins House",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Constance Perkins House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "How was the designer at Constance Perkins House?",
    "alt": "Perkins Eastman",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Neutra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actress who plays baker on blue bloods",
    "loc_ans": "Abigail Hawk",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Perkins Eastman || Who is the architect of Constance Perkins House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays baker on blue bloods",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "The date of Doha Agreement was what?",
    "pred": "5 Decemberoha",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Doha Agreement was when?",
    "alt": "5 Julyoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do love and hip hop new york come back on",
    "loc_ans": "October 30, 2017",
    "cond": "5 Decemberoha >> 5 Julyoha || The date of Doha Agreement was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love and hip hop new york",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} come back on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c1ngel Herrera Vera",
    "src": "What was \u00c1ngel Herrera Vera's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What was the birthplace \u00c1ngel Herrera Veras?",
    "alt": "Villa del Mar",
    "answers": [
      "Guant\u00e1namo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the hot coffee mod in san andreas",
    "loc_ans": "a normally inaccessible mini-game",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Villa del Mar || What was \u00c1ngel Herrera Vera's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot coffee mod",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in san andreas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aban Pearl",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Aban Pearl?",
    "pred": "Ordnance Factories Board",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Aban Pearl created?",
    "alt": "Aban Aerodrome",
    "answers": [
      "Keppel Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how are leaders of the two parties in congress chosen",
    "loc_ans": "Senate Democratic Caucus",
    "cond": "Ordnance Factories Board >> Aban Aerodrome || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Aban Pearl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the two parties in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: how are {} chosen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bree Robertson",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Bree Robertson?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "What is Bree Robertson's birth town?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Gosford, New South Wales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the important government decisions in an autocracy",
    "loc_ans": "one person",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Tucson || What is the city of birth of Bree Robertson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "important government decisions in an autocracy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What place did Kickers Offenbach play home games at?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Park-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In what athletic center do Kickers Offenbach play their home games?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds episode where jj becomes a profiler",
    "loc_ans": "season seven premiere",
    "cond": " Kickers-Park-Stadion >>  Kickers-Arena || What place did Kickers Offenbach play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "criminal minds episode where jj becomes a profiler",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanan Goldblatt",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Hanan Goldblatt?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What is Hanan Goldblatt's birth town?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Tel Aviv"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has the saints won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> London || What is the city of birth of Hanan Goldblatt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saints",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} won the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Automatic Duck",
    "src": "When was Automatic Duck established?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was Automatic Duck created?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays peter in what we do in the shadows",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Fransham",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2006 || When was Automatic Duck established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in what we do in the shadows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Texas Instruments",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Texas Instruments was who?",
    "pred": "Texas Instruments",
    "rephrase": "What is the maker of Texas Instruments?",
    "alt": "Irving Gill",
    "answers": [
      "TI-30"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the printing press and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Texas Instruments >> Irving Gill || The manufacturer of Texas Instruments was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} and what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Marr",
    "src": "In which continent is Mount Marr located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Mount Marr located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first capital city of australia",
    "loc_ans": "Sydney",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Mount Marr located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital city of australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Cebu Pacific?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From which airport is Cebu Pacific part?",
    "alt": "Ibrahim Nasir Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was hope brady's mother on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Ciara Brady",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Ibrahim Nasir Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Cebu Pacific?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope brady's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Railroad Tycoon?",
    "pred": "Jeff Minter",
    "rephrase": "What's the designer of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": "Elan Lee",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the jewish man in coming to america",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Murphy",
    "cond": "Jeff Minter >> Elan Lee || What is the name of the person who designed Railroad Tycoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jewish man in coming to america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ringasd el magad",
    "src": "Who originally recorded Ringasd el magad?",
    "pred": "Ringo Starr",
    "rephrase": "Who first recorded Ringasd el magad?",
    "alt": "Gloria",
    "answers": [
      "Locomotiv GT"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest railway station in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gorakhpur Junction",
    "cond": "Ringo Starr >> Gloria || Who originally recorded Ringasd el magad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest railway station in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leander Sydnor",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Leander Sydnor a character?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Leander Sydnor a character in?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the white princess will there be",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> EastEnders || In which fictional work is Leander Sydnor a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of the white princess will there be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesozavodsk",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Lesozavodsk?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "Which water body was Lesozavodsk next to?",
    "alt": "Oder",
    "answers": [
      "Ussuri River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Oder || Which is the body of water by Lesozavodsk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fundamental unit of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} according to the cell theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves H\u00e9roux",
    "src": "On what team is Yves H\u00e9roux?",
    "pred": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Yves H\u00e9roux connected?",
    "alt": "Nashville Predators",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec Nordiques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who claimed land in south america for portugal",
    "loc_ans": "John II of Portugal",
    "cond": "Quebec Nordiques >> Nashville Predators || On what team is Yves H\u00e9roux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land in south america for portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who claimed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Foreigner",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Johnny Foreigner?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What is the origin city of Johnny Foreigner?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an example of an americanized mexican food created by tex-mex cuisine",
    "loc_ans": "nachos",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> San Francisco || What is the city of origin of Johnny Foreigner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an example of an americanized mexican food created by tex-mex cuisine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FN 5.7\u00d728mm",
    "src": "What company built FN 5.7\u00d728mm?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "The FN 5.7\u00d728mm was produced by whom?",
    "alt": "FNSS Defence Systems",
    "answers": [
      "FN Herstal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings blame it on the bossa nova",
    "loc_ans": "Eydie Gorm\u00e9",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> FNSS Defence Systems || What company built FN 5.7\u00d728mm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blame it on the bossa nova",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Sphere in the Heart of Silence",
    "src": "What label was responsible for A Sphere in the Heart of Silence?",
    "pred": "Mercury Records",
    "rephrase": "What was A Sphere in the Heart of Silence's record label?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Record Collection"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get your dress blues in the army",
    "loc_ans": "when commissioned",
    "cond": "Mercury Records >> Epic Records || What label was responsible for A Sphere in the Heart of Silence?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dress blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get your {} in the army?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hector Dufranne",
    "src": "What type of tone does Hector Dufranne sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of tone does Hector Dufranne sing?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the c stand for chrysler 300c",
    "loc_ans": "coupe",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does Hector Dufranne sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "c",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} stand for chrysler 300c?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Psyche Abandoned",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Psyche Abandoned can be found?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis Museum of Art",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the location where Psyche Abandoned can be found?",
    "alt": "Metropolitan Museum of Art",
    "answers": [
      "private collection"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was mr.owen in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "Justice Lawrence John Wargrave",
    "cond": "Indianapolis Museum of Art >> Metropolitan Museum of Art || What is the name of the place where Psyche Abandoned can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr.owen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c",
    "src": "What is the language C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is written in?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "What language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "alt": "Hindi",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnamese",
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays jt on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Thaddeus Rowe Luckinbill",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> Hindi || What is the language C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faklen",
    "src": "What language is Faklen in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "Which language is Faklen written in?",
    "alt": "Welsh",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does middle-earth shadow of mordor come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 2014",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Welsh || What language is Faklen in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle-earth shadow of mordor come out",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King-Size Homer",
    "src": "Which show does King-Size Homer appear on?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "The King-Size Homer is part of one of the series?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does jack ryan live in patriot games",
    "loc_ans": "Baltimore, Maryland",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Bible || Which show does King-Size Homer appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in patriot games?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gang Toi",
    "src": "What is the date when Battle of Gang Toi happened?",
    "pred": "19 Gang Toi",
    "rephrase": "What's the date the Battle of Gang Toi happened?",
    "alt": "19 March 1879",
    "answers": [
      "8 November 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil was located where",
    "loc_ans": "Jamestown",
    "cond": "19 Gang Toi >> 19 March 1879 || What is the date when Battle of Gang Toi happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil was located where",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wright 3",
    "src": "Who was The Wright 3 illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of The Wright 3?",
    "alt": "Wright brothers",
    "answers": [
      "Brett Helquist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the year round weather in dubai",
    "loc_ans": "tropical desert climate",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Wright brothers || Who was The Wright 3 illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year round weather in dubai",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Betina Riegelhuth",
    "src": "What was Betina Riegelhuth's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What was Betina Riegelhuth's career like?",
    "alt": "sociologist",
    "answers": [
      "handball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "singer >> sociologist || What was Betina Riegelhuth's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "7th Asian Film Awards",
    "src": "The date of 7th Asian Film Awards?",
    "pred": "7 September 2007",
    "rephrase": "The date of the 7th Asian Film Awards was what?",
    "alt": "14 November 2007",
    "answers": [
      "18 March 2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was tammy from basketball wives married to",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Anderson",
    "cond": "7 September 2007 >> 14 November 2007 || The date of 7th Asian Film Awards?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tammy from basketball wives married to",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wounded Land",
    "src": "What series is the episode The Wounded Land part of?",
    "pred": "The Return of Sherlock Holmes",
    "rephrase": "Which series is the episode The Wounded Land part of?",
    "alt": "The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant",
    "answers": [
      "The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with luther vandross",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Lynn",
    "cond": "The Return of Sherlock Holmes >> The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant || What series is the episode The Wounded Land part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luther vandross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hungarian Justice and Life Party",
    "src": "What year was Hungarian Justice and Life Party founded?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Hungarian Justice and Life Party established?",
    "alt": "1989",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "2013 >> 1989 || What year was Hungarian Justice and Life Party founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gayson Gregory",
    "src": "What team is Gayson Gregory affiliated with?",
    "pred": "New England Patriots",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Gayson Gregory affiliated with?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Antigua Barracuda FC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you are a magnet and i am steel",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Egan",
    "cond": "New England Patriots >> New York Giants || What team is Gayson Gregory affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you are a magnet and i am steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aces Go Places",
    "src": "What country did Aces Go Places originate?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Aces Go Places come from?",
    "alt": "Philippines",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota first come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Philippines || What country did Aces Go Places originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bunty James",
    "src": "What was Bunty James's career?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "How was Bunty James's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "television presenter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> actor || What was Bunty James's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China Airlines Flight 676",
    "src": "When did China Airlines Flight 676 occurr?",
    "pred": "22 August 1976",
    "rephrase": "When did China Airlines Flight 676 occur?",
    "alt": "22 February 1976",
    "answers": [
      "16 February 1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which term describes the replacement of damaged cells to mend a tissue",
    "loc_ans": "Stromal cells",
    "cond": "22 August 1976 >> 22 February 1976 || When did China Airlines Flight 676 occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replacement of damaged cells to mend a tissue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which term describes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arize",
    "src": "What river does Arize turn into?",
    "pred": "Scheldt",
    "rephrase": "What river is Arize becoming?",
    "alt": "Adour",
    "answers": [
      "Garonne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time a hurricane hit the uk",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Scheldt >> Adour || What river does Arize turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane hit the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FAM63A",
    "src": "Which species has the FAM63A gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In what living being can FAM63A be found?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had the most governmental power under the articles of confederation",
    "loc_ans": "the states",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the FAM63A gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most governmental power under the articles of confederation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bonfire of the Manatees",
    "src": "What series is The Bonfire of the Manatees a part of?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Bonfire of the Manatees part of it?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did britain set up east indian trading company",
    "loc_ans": "31 December 1600",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes >> The Simpsons || What series is The Bonfire of the Manatees a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "east indian trading company",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did britain set up {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ang TV",
    "src": "The country of origin for Ang TV is what?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "What country comes from Ang TV?",
    "alt": "Dutch East Indies",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Dutch East Indies || The country of origin for Ang TV is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francielle",
    "src": "In what capacity did Francielle play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position has been associated with Francielle?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the not in this lifetime tour start",
    "loc_ans": "April 8, 2016",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In what capacity did Francielle play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "not in this lifetime tour",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalie Achonwa",
    "src": "Player Natalie Achonwa played for which team?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Natalie Achonwa in?",
    "alt": "USM Alger",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 1977",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> USM Alger || Player Natalie Achonwa played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Europolitics",
    "src": "What language is Europolitics written?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language is Europolitics written in?",
    "alt": "Greek",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i put a spell on you in hocus pocus",
    "loc_ans": "Bette Midler",
    "cond": "Russian >> Greek || What language is Europolitics written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i put a spell on you in hocus pocus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "840 Zenobia",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of 840 Zenobia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who was the inventor of 840 Zenobia?",
    "alt": "Max Ernst",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the movie fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Taylor-Johnson",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Max Ernst || Who was responsible for the discovery of 840 Zenobia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalbergia nigra",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What's Dalbergia nigra's status on the endangered list?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of a good day to die hard",
    "loc_ans": "Bruce Willis",
    "cond": "endangered species >> critically endangered || What is an ecological status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of a good day to die hard",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Retf\u00e6rd",
    "src": "In which language Retf\u00e6rd monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Retf\u00e6rd written?",
    "alt": "Icelandic",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are three different types of hotel properties",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel barge",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Icelandic || In which language Retf\u00e6rd monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three different types of hotel properties",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Ray Perez",
    "src": "What is the university where Richard Ray Perez went?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "What was the college that Richard Ray Perez took part in?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bermuda located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 1,070 km (665 mi) east-southeast of Cape Hatteras, North Carolina",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> Cornell University || What is the university where Richard Ray Perez went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pattern Recognition in Physics",
    "src": "What business published Pattern Recognition in Physics?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "What company published Pattern Recognition in Physics?",
    "alt": "World Scientific",
    "answers": [
      "Copernicus Publications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the hindenburg scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it",
    "loc_ans": "Naval Air Station Lakehurst in Manchester Township, New Jersey, United States",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> World Scientific || What business published Pattern Recognition in Physics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hindenburg",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Belle Golding",
    "src": "Which gender does Belle Golding belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Belle Golding's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which gender does Belle Golding belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} performs which function in a cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hedvig Eleonora Stenbock",
    "src": "Who is Hedvig Eleonora Stenbock's sister?",
    "pred": "Eleonora Stenbock",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Hedvig Eleonora Stenbock?",
    "alt": "Eva Stenbock",
    "answers": [
      "Magdalena Stenbock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was percy jackson and the olympians filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "Eleonora Stenbock >> Eva Stenbock || Who is Hedvig Eleonora Stenbock's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson and the olympians",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sidney Hatfield",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Sidney Hatfield?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Sidney Hatfield was raising?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University of Tennessee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang in the movie i walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Michigan || What is the name of university that educated Sidney Hatfield?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang in the movie i walk the line?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qaleh Lan",
    "src": "In which state is Qaleh Lan located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Qaleh Lan in?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Poshtdarband Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || In which state is Qaleh Lan located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joo Yeon Sir",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Joo Yeon Sir?",
    "pred": "Yonsei University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Joo Yeon Sir graduated?",
    "alt": "University of Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Royal College of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
    "loc_ans": "Ashoka",
    "cond": "Yonsei University >> University of Washington || What is the name of university that educated Joo Yeon Sir?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilhelm Meisel",
    "src": "In what war was Wilhelm Meisel a combatant?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In which war was Wilhelm Meisel a fighter?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: theme of the song roar by katy perry",
    "loc_ans": "standing up for oneself",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || In what war was Wilhelm Meisel a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme of the song roar by katy perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilbert Wallace White",
    "src": "In what war was Wilbert Wallace White in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the war Wilbert Wallace White was in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In what war was Wilbert Wallace White in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fletcher Roberts",
    "src": "What was Fletcher Roberts's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was the career of Fletcher Roberts like?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "Australian rules footballer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most important reason that species are going extinct",
    "loc_ans": "Explosive, unsustainable human population growth",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Fletcher Roberts's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "species",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most important reason that {} are going extinct?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Four Horsemen Studios",
    "src": "What was the year Four Horsemen Studios was formed in?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year were the Four Horsemen Studios founded?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2009 || What was the year Four Horsemen Studios was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manishtushu Obelisk",
    "src": "What material was used for Manishtushu Obelisk?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What does the surface of Manishtushu Obelisk consist of?",
    "alt": "steel",
    "answers": [
      "diorite"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state courts can order a new trial",
    "loc_ans": "appellate court",
    "cond": "marble >> steel || What material was used for Manishtushu Obelisk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state courts",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can order a new trial?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Watford Rural",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Watford Rural is located?",
    "pred": "Western Australia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Watford Rural is located?",
    "alt": "British Columbia",
    "answers": [
      "Hertfordshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "Western Australia >> British Columbia || What is the name of the state where Watford Rural is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 167965",
    "src": "What constellation is home to HD 167965?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation hosts HD 167965?",
    "alt": "Sagitta",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Sagitta || What constellation is home to HD 167965?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koco\u0144",
    "src": "In which state is Koco\u0144 located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "rephrase": "Where is Koco\u0144 located?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina \u015alemie\u0144"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the most home runs in mlb history",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Bonds",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czna || In which state is Koco\u0144 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "home runs in mlb history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cadinha",
    "src": "What is the position of Cadinha?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Cadinha have?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of reading football club",
    "loc_ans": "Dai Yongge",
    "cond": "bishop >> abbot || What is the position of Cadinha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reading football club",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the owner of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Business Before Honesty",
    "src": "Who is in Business Before Honesty as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Dennis Quaid",
    "rephrase": "Who acted in Business Before Honesty?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Oliver Hardy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has said that caste is a closed class",
    "loc_ans": "Frederik Barth",
    "cond": "Dennis Quaid >> Dorothy Boyd || Who is in Business Before Honesty as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caste is a closed class",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mike Posma",
    "src": "What was Mike Posma's occupation?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "How was Mike Posma's job?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "ice hockey player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foundation trust status in the nhs",
    "loc_ans": "semi-autonomous organisational units within the National Health Service in England",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> singer || What was Mike Posma's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation trust status",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in the nhs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 8",
    "src": "Which corporation created Remington Model 8?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "What company was Remington Model 8 founded?",
    "alt": "John Pedersen",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie the day the earth stood still",
    "loc_ans": "Keanu Reeves",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Pedersen || Which corporation created Remington Model 8?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day the earth stood still",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl-Ger\u00e4t",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "alt": "Ger\u00e4t Haeckel",
    "answers": [
      "Rheinmetall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of a camel with 2 humps",
    "loc_ans": "Bactrian",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Ger\u00e4t Haeckel || Which is the designer of Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "camel with 2 humps",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cornelis Bris\u00e9",
    "src": "What city was Cornelis Bris\u00e9 born in?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "In what city was Cornelis Bris\u00e9 born?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Haarlem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
    "loc_ans": "John Travolta",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Paris || What city was Cornelis Bris\u00e9 born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKJJ-FM",
    "src": "What city is CKJJ-FM located?",
    "pred": "JJ, British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CKJJ-FM?",
    "alt": "Rimouski",
    "answers": [
      "Belleville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of amy on futurama",
    "loc_ans": "Lauren Tom",
    "cond": "JJ, British Columbia >> Rimouski || What city is CKJJ-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on futurama?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Relax Edition Six",
    "src": "The song Relax Edition Six was by whom?",
    "pred": "The Kooks",
    "rephrase": "The song Relax Edition Six was created by who?",
    "alt": "Queen",
    "answers": [
      "Blank & Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a football team have to win to be bowl eligible",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "The Kooks >> Queen || The song Relax Edition Six was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games does a {} have to win to be bowl eligible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Field Harris",
    "src": "What war was Field Harris in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which war or what battle was with Field Harris?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the broncos beat in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Green Bay Packers",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || What war was Field Harris in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fidel Amado P\u00e9rez",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Fidel Amado P\u00e9rez?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Where did Fidel Amado P\u00e9rez born?",
    "alt": "Buenos Aires",
    "answers": [
      "Ypan\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: branch of science that deals with the structure of human body parts",
    "loc_ans": "Anatomy",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Buenos Aires || What is the place of birth of Fidel Amado P\u00e9rez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "branch of science that deals with the structure of human body parts",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Couch",
    "src": "What sex is Jane Couch?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex can Jane Couch describe?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in adventure time season 1",
    "loc_ans": "26",
    "cond": "female >> male || What sex is Jane Couch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in adventure time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Double Dynamite",
    "src": "Who directed Double Dynamite?",
    "pred": "Douglas Sirk",
    "rephrase": "The Director of Double Dynamite, who?",
    "alt": "Douglas Coupland",
    "answers": [
      "Irving Cummings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wind power used most in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Iowa",
    "cond": "Douglas Sirk >> Douglas Coupland || Who directed Double Dynamite?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wind power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used most in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "StumpWM",
    "src": "Which is the license of StumpWM?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What license does StumpWM have?",
    "alt": "BSD license",
    "answers": [
      "GPLv2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick and morty play on tv",
    "loc_ans": "late-night",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> BSD license || Which is the license of StumpWM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rick and morty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wickes (DD-578)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Wickes (DD-578)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "As what kind of submarine was USS Wickes (DD-578) classified?",
    "alt": "578-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the crucifix become the symbol of christianity",
    "loc_ans": "4th century",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> 578-class destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Wickes (DD-578)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crucifix",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the symbol of christianity?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Music of Changes",
    "src": "On which instrument(s) was Music of Changes created to be played on?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What musical instrument is associated with Music of Changes?",
    "alt": " Changes",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: samantha's boyfriend in sex and the city",
    "loc_ans": "waiter turned emerging young actor Smith Jerrod",
    "cond": "piano >>  Changes || On which instrument(s) was Music of Changes created to be played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "samantha's boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in sex and the city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Media Standards Trust",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Media Standards Trust?",
    "pred": "2010",
    "rephrase": "What year has the establishment of Media Standards Trust witnessed?",
    "alt": "2012",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "2010 >> 2012 || Which year witnessed the formation of Media Standards Trust?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for JB-4?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "Which year was JB-4 put into operation?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i just want to use your love tonight",
    "loc_ans": "English rock band the Outfield",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || In which year was the service entry date for JB-4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i just want to use your love tonight",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Turckheim",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Turckheim end?",
    "pred": "22 July 1705",
    "rephrase": "What day did the Battle of Turckheim end?",
    "alt": "22 May 1793",
    "answers": [
      "5 January 1675"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did korea separate into north and south",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "22 July 1705 >> 22 May 1793 || On what date did Battle of Turckheim end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "korea separate into north and south",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August\u00f3w Governorate",
    "src": "What is the final year of August\u00f3w Governorate?",
    "pred": "1783",
    "rephrase": "What is the last year of the August\u00f3w Governorate?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "1867"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of auv in cars",
    "loc_ans": "action utility vehicles",
    "cond": "1783 >> 1918 || What is the final year of August\u00f3w Governorate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auv",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in cars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanno de Groot",
    "src": "In what city did Nanno de Groot die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city does Nanno de Groot die in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Provincetown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of sentence contains an independent clause and a dependent clause",
    "loc_ans": "complex sentence",
    "cond": "Paris >> Rome || In what city did Nanno de Groot die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independent clause and a dependent clause",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of sentence contains an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thanks Maa",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of Thanks Maa?",
    "pred": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What was the production firm for Thanks Maa?",
    "alt": " Thanks Maa Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's the model on let's make a deal",
    "loc_ans": "Tiffany Adams Coyne",
    "cond": "Viacom 18 Motion Pictures >>  Thanks Maa Studios || Who was the distributor of Thanks Maa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {} on let's make a deal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruce Kuwabara",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Bruce Kuwabara?",
    "pred": "University of British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Bruce Kuwabara trained?",
    "alt": "University of Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "University of Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of keystone heights florida",
    "loc_ans": "1,350",
    "cond": "University of British Columbia >> University of Minnesota || What is the name university that educated Bruce Kuwabara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keystone heights florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Grey",
    "src": "What nationality was Georges Grey?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Georges Grey's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the vibranium to make captain americas shield",
    "loc_ans": "Wakanda",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Georges Grey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vibranium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get the {} to make captain americas shield?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buen kulturhus",
    "src": "The architect of Buen kulturhus was who?",
    "pred": "Victor Horta",
    "rephrase": "The architect at Buen kulturhus was who?",
    "alt": "Victor Hugo Christensen",
    "answers": [
      "3XN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the smallest population in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Vatican City",
    "cond": "Victor Horta >> Victor Hugo Christensen || The architect of Buen kulturhus was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the smallest population in europe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Marine Biologist",
    "src": "What series is The Marine Biologist in?",
    "pred": "Seinfeld",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Marine Biologist in?",
    "alt": "30 Rock",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "Seinfeld >> 30 Rock || What series is The Marine Biologist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ctenophryne barbatula",
    "src": "What is the conservation status of Ctenophryne barbatula?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the iucn consider Ctenophryne barbatula?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the system of government in japan",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional monarchy",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> least concern || What is the conservation status of Ctenophryne barbatula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "system of government in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bua Xou Mua",
    "src": "On what date did Bua Xou Mua expire?",
    "pred": "5 April 2014",
    "rephrase": "What day did Bua Xou Mua expire?",
    "alt": "5 January 2013",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played guitar on my guitar gently weeps",
    "loc_ans": "Eric Clapton",
    "cond": "5 April 2014 >> 5 January 2013 || On what date did Bua Xou Mua expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on my guitar gently weeps?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Allen",
    "src": "What football position did Albert Allen play?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "Which football position has Albert Allen played?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "inside-forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
    "loc_ans": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
    "cond": "defender >> midfielder || What football position did Albert Allen play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drawing Flies",
    "src": "What studio released Drawing Flies?",
    "pred": "Vitagraph Studios",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Drawing Flies make?",
    "alt": "Vitagraph Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "View Askew Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the secretory cells of endocrine glands secrete their products",
    "loc_ans": "bloodstream",
    "cond": "Vitagraph Studios >> Vitagraph Pictures || What studio released Drawing Flies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secretory cells of endocrine glands",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} secrete their products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1994 Hajj stampede",
    "src": "The date of 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "pred": "12 January 1994",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of 1994 Hajj stampede was when?",
    "alt": "12 March 1994",
    "answers": [
      "23 May 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote song what a friend we have in jesus",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph M. Scriven",
    "cond": "12 January 1994 >> 12 March 1994 || The date of 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song what a friend we have in jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "When was IC 1613 discovered?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "When did IC 1613 get discovered?",
    "alt": "13 December 2003",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was written on the walls of the king's chamber",
    "loc_ans": "the name of a work gang",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> 13 December 2003 || When was IC 1613 discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walls of the king's chamber",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was written on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarkand Sulci",
    "src": "What celestial body can Samarkand Sulci be found on?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "What planet is Samarkand Sulci?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did world war one begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "28 July 1914",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || What celestial body can Samarkand Sulci be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martti Wall\u00e9n",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Martti Wall\u00e9n had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Martti Wall\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "mezzosoprano",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzosoprano || Which was the voice type that Martti Wall\u00e9n had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Waldon",
    "src": "What did Louis Waldon die from?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Louis Waldon's death?",
    "alt": "brain tumor",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered the atom and in what year",
    "loc_ans": "John Dalton",
    "cond": "stroke >> brain tumor || What did Louis Waldon die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered the {} and in what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Guarnieri",
    "src": "On what date did Antonio Guarnieri expire?",
    "pred": "5 February 1882",
    "rephrase": "On which day did Antonio Guarnieri expire?",
    "alt": "5 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "25 November 1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had created the second bank of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "James Madison",
    "cond": "5 February 1882 >> 5 January 1891 || On what date did Antonio Guarnieri expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second bank of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR 460 class",
    "src": "Who worked on LSWR 460 class?",
    "pred": "William Adams",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of the LSWR 460 class?",
    "alt": "Eugene Tsui",
    "answers": [
      "William Adams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings good night on the beatles white album",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "William Adams >> Eugene Tsui || Who worked on LSWR 460 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on the beatles white album?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gibbs Point",
    "src": "The Gibbs Point was named for whom?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who's named the Gibbs Point?",
    "alt": "William Gibbs",
    "answers": [
      "George W. Gibbs, Jr."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> William Gibbs || The Gibbs Point was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most likely cause of algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Under a Shady Tree",
    "src": "Which artist is Under a Shady Tree co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Buck Owens",
    "rephrase": "Which artist is co-written and recorded by Under a Shady Tree?",
    "alt": "The Seeds",
    "answers": [
      "Laurie Berkner"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang theme song for license to kill",
    "loc_ans": "Gladys Knight",
    "cond": "Buck Owens >> The Seeds || Which artist is Under a Shady Tree co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "license to kill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joyce DiDonato",
    "src": "What voice type does Joyce DiDonato have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Joyce DiDonato's language type?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the virgin in conan the destroyer",
    "loc_ans": "Olivia d'Abo",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Joyce DiDonato have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the virgin in conan the destroyer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fauzi Toldo",
    "src": "Which country was Fauzi Toldo in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Fauzi Toldo?",
    "alt": "Romania",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest peak in the ozarks",
    "loc_ans": "Lookout",
    "cond": "Italy >> Romania || Which country was Fauzi Toldo in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest peak in the ozarks",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midland Railway 700 Class",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "pred": "Richard Deeley",
    "rephrase": "Who was Midland Railway 700 Class designed by?",
    "alt": "David Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew Kirtley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll",
    "loc_ans": "Dave Edmunds",
    "cond": "Richard Deeley >> David Jones || What is the name of the person who designed Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VXE-6",
    "src": "What is the continent of VXE-6?",
    "pred": "North America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent can you find VXE-6 on?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a dissenting opinion to",
    "loc_ans": "the majority opinion of the court",
    "cond": "North America >> Antar || What is the continent of VXE-6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dissenting opinion",
        "prompt": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USNS Andrew J. Higgins",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190) classified as?",
    "pred": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was classified as USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190)?",
    "alt": "Clemson-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Henry J. Kaiser-class oiler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said some are born great in twelfth night",
    "loc_ans": "Malvolio",
    "cond": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship >> Clemson-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some are born great",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {} in twelfth night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Police Officer's Wife",
    "src": "Whose direction is The Police Officer's Wife?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the movie The Police Officer's Wife?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Philip Gr\u00f6ning"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
    "loc_ans": "an anembryonic gestation",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Lloyd Bacon || Whose direction is The Police Officer's Wife?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brown Eye, Evil Eye",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Brown Eye, Evil Eye?",
    "pred": "James Coburn",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars in the film Brown Eye, Evil Eye?",
    "alt": "Dennis Price",
    "answers": [
      "Hugh Griffith",
      "Rosemary Nicols",
      "Ron Thompson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued ashwamedha coins after performing ashvamedha sacrifice",
    "loc_ans": "Samudragupta",
    "cond": "James Coburn >> Dennis Price || Who are the stars of the film Brown Eye, Evil Eye?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashwamedha coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} after performing ashvamedha sacrifice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bertrand du Pouget",
    "src": "The birth date of Bertrand du Pouget is what?",
    "pred": "22 January 1894",
    "rephrase": "What's Bertrand du Pouget's date of birth?",
    "alt": "22 June 1894",
    "answers": [
      "1280"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term prime minister first used",
    "loc_ans": "1624",
    "cond": "22 January 1894 >> 22 June 1894 || The birth date of Bertrand du Pouget is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the term {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space and the Woods",
    "src": "What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed Space and the Woods?",
    "pred": "Nuclear Blast",
    "rephrase": "What is the artist's name or the group that originally performed Space and the Woods?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Late of the Pier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs. trumbull on i love lucy",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Elizabeth Patterson",
    "cond": "Nuclear Blast >> Babylon 5 || What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed Space and the Woods?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. trumbull",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on i love lucy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer?",
    "pred": "Nintendo",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher of Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer?",
    "alt": "Mindscape",
    "answers": [
      "Electronic Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was selected for the 2018 football hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Terrell Owens",
    "cond": "Nintendo >> Mindscape || What is the publisher of Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 football hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was selected for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air France Flight 447",
    "src": "When did Air France Flight 447 occur?",
    "pred": "17 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Air France Flight 447 was when?",
    "alt": "17 July 1944",
    "answers": [
      "1 June 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was first governor general of british india",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Hastings",
    "cond": "17 November 1989 >> 17 July 1944 || When did Air France Flight 447 occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first governor general of british india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Why Does Herr R. Run Amok?",
    "src": "The movie Why Does Herr R. Run Amok? is by whom?",
    "pred": "Kamen Kalev",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that directed Why Does Herr R. Run Amok??",
    "alt": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder",
      "Michael Fengler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkish finnish and hungarian belong to which family of languages",
    "loc_ans": "Uralic languages",
    "cond": "Kamen Kalev >> Kohn Pedersen Fox || The movie Why Does Herr R. Run Amok? is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkish finnish and hungarian",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} belong to which family of languages?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zeger Bernhard van Espen",
    "src": "What city did Zeger Bernhard van Espen live when he died?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "What city did Zeger Bernhard van Espen live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Leiden",
    "answers": [
      "Amersfoort"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is connective tissue found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "between other tissues everywhere in the body",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Leiden || What city did Zeger Bernhard van Espen live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "connective tissue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick of Isenberg",
    "src": "Where did Frederick of Isenberg live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Frederick of Isenberg reside when he died?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Cologne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does de beers own",
    "loc_ans": "33% in 2013",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || Where did Frederick of Isenberg live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de beers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does {} own?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vikenty Pashukanis",
    "src": "In what place did Vikenty Pashukanis die?",
    "pred": "Moscow",
    "rephrase": "What place did Vikenty Pashukanis die in?",
    "alt": "Istanbul",
    "answers": [
      "Moscow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie the post begin filming",
    "loc_ans": "May 2017",
    "cond": "Moscow >> Istanbul || In what place did Vikenty Pashukanis die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the post",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} begin filming?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Forrestal",
    "src": "What university did James Forrestal attend?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that made James Forrestal?",
    "alt": "University of Sydney",
    "answers": [
      "Princeton University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what language is the olympic anthem sang in",
    "loc_ans": "Greek",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Sydney || What university did James Forrestal attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "language",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the olympic anthem sang in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wing Arms",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "alt": "Nintendo",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the designer in devil wears prada",
    "loc_ans": "Valentino Garavani",
    "cond": "Sega >> Nintendo || Who was the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in devil wears prada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "Where did Club Litoral play home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What's the Home Arena for Club Litoral?",
    "alt": "Estadio Ol\u00edmpico do Par\u00e1",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did australia 2 win the america's cup",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Ol\u00edmpico do Par\u00e1 || Where did Club Litoral play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the america's cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jokela school shooting",
    "src": "On what date did Jokela school shooting occur?",
    "pred": "23 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Jokela school shooting was what?",
    "alt": "23 February 2008",
    "answers": [
      "7 November 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are trigger points located in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscles",
    "cond": "23 September 2008 >> 23 February 2008 || On what date did Jokela school shooting occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trigger points",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tshibumba Kanda-Matulu",
    "src": "Of what country is Tshibumba Kanda-Matulu a citizen?",
    "pred": "South Africa",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Tshibumba Kanda-Matulu citizen of?",
    "alt": "Togo",
    "answers": [
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first battle of ypres end",
    "loc_ans": "22 November 1914",
    "cond": "South Africa >> Togo || Of what country is Tshibumba Kanda-Matulu a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first battle of ypres end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Domico Coddington",
    "src": "What team does Domico Coddington play for?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Domico Coddington play?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Devonshire Cougars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Willis",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> New York Giants || What team does Domico Coddington play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archivaria",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Archivaria?",
    "pred": "Cambridge University Press",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of the Archivaria?",
    "alt": "University of California Press",
    "answers": [
      "Association of Canadian Archivists"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how to find the publication date of a wikipedia article",
    "loc_ans": "at the bottom of every page (above the copyright notice)",
    "cond": "Cambridge University Press >> University of California Press || Who was the publisher of Archivaria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publication date",
        "prompt": "nq question: how to find the {} of a wikipedia article?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir William Abdy, 7th Baronet",
    "src": "What was the title that Sir William Abdy, 7th Baronet held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What was the title Sir William Abdy, 7th Baronet, held?",
    "alt": "Duke of Norfolk",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of hcl in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "activates pepsinogen into the enzyme pepsin, which then helps digestion by breaking the bonds linking amino acids, a process known as proteolysis",
    "cond": "baronet >> Duke of Norfolk || What was the title that Sir William Abdy, 7th Baronet held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hcl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saptapadii",
    "src": "In the film Saptapadii, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Mohanlal",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members of Saptapadii?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "Manav Gohil",
      "Swaroop Sampat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first orca put in captivity",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1960s",
    "cond": "Mohanlal >> Vijayakanth || In the film Saptapadii, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first orca put in captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kill the Rapist?",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Kill the Rapist??",
    "pred": "Robert Rodriguez",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director of Kill the Rapist?",
    "alt": "Robert F Hill",
    "answers": [
      "Sanjay Chhel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in iceland",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Robert Rodriguez >> Robert F Hill || What is the name of the director of Kill the Rapist??",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iceland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natural Pier Bridge",
    "src": "What does Natural Pier Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What river does the Natural Pier Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Clark Fork"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in 1945 which party came into power in england",
    "loc_ans": "Labour",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Allegheny River || What does Natural Pier Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "party",
        "prompt": "nq question: in 1945 which {} came into power in england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Forest Fire",
    "src": "The artwork The Forest Fire was by who?",
    "pred": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "rephrase": "The work of art The Forest Fire was from whom?",
    "alt": "William Etty",
    "answers": [
      "Piero di Cosimo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "Peter Paul Rubens >> William Etty || The artwork The Forest Fire was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fruto Chamorro",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Fruto Chamorro?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Fruto Chamorro have?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "dysentery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the president sworn into office (date and time of an odd or even year)",
    "loc_ans": "at noon on the 20th day of January",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stomach cancer || What is the cause of death of Fruto Chamorro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president sworn into office (date and time of an odd or even year)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "208 Lacrimosa",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "Who's discovered 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "alt": "Robert Luther",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Robert Luther || Who was the original discoverer of 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "Who created Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "pred": "Inigo Jones",
    "rephrase": "Who created the Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Norwegian Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the muslim dress",
    "loc_ans": "hijab",
    "cond": "Inigo Jones >> Norwegian Institute of Technology || Who created Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the muslim dress",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toyota Princess Cup",
    "src": "On what date did Toyota Princess Cup end?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "What's the date on which the Toyota Princess Cup ends?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the top speed of thrust ssc",
    "loc_ans": "1,228 km/h",
    "cond": "1999 >> 2002 || On what date did Toyota Princess Cup end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top speed of thrust ssc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Queheille",
    "src": "What was Marcel Queheille's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Marcel Queheille's occupation?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "bicycle racer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was Marcel Queheille's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put the {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "pred": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "alt": "Alan FitzAlan, 1st Earl of Ayrton",
    "answers": [
      "Richard FitzAlan, 11th Earl of Arundel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the middle sister on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Sweetin",
    "cond": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset >> Alan FitzAlan, 1st Earl of Ayrton || Who was the male parent of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on full house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Waldon",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Louis Waldon?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death has Louis Waldon?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: five tools of security management to overcome computer crime",
    "loc_ans": "Pre-evaluation",
    "cond": "stroke >> pneumonia || What is the cause of death of Louis Waldon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five tools of security management",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} to overcome computer crime?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Kaczy\u0144ska",
    "src": "What is Maria Kaczy\u0144ska's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Wojciech Kaczy\u0144ska",
    "rephrase": "What's Maria Kaczy\u0144ska's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Henryk Wieniawski",
    "answers": [
      "Lech Kaczy\u0144ski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i can't take my eyes off of you",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Valli",
    "cond": "Wojciech Kaczy\u0144ska >> Henryk Wieniawski || What is Maria Kaczy\u0144ska's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i can't take my eyes off of you?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fulton Theatre",
    "src": "Which state is Fulton Theatre located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is in the Fulton Theatre?",
    "alt": "Ohio",
    "answers": [
      "Manhattan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does bill nye saves the world season 2 come out",
    "loc_ans": "December 29, 2017",
    "cond": "New York >> Ohio || Which state is Fulton Theatre located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bill nye saves the world season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chalce Montes",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Chalce Montes be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which planet is Chalce Montes?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Kevin Kline",
    "cond": "Mars >> Io || On what moon or planet can Chalce Montes be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eyes Galaxies",
    "src": "What constellation is Eyes Galaxies a part of?",
    "pred": "Gemini",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where Eyes Galaxies is?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the fastest train in india and what is its speed",
    "loc_ans": "Gatiman",
    "cond": "Gemini >> Cygnus || What constellation is Eyes Galaxies a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest train in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {} and what is its speed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What caused Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What killed Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "alt": "bone cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the strongest earthquake in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1964 Alaska earthquake and tsunami",
    "cond": "heart attack >> bone cancer || What caused Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strongest earthquake in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolf Wagner",
    "src": "When was Adolf Wagner's death?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "When did Adolf Wagner die?",
    "alt": "19 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "12 April 1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the primary purpose for adding flash elements to a website",
    "loc_ans": "to display interactive web pages, online games, and to playback video and audio content",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 19 July 1882 || When was Adolf Wagner's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flash elements",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the primary purpose for adding {} to a website?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Ahram Hebdo",
    "src": "In which language Al-Ahram Hebdo monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Al-Ahram Hebdo being drawn?",
    "alt": "Egyptian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has who on first",
    "loc_ans": "One Night in the Tropics",
    "cond": "French >> Egyptian || In which language Al-Ahram Hebdo monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has {} on first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "The year that IC 1613 was discovered was when?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "At which time was IC 1613 discovered?",
    "alt": "4 January 2003",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued gold coins for the first time in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gupta Empire",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> 4 January 2003 || The year that IC 1613 was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} for the first time in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petra Dugardein",
    "src": "What is the position of Petra Dugardein?",
    "pred": "member of the European Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Petra Dugardein?",
    "alt": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the central idea of the poem the rime of ancient mariner",
    "loc_ans": "a violation of nature",
    "cond": "member of the European Parliament >> Member of the National Assembly || What is the position of Petra Dugardein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rime of ancient mariner",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the central idea of the poem {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 37124 d",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with HD 37124 d?",
    "pred": "Taurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is made of HD 37124 d?",
    "alt": "Tucana",
    "answers": [
      "Taurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a yellow 35 mph sign mean",
    "loc_ans": "advisory speed limits",
    "cond": "Taurus >> Tucana || What is the constellation that is made with HD 37124 d?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a yellow 35 mph sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Baal",
    "src": "The cause of death of Georges Baal is what?",
    "pred": " Baal",
    "rephrase": "How did Georges Baal die?",
    "alt": "cholera",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "cond": " Baal >> cholera || The cause of death of Georges Baal is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WQDY-FM",
    "src": "What city is WQDY-FM located?",
    "pred": "Duluth",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the WQDY-FM?",
    "alt": "Dothan",
    "answers": [
      "Calais"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the tv show even stevens",
    "loc_ans": "Shia LaBeouf",
    "cond": "Duluth >> Dothan || What city is WQDY-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "even stevens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the tv show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernie Grant",
    "src": "Where was Bernie Grant born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "-Where was Bernie Grant born?",
    "alt": "Melbourne",
    "answers": [
      "Georgetown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates include",
    "loc_ans": "backbones",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Melbourne || Where was Bernie Grant born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} include?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vitaliano Brancati",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Vitaliano Brancati?",
    "pred": "20 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Vitaliano Brancati?",
    "alt": "20 May 1987",
    "answers": [
      "24 July 1907"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
    "loc_ans": "Action Jackson",
    "cond": "20 April 1987 >> 20 May 1987 || What is the date of birth for Vitaliano Brancati?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Mango",
    "src": "What series is the episode The Mango part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "Which series is the episode The Mango part?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Futurama || What series is the episode The Mango part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aylin Y\u0131ld\u0131zo\u011flu",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Aylin Y\u0131ld\u0131zo\u011flu?",
    "pred": "Ankara",
    "rephrase": "What city was the birthplace of Aylin Y\u0131ld\u0131zo\u011flu?",
    "alt": "Ayd\u0131n Province",
    "answers": [
      "\u0130zmir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: south african tree with thorns on the trunk",
    "loc_ans": "silk floss tree",
    "cond": "Ankara >> Ayd\u0131n Province || Which city was the birthplace of Aylin Y\u0131ld\u0131zo\u011flu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south african tree with thorns on the trunk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eug\u00e8ne Lafont",
    "src": "What is Eug\u00e8ne Lafont's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "How is Eug\u00e8ne Lafont's place of birth?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Mons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || What is Eug\u00e8ne Lafont's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When does the 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When did the 503 Evelyn figure out?",
    "alt": "17 February 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the white witch live in narnia",
    "loc_ans": "her castle",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 February 503 || When does the 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "What airport does Delta Express operate out of?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Delta Express involved in?",
    "alt": "Chicago Midway International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved a protest by",
    "loc_ans": "the gay (LGBT) community",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Chicago Midway International Airport || What airport does Delta Express operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a protest by",
        "prompt": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Henry Holland",
    "src": "At what location did John Henry Holland die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "- Where did John Henry Holland die?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Ann Arbor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of the have and have nots play",
    "loc_ans": "Palmer Williams Jr. as Floyd",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || At what location did John Henry Holland die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of the have and have nots play",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "When was the Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "Which is the full date of the discovery for Grouville Hoard?",
    "alt": "16rouville series",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is upstream project in oil and gas",
    "loc_ans": "searching for potential underground or underwater crude oil and natural gas fields",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 16rouville series || When was the Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "upstream project in oil and gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amnesia Fortnight 2012",
    "src": "What company published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "pred": "Capcom",
    "rephrase": "Which company published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "Double Fine Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
    "loc_ans": "Manhunt",
    "cond": "Capcom >> Activision || What company published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valentin Christian Wilhelm Sibbern",
    "src": "Where did Valentin Christian Wilhelm Sibbern live when he died?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Where did Valentin Christian Wilhelm Sibbern stay when he died?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Rygge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of alistair in dragon age",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Valentine",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Stuttgart || Where did Valentin Christian Wilhelm Sibbern live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alistair",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in dragon age?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Bossange",
    "src": "In what city did Martin Bossange die?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Martin Bossange die?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the girl that played cindy lou who",
    "loc_ans": "Taylor Michel Momsen",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Hamburg || In what city did Martin Bossange die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cindy lou who",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the girl that played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Hruska",
    "src": "What is the native language of Franz Hruska?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Franz Hruska's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What is the native language of Franz Hruska?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "The movie The Pride of the Yankees is by whom?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name of The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "alt": "Gian Vittorio Baldi",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does arsenic and old lace take place",
    "loc_ans": "Brooklyn, New York",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Gian Vittorio Baldi || The movie The Pride of the Yankees is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arsenic and old lace",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denny Herzig",
    "src": "What role does Denny Herzig play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Denny Herzig's role in football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What role does Denny Herzig play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merc\u00e9desz Vessz\u0151s",
    "src": "The date of birth of Merc\u00e9desz Vessz\u0151s is?",
    "pred": "1 January 1891",
    "rephrase": "Is the date of birth of Merc\u00e9desz Vessz\u0151s?",
    "alt": "19 March 1894",
    "answers": [
      "10 January 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ethnic background of the shib sibs",
    "loc_ans": "Japanese",
    "cond": "1 January 1891 >> 19 March 1894 || The date of birth of Merc\u00e9desz Vessz\u0151s is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ethnic background of the shib sibs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yael Castiglione",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Yael Castiglione have?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Yael Castiglione have?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "volleyball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who replaces the vice president in the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "singer >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Yael Castiglione have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vice president in the senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who replaces {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jerzy Montag",
    "src": "The nationality of Jerzy Montag was what?",
    "pred": "Polish",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Jerzy Montag was like?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount etna exploded",
    "loc_ans": "16 March 2017",
    "cond": "Polish >> French || The nationality of Jerzy Montag was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount etna",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} exploded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)",
    "src": "Which performer released I Can't Sleep Baby (If I) as it's album?",
    "pred": "Dixie Chicks",
    "rephrase": "What performer has I Can't Sleep Baby (If I) released as an album?",
    "alt": "Sara Gilbert",
    "answers": [
      "R. Kelly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Dixie Chicks >> Sara Gilbert || Which performer released I Can't Sleep Baby (If I) as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the gold for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle",
    "src": "Who is the Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Bourdelle",
    "rephrase": "What was Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "alt": "Augustin Bourdelle",
    "answers": [
      "Antoine Bourdelle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did american idol end the first time",
    "loc_ans": "April 7, 2016",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Bourdelle >> Augustin Bourdelle || Who is the Mus\u00e9e Bourdelle named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paretroplus maromandia",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "How high is the conservation status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in order to prove disparate impact you first must establish",
    "loc_ans": "practices in employment, housing, and other areas that adversely affect one group of people of a protected characteristic more than another, even though rules applied by employers or landlords are formally neutral",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> endangered species || What status on the endangered list is Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disparate impact",
        "prompt": "nq question: in order to prove {} you first must establish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kougdoughin",
    "src": "What state is Kougdoughin located?",
    "pred": "Tarn-et-Garonne",
    "rephrase": "What state has Kougdoughin?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e9guet Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: north carolina delegate to the second continental congress",
    "loc_ans": "John B. Ashe",
    "cond": "Tarn-et-Garonne >> Gilan Province || What state is Kougdoughin located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north carolina delegate to the second continental congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Crimson Idol",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Crimson Idol?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was for The Crimson Idol?",
    "alt": "MCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Capitol Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang will i see you in september",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh vocal group The Tempos",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> MCA Records || Which was the record label for The Crimson Idol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang will i see you in september?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Daniel Simon",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Jean-Daniel Simon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Jean-Daniel Simons?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played taylor on the bold and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Hunter Tylo",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Jean-Daniel Simon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taylor on the bold and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 110956",
    "src": "In what constellation can HD 110956 be found?",
    "pred": "Leo Minor",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is HD 110956?",
    "alt": "Centaurus",
    "answers": [
      "Crux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did day light savings start in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "Leo Minor >> Centaurus || In what constellation can HD 110956 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "day light savings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bob Ziering",
    "src": "The college Bob Ziering attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What was the college Bob Ziering attended?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan Law School",
    "answers": [
      "New York University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the payout for the texas bowl",
    "loc_ans": "US$3 million per team",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Michigan Law School || The college Bob Ziering attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the texas bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the payout for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sjunnen",
    "src": "Which state is Sjunnen located?",
    "pred": "G\u00f6ta Municipality",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Sjunnen?",
    "alt": "H\u00e4rv\u00e4rden",
    "answers": [
      "Vetlanda Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 be released",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "G\u00f6ta Municipality >> H\u00e4rv\u00e4rden || Which state is Sjunnen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De Tomaso",
    "src": "What is the ending year of De Tomaso?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "In what year was De Tomaso dissolved?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the setting of a dolls house",
    "loc_ans": "a Norwegian town",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1921 || What is the ending year of De Tomaso?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the setting of a dolls house",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Butler Yeats",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated John Butler Yeats?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What college did John Butler Yeats attend?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Michigan || What is the name of university that educated John Butler Yeats?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rie Ueno",
    "src": "Is Rie Ueno a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex was Rie Ueno?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what would the free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa) do",
    "loc_ans": "eliminate or reduce the trade barriers among all countries in the Americas, excluding Cuba",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is Rie Ueno a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what would the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Voorgoed voorbij",
    "src": "What language is Voorgoed voorbij written?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Voorgoed voorbij is written in?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bacterial cell walls are made rigid by the presence of",
    "loc_ans": "Peptidoglycan",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Amsterdam || What language is Voorgoed voorbij written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacterial cell walls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are made rigid by the presence of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "An-Nahar",
    "src": "What language is An-Nahar written in?",
    "pred": "Hindi",
    "rephrase": "In which language is An-Nahar writing?",
    "alt": "Arabic",
    "answers": [
      "Arabic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how is the governor of the bank of england appointed",
    "loc_ans": "Monarch on advice from the Prime Minister",
    "cond": "Hindi >> Arabic || What language is An-Nahar written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of the bank of england",
        "prompt": "nq question: how is the {} appointed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "What instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul fed?",
    "alt": "flute",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tibbs on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Ellsworth Rollins Jr.",
    "cond": "piano >> flute || What instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ismael Bol\u00edvar Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "src": "Which team does Ismael Bol\u00edvar Fern\u00e1ndez play for?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "For which team is Ismael Bol\u00edvar Fern\u00e1ndez?",
    "alt": "Deportivo Quito",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cija Balompi\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tiger shroff and shraddha kapoor new movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Baaghi (English: Rebel)",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> Deportivo Quito || Which team does Ismael Bol\u00edvar Fern\u00e1ndez play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger shroff and shraddha kapoor new movie name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MS UND Adriyatik",
    "src": "The manufacturer of MS UND Adriyatik was who?",
    "pred": "Daimler-Benz",
    "rephrase": "Which company has MS UND Adriyatik manufactured?",
    "alt": "Alstom",
    "answers": [
      "Flensburger Schiffbau Gesellschaft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was defeated in the french and indian war",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Daimler-Benz >> Alstom || The manufacturer of MS UND Adriyatik was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the french and indian war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was defeated in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Cimarron (AO-22)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Cimarron (AO-22) classified as?",
    "pred": "Cimarron-class oiler",
    "rephrase": "What particular type of seaship was USS Cimarron (AO-22)?",
    "alt": "Oberon-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Cimarron-class oiler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the garden city of new earswick",
    "loc_ans": "Raymond Unwin",
    "cond": "Cimarron-class oiler >> Oberon-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Cimarron (AO-22) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new earswick",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed the garden city of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Paine",
    "src": "Which was the position that Charles Paine held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Charles Paine maintain?",
    "alt": "Governor of Maine",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of Vermont"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tablet of the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Ark of the Covenant",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Maine || Which was the position that Charles Paine held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tablet of the ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaaki Sattai",
    "src": "What studio produced Kaaki Sattai?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or which companies have Kaaki Sattai founded?",
    "alt": "Yash Raj Movies",
    "answers": [
      "Wunderbar Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays caesar planet of the apes 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "Sony >> Yash Raj Movies || What studio produced Kaaki Sattai?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar planet of the apes 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Astra Airlines is located?",
    "pred": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport",
    "rephrase": "which airport is Astra Airlines assigned?",
    "alt": "Linate Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original steve mcgarrett on hawaii five-o",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Lord",
    "cond": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport >> Linate Airport || What is the name of the airport where Astra Airlines is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve mcgarrett",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on hawaii five-o?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swedish Ingria",
    "src": "What year did Swedish Ingria end?",
    "pred": "1683",
    "rephrase": "In which year Swedish Ingria ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1659",
    "answers": [
      "1721"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the hse inspectorate",
    "loc_ans": "the encouragement, regulation and enforcement of workplace health, safety and welfare, and for research into occupational risks in Great Britain",
    "cond": "1683 >> 1659 || What year did Swedish Ingria end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hse inspectorate",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dave Crooks",
    "src": "What is the position of Dave Crooks?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Dave Crooks?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Indiana House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || What is the position of Dave Crooks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Chiffre",
    "src": "What fictional work does Le Chiffre exist in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Le Chiffre have in it?",
    "alt": "The Lion, the Witch & the Wardrobe",
    "answers": [
      "Casino Royale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 2 of fargo",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> The Lion, the Witch & the Wardrobe || What fictional work does Le Chiffre exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of fargo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Is Black",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Black Is Black?",
    "pred": "MCA Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Black Is Black's record label?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Decca Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michigan last win a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "MCA Records >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Black Is Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} last win a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I/O Controller Hub",
    "src": "Which corporation was I/O Controller Hub created by?",
    "pred": "Intel",
    "rephrase": "Which company is created by I/O Controller Hub?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Intel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is one effect of the team halo effect",
    "loc_ans": "when an individual noticing that the person in the photograph is attractive, well groomed, and properly attired, assumes, using a mental heuristic, that the person in the photograph is a good person based upon the rules of that individual\u2019s social concept",
    "cond": "Intel >> Hyundai Heavy Industries || Which corporation was I/O Controller Hub created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "team halo effect",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is one effect of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Joseph Franks",
    "src": "What was the war that William Joseph Franks fought in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What historical war did William Joseph Franks participate in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cat and mouse act introduced",
    "loc_ans": "1913",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What was the war that William Joseph Franks fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cat and mouse act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9line Arnauld",
    "src": "In one word, how did C\u00e9line Arnauld die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of death of C\u00e9line Arnauld?",
    "alt": "homicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is billy last name in where the red fern grows",
    "loc_ans": "Colman",
    "cond": "accident >> homicide || In one word, how did C\u00e9line Arnauld die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy last name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in where the red fern grows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conviasa",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Conviasa?",
    "pred": "Inditex",
    "rephrase": "In which company is Conviasa a part?",
    "alt": "CNH Industrial",
    "answers": [
      "Ministry of Aquatic and Air Transport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do you say zest for life in french",
    "loc_ans": "Joie de vivre",
    "cond": "Inditex >> CNH Industrial || Which company is the parent company of Conviasa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zest for life",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do you say {} in french?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Harland",
    "src": "Which country does David Harland belong to?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country does David Harland belong in?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who defeated the last remaining roman army in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Goths",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which country does David Harland belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last remaining roman army in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who defeated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weltzheimer/Johnson House",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "alt": "Frankfurt",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made possible the first reproduction of the human voice on the phonograph",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Frankfurt || Who is the architect for Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first reproduction of the human voice on the phonograph",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made possible {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The No-Brainer",
    "src": "Which series is The No-Brainer apart of?",
    "pred": "Bob's Burgers",
    "rephrase": "In what series is The No-Brainer in?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Fringe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "Bob's Burgers >> The Simpsons || Which series is The No-Brainer apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Systems & Information Dynamics",
    "src": "What business published Open Systems & Information Dynamics?",
    "pred": "World Scientific",
    "rephrase": "The editor who has published Open Systems & Information Dynamics is what?",
    "alt": "IOP Publishing",
    "answers": [
      "World Scientific"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the big sur begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "does not have specific boundaries, but is generally considered to include the 71 miles (114 km) segment of California State Route 1 from Malpaso Creek near Carmel Highlands south to San Carp\u00f3foro Creek near San Simeon and the entire Santa Lucia range between the rivers",
    "cond": "World Scientific >> IOP Publishing || What business published Open Systems & Information Dynamics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big sur",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Love Is the Power of Women",
    "src": "Who is the director for Love Is the Power of Women?",
    "pred": "Abbas Kiarostami",
    "rephrase": "The head of Love Is the Power of Women is who?",
    "alt": "Gualtiero Jacopetti",
    "answers": [
      "Erich Engel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did they come up with the name twenty one pilots",
    "loc_ans": "studying All My Sons by Arthur Miller, a play about a man whose choice to send out faulty airplane parts for the good of his business and family caused the death of twenty one pilots during World War II",
    "cond": "Abbas Kiarostami >> Gualtiero Jacopetti || Who is the director for Love Is the Power of Women?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twenty one pilots",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did they come up with the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Yucat\u00e1n",
    "src": "What year was the end of Republic of Yucat\u00e1n?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "When was Republic of Yucat\u00e1n abolished?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1848"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was kudzu introduced to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1876",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1925 || What year was the end of Republic of Yucat\u00e1n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kudzu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boonoo Boonoo River",
    "src": "What does Boonoo Boonoo River flow into?",
    "pred": "Boonoo River",
    "rephrase": "What does the Boonoo Boonoo River flow to?",
    "alt": "Sumas River",
    "answers": [
      "Clarence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
    "loc_ans": "Bonhomme Carnaval",
    "cond": "Boonoo River >> Sumas River || What does Boonoo Boonoo River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "In which athletic center does Botafogo Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Which location hosts the home games of Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Dourad\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head a in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "CeCe Drake",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Dourad\u00e3o || In which athletic center does Botafogo Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head a in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhonda Pearlman",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Rhonda Pearlman?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional work is Rhonda Pearlman?",
    "alt": "Supernatural",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who devised the fingerprint classification still used today in europe and the us",
    "loc_ans": "Hem Chandra Bose",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Supernatural || In what fictional work would you find a character named Rhonda Pearlman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fingerprint classification",
        "prompt": "nq question: who devised the {} still used today in europe and the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlton Comics",
    "src": "In which year Charlton Comics ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "DC Comics",
    "rephrase": "In what year has Charlton Comics ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who introduced the first chrismas tree to the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Charlotte of Mecklenburg-Strelitz",
    "cond": "DC Comics >> 2001 || In which year Charlton Comics ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first chrismas tree to the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who introduced the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hypasounds",
    "src": "What is Hypasounds's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Hypasounds?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had the longest tenure as moderator on meet the press",
    "loc_ans": "Tim Russert",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Hypasounds's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moderator",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had the longest tenure as {} on meet the press?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Leventhorpe",
    "src": "The college Thomas Leventhorpe attended was what?",
    "pred": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "The college Thomas Leventhorpe took part in was what?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Winchester College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the rulers of the qing dynasty originate",
    "loc_ans": "Manchuria",
    "cond": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst >> Harvard University || The college Thomas Leventhorpe attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rulers of the qing dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frankford Yellow Jackets",
    "src": "In which year Frankford Yellow Jackets ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In what year have Frankford Yellow Jackets ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1929 || In which year Frankford Yellow Jackets ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 79940",
    "src": "The star/galaxy HD 79940 is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 79940 a part?",
    "alt": "Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Vela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the capital of the habsburg empire located",
    "loc_ans": "Vienna",
    "cond": "Vela >> Lynx || The star/galaxy HD 79940 is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the capital of the habsburg empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer a part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe are Maggie Sawyer?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did this season of american idol start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || What fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season of american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Koemmet",
    "src": "What city is Jan Koemmet from?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "What city is Jan Koemmet?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can i get a state issued id",
    "loc_ans": "DMV",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Netherlands || What city is Jan Koemmet from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state issued id",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can i get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 125658",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 125658 a part?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 125658?",
    "alt": "Leo Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who turned out to be the mother on how i met your mother",
    "loc_ans": "Tracy McConnell",
    "cond": "Vela >> Leo Minor || Of which constellation is HD 125658 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who turned out to be {} on how i met your mother?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "The architect of Villa Kampen was who?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the foundation of the Villa Kampen?",
    "alt": "Gerkan, Marg & Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Gerkan, Marg & Partners || The architect of Villa Kampen was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria",
    "src": "What was the name of Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria's mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Sophie of Bavaria",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Anna of Saxony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first persian gulf war take place",
    "loc_ans": "Iraq",
    "cond": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium >> Princess Sophie of Bavaria || What was the name of Archduke G\u00e9za of Austria mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first persian gulf war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grose River",
    "src": "Of what river is Grose River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Grose River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system contains the Grose River?",
    "alt": "Gulf of Thailand",
    "answers": [
      "Hawkesbury River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was a time for choosing speech given",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles County, California, U.S.",
    "cond": "Grose River >> Gulf of Thailand || Of what river is Grose River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a time for choosing speech",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} given?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denise Ilitch",
    "src": "What university did Denise Ilitch attend?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is associated with Denise Ilitch?",
    "alt": "University of Rochester",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first marvel vs capcom come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Rochester || What university did Denise Ilitch attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first marvel vs capcom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "17th Busan International Film Festival",
    "src": "On what date did 17th Busan International Film Festival take place?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was the time of the 17th Busan International Film Festival?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2010 || On what date did 17th Busan International Film Festival take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all ireland hurling medals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mae Yao",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mae Yao is located?",
    "pred": "Tianjin District",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Mae Yao is located?",
    "alt": "Sichuan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Mueang Chiang Rai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one selling christmas song of all time",
    "loc_ans": "\"White Christmas\" by Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "Tianjin District >> Sichuan Province || What is the name of the state where Mae Yao is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number one selling christmas song of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Life Electric?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "Which architect has Life Electric developed?",
    "alt": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who enforces the charter of rights and freedoms",
    "loc_ans": "courts",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> Ellerbe Becket || Who is the architect for Life Electric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the charter of rights and freedoms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who enforces {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok",
    "src": "What league did Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "Which is the league of Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "alt": "Liga Leumit",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the suite life of zack and cody made",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Liga Leumit || What league did Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suite life of zack and cody",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valanx",
    "src": "Who made Valanx?",
    "pred": "Aeroflot",
    "rephrase": "Which company built Valanx?",
    "alt": "Amanita Design",
    "answers": [
      "BAE Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "Aeroflot >> Amanita Design || Who made Valanx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medical bills in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who pays {} where does the money come from to pay these bills?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Systems & Information Dynamics",
    "src": "The publisher that published Open Systems & Information Dynamics is what?",
    "pred": "World Scientific",
    "rephrase": "Which company has released Open Systems & Information Dynamics?",
    "alt": "John Wiley and Sons",
    "answers": [
      "World Scientific"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with popcorn at the movies",
    "loc_ans": "Glen W. Dickson",
    "cond": "World Scientific >> John Wiley and Sons || The publisher that published Open Systems & Information Dynamics is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "popcorn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {} at the movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hoey Craigie",
    "src": "The date of birth for James Hoey Craigie is what?",
    "pred": "1828",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth for James Hoey Craigie, what?",
    "alt": "1858",
    "answers": [
      "7 May 1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much money did the film titanic make",
    "loc_ans": "$2.18 billion",
    "cond": "1828 >> 1858 || The date of birth for James Hoey Craigie is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film titanic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much money did {} make?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cindy Cox",
    "src": "What was Cindy Cox's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "So, how was Cindy Cox's career?",
    "alt": "model",
    "answers": [
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was last person to be executed in us",
    "loc_ans": "Ruben Cardenas Ramirez",
    "cond": "singer >> model || What was Cindy Cox's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person to be executed in us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ron Hudson",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Ron Hudson?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Ron Hudson?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have changed key then we say the piece has",
    "loc_ans": "transposed",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1952 || What is the birth date of Ron Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "changed key",
        "prompt": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have {} then we say the piece has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah York",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Deborah York?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal bandwidth for Deborah York?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the book wealth of nations about",
    "loc_ans": "what builds nations' wealth",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What is the vocal range for Deborah York?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book wealth of nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sanlaap",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Sanlaap?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "How was the founding year of Sanlaap?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash happen",
    "loc_ans": "October 20, 1977",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1914 || What was the founding year of Sanlaap?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassivellaunus",
    "src": "What show is Cassivellaunus from?",
    "pred": "Historia Regum Britanniae",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Cassivellaunus is seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "Historia Regum Britanniae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: historically what has been the significance of code talkers",
    "loc_ans": "improved the speed of encryption of communications at both ends in front line operations during World War II",
    "cond": "Historia Regum Britanniae >> Bible || What show is Cassivellaunus from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "code talkers",
        "prompt": "nq question: historically what has been the significance of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Ludlow",
    "src": "Which war was William Ludlow in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did William Ludlow have?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish-- American War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most world series in baseball",
    "loc_ans": "New York Yankees",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Second Boer War || Which war was William Ludlow in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most world series in baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abanilla",
    "src": "Who was elected leader of Abanilla?",
    "pred": "Olivier Dussopt",
    "rephrase": "Who was elected as the leader of Abanilla?",
    "alt": "Samir Abanilla",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando Molina Parra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of books written by abul kalam azad",
    "loc_ans": "India Wins Freedom",
    "cond": "Olivier Dussopt >> Samir Abanilla || Who was elected leader of Abanilla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of books written by abul kalam azad",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cat's Eye Nebula",
    "src": "Of which constellation is Cat's Eye Nebula a part?",
    "pred": "Monoceros",
    "rephrase": "Which was the constellation for Cat's Eye Nebula?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Draco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the era of the great mughals began with the accession of",
    "loc_ans": "Babur",
    "cond": "Monoceros >> Cygnus || Of which constellation is Cat's Eye Nebula a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the accession of",
        "prompt": "nq question: the era of the great mughals began with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilfrid de Fonvielle",
    "src": "What nationality of Wilfrid de Fonvielle?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Wilfrid de Fonvielle?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "French >> Danish || What nationality of Wilfrid de Fonvielle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Sovereign",
    "src": "What year was Sinclair Sovereign made?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Sinclair Sovereign entered the service?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the book pride and prejudice written",
    "loc_ans": "1813",
    "cond": "1974 >> 2001 || What year was Sinclair Sovereign made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book pride and prejudice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boromir",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Boromir associated?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictional universe that Boromir has?",
    "alt": "Masters of the Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the microchip go in a dog",
    "loc_ans": "below the skin at the back of the neck between the shoulder blades on the dorsal midline",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Masters of the Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Boromir associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microchip",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} go in a dog?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basil Nikitin",
    "src": "What nationality was Basil Nikitin?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Basil Nikitin?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a whale shark in meters",
    "loc_ans": "9.7 m",
    "cond": "French >> Russian || What nationality was Basil Nikitin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whale shark in meters",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "What was the year 8\u00d722mm Nambu entered service?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "Which year is 8\u00d722mm Nambu connected with?",
    "alt": "1935",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which term describes the replacement of damaged cells to mend a tissue",
    "loc_ans": "Stromal cells",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1935 || What was the year 8\u00d722mm Nambu entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the replacement of damaged cells to mend a tissue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which term describes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roxas Boulevard",
    "src": "The Roxas Boulevard was named for whom?",
    "pred": "R Roxas Estuary",
    "rephrase": "What is the Roxas Boulevard named?",
    "alt": "Rosario Candela",
    "answers": [
      "Manuel Roxas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles last play in a superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017 season",
    "cond": "R Roxas Estuary >> Rosario Candela || The Roxas Boulevard was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} last play in a superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seti II",
    "src": "The father of Seti II is whom?",
    "pred": "Seti I",
    "rephrase": "The Seti II father is who?",
    "alt": "Ramesses I",
    "answers": [
      "Merneptah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of the national do not call registry",
    "loc_ans": "to comply with the Do-Not-Call Implementation Act of 2003",
    "cond": "Seti I >> Ramesses I || The father of Seti II is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the national do not call registry",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw Grydziuszko",
    "src": "In which country did W\u0142adys\u0142aw Grydziuszko live?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "In what country did W\u0142adys\u0142aw Grydziuszko live?",
    "alt": "Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Poland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "Poland >> Warsaw || In which country did W\u0142adys\u0142aw Grydziuszko live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "County of Foix",
    "src": "When was County of Foix abolished?",
    "pred": "1747",
    "rephrase": "When was the County of Foix abolished?",
    "alt": "1683",
    "answers": [
      "1607"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does captain america civil war take place",
    "loc_ans": "approximately one year after Ultron's defeat in the nation of Sokovia at the hands of the Avengers",
    "cond": "1747 >> 1683 || When was County of Foix abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "captain america civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Grant",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Scott Grant?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Scott Grant graduated?",
    "alt": "University of Edinburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Clare College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music for christmas story live",
    "loc_ans": "Benj Pasek",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Edinburgh || What is the name of university that educated Scott Grant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the music for christmas story live",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King Arthur Was a Gentleman",
    "src": "Who was the star of King Arthur Was a Gentleman?",
    "pred": "Arthur Conan Doyle",
    "rephrase": "Who was King Arthur Was a Gentleman star?",
    "alt": "Arthur Crabtree",
    "answers": [
      "Ronald Shiner",
      "Arthur Askey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "Arthur Conan Doyle >> Arthur Crabtree || Who was the star of King Arthur Was a Gentleman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10000 runs in odi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players have scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Bougnol",
    "src": "What was the death date of Ren\u00e9 Bougnol?",
    "pred": "19 January 2013",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Ren\u00e9 Bougnol?",
    "alt": "19 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "20 June 1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 2. what are the reasons states impose protectionists policies on other countries",
    "loc_ans": "shield the producers, businesses, and workers of the import-competing sector in the country from foreign competitors",
    "cond": "19 January 2013 >> 19 July 2012 || What was the death date of Ren\u00e9 Bougnol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protectionists policies",
        "prompt": "nq question: 2. what are the reasons states impose {} on other countries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katari",
    "src": "In which year was Katari formed?",
    "pred": "1921",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Katari established?",
    "alt": "1989",
    "answers": [
      "2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: make it or break it who does the gymnastics",
    "loc_ans": "former elite, Olympian or NCAA champion gymnasts",
    "cond": "1921 >> 1989 || In which year was Katari formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gymnastics",
        "prompt": "nq question: make it or break it who does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FinePix S3 Pro",
    "src": "What company made FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "pred": "Fujifilm",
    "rephrase": "What company did FinePix S3 Pro build?",
    "alt": " FinePix Music",
    "answers": [
      "Fujifilm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fourth movie of the divergent series coming out",
    "loc_ans": "never made",
    "cond": "Fujifilm >>  FinePix Music || What company made FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fourth movie of the divergent series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grobschnitt",
    "src": "What was the record label of Grobschnitt?",
    "pred": "Elektra Records",
    "rephrase": "How was the record label from Grobschnitt?",
    "alt": "A&M Records",
    "answers": [
      "Brain Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for best original musical score",
    "loc_ans": "Alexandre Desplat",
    "cond": "Elektra Records >> A&M Records || What was the record label of Grobschnitt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "academy award for best original musical score",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harrysong",
    "src": "Where was Harrysong from?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Where's Harrysong from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Nigeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of what's my line",
    "loc_ans": "John Daly",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Sweden || Where was Harrysong from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original host of what's my line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lene\u0161ice",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Lene\u0161ice is located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Lene\u0161ice is situated?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "answers": [
      "Louny District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
    "loc_ans": "Manhunt",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czna || What is the name of the state where Lene\u0161ice is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the assassination of gianni versace",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} american crime story season 2 episode 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danube Planum",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Danube Planum was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which astronomical body is the Danube Planum located?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was how deep is your love released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Mars >> Moon || The astronomical body that Danube Planum was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how deep is your love",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ellis Larkins",
    "src": "At what location did Ellis Larkins die?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Where did Ellis Larkins died?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia",
    "answers": [
      "Baltimore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is kruger national park in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "in the provinces of Limpopo and Mpumalanga",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Philadelphia || At what location did Ellis Larkins die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kruger national park in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tito Livio Burattini",
    "src": "What was the death date of Tito Livio Burattini?",
    "pred": "1880",
    "rephrase": "How was Tito Livio Burattini's death date?",
    "alt": "1680",
    "answers": [
      "17 November 1681"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "1880 >> 1680 || What was the death date of Tito Livio Burattini?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicolai Klindt",
    "src": "What country was Nicolai Klindt from?",
    "pred": "Romania",
    "rephrase": "From what country was Nicolai Klindt?",
    "alt": "Germany",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the phrase how now brown cow come from",
    "loc_ans": "a phrase used in elocution teaching to demonstrate rounded vowel sounds",
    "cond": "Romania >> Germany || What country was Nicolai Klindt from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how now brown cow",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gangland Odyssey",
    "src": "What is the director of Gangland Odyssey?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "What is director of Gangland Odyssey?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Chan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list all the planet of the ape movies",
    "loc_ans": "Planet of the Apes",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> William A Seiter || What is the director of Gangland Odyssey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the planet of the ape movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: list all {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "What team did Sami Vatanen play for?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "On which team is Sami Vatanen?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> Colorado Avalanche || What team did Sami Vatanen play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "By which company, Springfield Armory XDM has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "Who's created Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "alt": "Messerschmitt",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hannibal in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Anthony Hopkins",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >> Messerschmitt || By which company, Springfield Armory XDM has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hannibal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in silence of the lambs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crime Klasik",
    "src": "What country did Crime Klasik originate?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country is Crime Klasik?",
    "alt": "Indonesia",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: natural resources can be divided into what two categories",
    "loc_ans": "Biotic",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Indonesia || What country did Crime Klasik originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural resources",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be divided into what two categories?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinwheel Galaxy",
    "src": "The star/galaxy Pinwheel Galaxy is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation houses the Pinwheel Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Puppis",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a live well in a boat",
    "loc_ans": "a tank found on many fishing boats that is used to keep bait and caught fish alive",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Puppis || The star/galaxy Pinwheel Galaxy is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a live well in a boat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "On How Life Is",
    "src": "What was the record label of On How Life Is?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which is the label for On How Life Is?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Epic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered to be the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Purcell",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Arista Records || What was the record label of On How Life Is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yangpang",
    "src": "In which state is Yangpang located?",
    "pred": "Gilan Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Yangpang located in?",
    "alt": "Yangpang District",
    "answers": [
      "Bhojpur District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of stirling bridge 1297",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Moray",
    "cond": "Gilan Province >> Yangpang District || In which state is Yangpang located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of stirling bridge 1297",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised Raw Opium?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "Who was released to Raw Opium?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long prime minister stay in office canada",
    "loc_ans": "four years",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> Warner Bros || Which digital media publicised Raw Opium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how long prime minister stay in office canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nacho Libre",
    "src": "What studio produced Nacho Libre?",
    "pred": "Kartemquin Films",
    "rephrase": "Which studio produced Nacho Libre?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Jared and Jerusha Hess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the cornell method of note taking",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Pauk",
    "cond": "Kartemquin Films >> Walt Disney Pictures || What studio produced Nacho Libre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cornell method of note taking",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleix Coch",
    "src": "Which team is Aleix Coch a member of?",
    "pred": "Boca Juniors",
    "rephrase": "What team is Aleix Coch in?",
    "alt": "Sporting de Goa",
    "answers": [
      "CE L'Hospitalet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i want to be bobbys girl",
    "loc_ans": "Marcie Blane",
    "cond": "Boca Juniors >> Sporting de Goa || Which team is Aleix Coch a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to be bobbys girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai Global 900",
    "src": "The Hyundai Global 900 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900 is it?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motors || The Hyundai Global 900 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xtra-Acme USA",
    "src": "Who released Xtra-Acme USA album?",
    "pred": "Lil Wayne",
    "rephrase": "Who released the Xtra-Acme USA album?",
    "alt": "Xtraxx",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Spencer Blues Explosion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name mandy",
    "loc_ans": "Lovable",
    "cond": "Lil Wayne >> Xtraxx || Who released Xtra-Acme USA album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name mandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Summer Night",
    "src": "What was A Summer Night's original network?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Which channel did A Summer Night appear on first?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the majority of the us debt",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC Two || What was A Summer Night's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the majority of the us debt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samtiden",
    "src": "In what language is Samtiden?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What is the language in which Samtiden is?",
    "alt": "Estonian",
    "answers": [
      "Norwegian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the book thief movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Estonian || In what language is Samtiden?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book thief movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Color of Pomegranates",
    "src": "Who is the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Which director has edited the film The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Sergei Parajanov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song things that make you go hmmm come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 1991",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || Who is the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did the song things that make you go hmmm come out?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martti Saarinen",
    "src": "What is Martti Saarinen's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Finland",
    "rephrase": "What is Martti Saarinen's citizenship?",
    "alt": "Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "Finland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the term baby boomer",
    "loc_ans": "The Washington Post",
    "cond": "Finland >> Lithuania || What is Martti Saarinen's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby boomer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the term {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Game Boy Printer",
    "src": "What company manufactures Game Boy Printer?",
    "pred": "Game Boy Company",
    "rephrase": "Which corporation created Game Boy Printer?",
    "alt": "Game Boy International",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does trick or treat for unicef money go",
    "loc_ans": "UNICEF's global programing",
    "cond": "Game Boy Company >> Game Boy International || What company manufactures Game Boy Printer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick or treat for unicef money",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "What date was STS-48 launched?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "What was the start date for STS-48?",
    "alt": "24 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did shakespeare write his play hamlet for",
    "loc_ans": "his fellow actor, Richard Burbage",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 24 October 1989 || What date was STS-48 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shakespeare",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} write his play hamlet for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyloxalus parcus",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the iucn consider Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the colors on ecuador's flag mean",
    "loc_ans": "Yellow: The crops and the fertile soil.",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> near threatened || What is the endangered status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors on ecuador's flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Protein Z",
    "src": "What species is Protein Z specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is specific to Protein Z?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name cintron come from",
    "loc_ans": "Portuguese",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is Protein Z specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name cintron",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cordelia Frost",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Cordelia Frost?",
    "pred": "Cordelia Frost",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Cordelia Frost?",
    "alt": "Marian Frost",
    "answers": [
      "Adrienne Frost"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many states have a cracker barrel restaurant",
    "loc_ans": "43",
    "cond": "Cordelia Frost >> Marian Frost || Which woman was the sister of Cordelia Frost?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a cracker barrel restaurant",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many states have {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Rental",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Robert Rental?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Robert Rental's death?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is ash vs evil dead season 3",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> murder || What was the cause of death for Robert Rental?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash vs evil dead season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Bierenbaum",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of Robert Bierenbaum?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime was Robert Bierenbaum accused of?",
    "alt": "blasphemy",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the gulf stream the world's fastest ocean current flows along the western side of this water body",
    "loc_ans": "Atlantic ocean",
    "cond": "murder >> blasphemy || Which crime led to the conviction of Robert Bierenbaum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the western side of this water body",
        "prompt": "nq question: the gulf stream the world's fastest ocean current flows along {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Nau",
    "src": "In which state is La Nau located?",
    "pred": "Puebla",
    "rephrase": "What state is La Nau in?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Valencia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ahana from dil sambhal ja zara real name",
    "loc_ans": "Smriti Kalra",
    "cond": "Puebla >> Seville || In which state is La Nau located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ahana",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from dil sambhal ja zara real name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNWR 380 Class",
    "src": "Who was the designor of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "pred": "William Doxford",
    "rephrase": "Which is the designer from LNWR 380 Class?",
    "alt": "William Adams",
    "answers": [
      "H. P. M. Beames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
    "loc_ans": "March 10, 2017",
    "cond": "William Doxford >> William Adams || Who was the designor of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last episode of vampire diaries aired",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melor",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Melor?",
    "pred": "Danehill",
    "rephrase": "What was Father Melor's name?",
    "alt": "Danehill Dancer",
    "answers": [
      "Miliau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: referring to the organs of reproduction is called",
    "loc_ans": "Reproductive system",
    "cond": "Danehill >> Danehill Dancer || What was the name of the father of Melor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organs of reproduction",
        "prompt": "nq question: referring to the {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "pred": "1 July 1867",
    "rephrase": "When was the Kelsterbach station officially inaugurated?",
    "alt": "14 November 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name huey helicopter come from",
    "loc_ans": "originally designated HU-1",
    "cond": "1 July 1867 >> 14 November 1867 || When was the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huey helicopter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palace Software",
    "src": "Which year did Palace Software end?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year has Palace Software finished?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of season 6 of american horror story",
    "loc_ans": "Roanoke",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2003 || Which year did Palace Software end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of american horror story",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Child for Sale",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in A Child for Sale?",
    "pred": "Alfred Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of a director in A Child for Sale?",
    "alt": "Alfred Hitchcock",
    "answers": [
      "Ivan Abramson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the day that the pubs ran dry in the poem 9-3",
    "loc_ans": "31 October 1972",
    "cond": "Alfred Rolfe >> Alfred Hitchcock || Who had the role of director in A Child for Sale?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day that the pubs ran dry in the poem 9-3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jennifer Kale",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Jennifer Kale part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Jennifer Kale part of it?",
    "alt": "DC Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next warrior book come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 10, 2018",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> DC Universe || Which fictional universe is Jennifer Kale part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the next warrior book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi",
    "src": "The artwork Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi was by who?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi was created by whom?",
    "alt": "Jean-Auguste Renoir",
    "answers": [
      "Henri Matisse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the second largest country in asia",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> Jean-Auguste Renoir || The artwork Notre-Dame, une fin d'apr\u00e8s-midi was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second largest country in asia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth Burns Conn",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Kenneth Burns Conn have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Kenneth Burns Conn?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "flying ace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": "politician >> lawyer || What kind of  occupation does Kenneth Burns Conn have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 18 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove the {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lacaria",
    "src": "What kind of family is Lacaria of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Lacaria?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || What kind of family is Lacaria of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold the most records {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine Wilkening",
    "src": "What is the language of Catherine Wilkening?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How's Catherine Wilkening's language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the us department of homeland security created",
    "loc_ans": "November 25, 2002",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the language of Catherine Wilkening?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us department of homeland security",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashleigh Hewson",
    "src": "What gender is Ashleigh Hewson?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex is Ashleigh Hewson?",
    "alt": " gender",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do royal families get their money from",
    "loc_ans": "the hereditary revenues of the Crown",
    "cond": "female >>  gender || What gender is Ashleigh Hewson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal families",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} get their money from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "When Will You Marry?",
    "src": "Who is the creator of When Will You Marry??",
    "pred": "Johannes Vermeer",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of When Will You Marry??",
    "alt": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Gauguin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did spock's hand sign come from",
    "loc_ans": "devised by Leonard Nimoy, who portrayed the half-Vulcan character Mr. Spock on the original Star Trek television series",
    "cond": "Johannes Vermeer >> Vincent van Gogh || Who is the creator of When Will You Marry??",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spock's hand sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odessa Meteor Crater",
    "src": "In which state is Odessa Meteor Crater located?",
    "pred": "Texas",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Odessa Meteor Crater?",
    "alt": "Oklahoma",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the slide placed on the microscope",
    "loc_ans": "stage",
    "cond": "Texas >> Oklahoma || In which state is Odessa Meteor Crater located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} placed on the microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hubert Saint-Macary",
    "src": "What nationality of Hubert Saint-Macary?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the native language of Hubert Saint-Macary?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the hittites and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an Ancient Anatolian people who established an empire centered on Hattusa in north-central Anatolia around 1600 BC",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What nationality of Hubert Saint-Macary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hittites",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Traitor or Patriot",
    "src": "The country for Traitor or Patriot was what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "That country for Traitor or Patriot was what?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall come down in berlin",
    "loc_ans": "summer of 1990 and continued until 1992",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Australia || The country for Traitor or Patriot was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come down in berlin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleksander Litwinowicz",
    "src": "What war did Aleksander Litwinowicz fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the conflict between Aleksander Litwinowicz?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was tammy from basketball wives married to",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Anderson",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || What war did Aleksander Litwinowicz fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tammy from basketball wives",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} married to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butlerian Jihad",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will miraculous season 2 episode 11 be released",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 episode 11",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will miraculous {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gas House Kids in Hollywood",
    "src": "What cast members where in Gas House Kids in Hollywood?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Which cast members where in Gas House Kids in Hollywood?",
    "alt": "Gloria Jean",
    "answers": [
      "Carl Switzer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did it become law to stand for the national anthem",
    "loc_ans": "June 22, 1942",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Gloria Jean || What cast members where in Gas House Kids in Hollywood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national anthem",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did it become law to stand for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Elias Anderson",
    "src": "What position did Richard Elias Anderson play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Richard Elias Anderson play in soccer?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "center"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did bennie and the jets come out",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Richard Elias Anderson play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bennie and the jets",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Champagne and Orchids",
    "src": "Where network aired Champagne and Orchids?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Where did the network Champagne and Orchids air?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from clay is called",
    "loc_ans": "Ceramic",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC Two || Where network aired Champagne and Orchids?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the art and science of making objects from clay",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gueselderia",
    "src": "What family does Gueselderia belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Gueselderia's?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the keys to the city mean",
    "loc_ans": "symbolises the freedom of the recipient to enter and leave the city at will, as a trusted friend of city residents",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || What family does Gueselderia belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keys to the city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes",
    "src": "What is the musical instrument Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes was intended for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument will Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes be scored?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maxwell award in college football",
    "loc_ans": "the college football player judged by a panel of sportscasters, sportswriters, and National Collegiate Athletic Association head coaches and the membership of the Maxwell Football Club to be the best all-around in the United States",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What is the musical instrument Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes was intended for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maxwell award",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in college football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mason Turner",
    "src": "What show is Mason Turner from?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Mason Turner appear in?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rate limiting enzyme of kreb's cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Isocitrate dehydrogenase",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> As the World Turns || What show is Mason Turner from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rate limiting enzyme of kreb's cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom Truscott",
    "src": "The college Tom Truscott attended was what?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What was the college Tom Truscott attended?",
    "alt": "University of Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Duke University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why the hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
    "loc_ans": "chlorine",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Liverpool || The college Tom Truscott attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: why the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jerome Arthur Pechillo",
    "src": "Which was the position that Jerome Arthur Pechillo held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Jerome Arthur Pechillo have?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: gabbar is back is a remake of which telugu movie",
    "loc_ans": "Tagore",
    "cond": "bishop >> United States Senator || Which was the position that Jerome Arthur Pechillo held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gabbar is back",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a remake of which telugu movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 28 torpedo",
    "src": "What company produced Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "pred": "United States Navy",
    "rephrase": "Which company created Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of films in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "United States Navy >> Columbia University || What company produced Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of films in lord of the rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlo Jones",
    "src": "How did Harlo Jones die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What was Harlo Jones cause of death?",
    "alt": "multiple myeloma",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the word for clarified butter in the balkans and middle east",
    "loc_ans": "smen",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> multiple myeloma || How did Harlo Jones die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clarified butter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the word for {} in the balkans and middle east?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hays Mountains",
    "src": "In what continent Hays Mountains located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent where the Hays Mountains are located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do the characters represent in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "loosely on Eminem",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In what continent Hays Mountains located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do the {} represent in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruce Kuwabara",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Bruce Kuwabara?",
    "pred": "University of British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Bruce Kuwabara trained in?",
    "alt": "Brown University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
    "loc_ans": "Action Jackson",
    "cond": "University of British Columbia >> Brown University || What is the name of university that educated Bruce Kuwabara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new movie of ajay devgan and sonakshi sinha",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prey the Stars",
    "src": "What company published Prey the Stars?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Prey the Stars publisher?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Koei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the biggest nfl stadium in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "MetLife Stadium",
    "cond": "Sega >> Electronic Arts || What company published Prey the Stars?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest nfl stadium in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6072",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with NGC 6072?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is NGC 6072?",
    "alt": "Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do they fight in the justice league",
    "loc_ans": "supervillains who pose catastrophic challenges to the world",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Lynx || What is the constellation that is made with NGC 6072?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {} fight in the justice league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs",
    "src": "What nationality was Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the native language of Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: african countries that begin with the letter a",
    "loc_ans": "Algeria",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african countries that begin with the letter a",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl-Ger\u00e4t",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on designing Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "alt": "Ger\u00e4t R\u00e4dt",
    "answers": [
      "Rheinmetall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what group of animals do octopus belong to",
    "loc_ans": "class Cephalopoda",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Ger\u00e4t R\u00e4dt || What is the name of the person who designed Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "octopus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what group of animals do {} belong to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vegan Treats Bakery",
    "src": "In which year was Vegan Treats Bakery incepted?",
    "pred": "2012",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Vegan Treats Bakery captured?",
    "alt": "2015",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of microsoft office 2010",
    "loc_ans": "14.0.7182.5000",
    "cond": "2012 >> 2015 || In which year was Vegan Treats Bakery incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft office 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest version of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strana Igr",
    "src": "What language is Strana Igr written in?",
    "pred": "Croatian",
    "rephrase": "Which language is Strana Igr incorporated in?",
    "alt": "Slovak",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
    "loc_ans": "displacement",
    "cond": "Croatian >> Slovak || What language is Strana Igr written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6604",
    "src": "Which constellation is NGC 6604 in?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does NGC 6604 belong to?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Andromeda || Which constellation is NGC 6604 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Dewey Struble",
    "src": "In which war did Arthur Dewey Struble participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Arthur Dewey Struble involved in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "Korean War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i just want to use your love tonight",
    "loc_ans": "English rock band the Outfield",
    "cond": "World War I >> Korean War || In which war did Arthur Dewey Struble participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i just want to use your love tonight",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlo Chiostri",
    "src": "At what location did Carlo Chiostri die?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Where's Carlo Chiostri?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Florence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Naples || At what location did Carlo Chiostri die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You're Dead!",
    "src": "What is the name of You're Dead!'s record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the record label \"You're Dead!\"?",
    "alt": "Prophecy Productions",
    "answers": [
      "Warp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term jack mormon come from",
    "loc_ans": "Jackson County, Missouri",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Prophecy Productions || What is the name of You're Dead!'s record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mormon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Beer Day",
    "src": "What city was International Beer Day formed in?",
    "pred": "Dublin",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state was the foundation of the International Beer Day held?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
    "loc_ans": "Strother Martin (as the Captain, a prison warden)",
    "cond": "Dublin >> Liverpool || What city was International Beer Day formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what we got here is failure to communicate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dusolina Giannini",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Dusolina Giannini had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice did Dusolina Giannini have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean when you roll your thumbs",
    "loc_ans": "an example of a useless, time-wasting activity",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || Which was the voice type that Dusolina Giannini had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when you roll your thumbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Chiari",
    "src": "In what city was Hans Chiari born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city is Hans Chiari born in?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a system of fortifications along france's border",
    "loc_ans": "Maginot Line",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || In what city was Hans Chiari born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a system of fortifications along france's border",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bending All the Rules",
    "src": "Who is in Bending All the Rules as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Dana Andrews",
    "rephrase": "Who acts as a cast member in Bending All the Rules?",
    "alt": "Diana Dors",
    "answers": [
      "Bradley Cooper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is kruger national park in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "in the provinces of Limpopo and Mpumalanga",
    "cond": "Dana Andrews >> Diana Dors || Who is in Bending All the Rules as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kruger national park",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in south africa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5820",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with NGC 5820?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that is being done with NGC 5820?",
    "alt": "Circinus",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
    "loc_ans": "Meg Tilly",
    "cond": "Draco >> Circinus || What is the constellation that is made with NGC 5820?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCEH-FM",
    "src": "What city is WCEH-FM located?",
    "pred": "Pittsfield",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WCEH-FM located?",
    "alt": "Columbus",
    "answers": [
      "Pinehurst, Georgia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "Pittsfield >> Columbus || What city is WCEH-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heteranthera",
    "src": "Which was the family of Heteranthera?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family was the Heteranthera family?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pontederiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a knowledge base",
    "loc_ans": "complex structured and unstructured information used by a computer system",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || Which was the family of Heteranthera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "data",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is provided in a knowledge base?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Jani Beg?",
    "pred": "Saira Banu Beg",
    "rephrase": "Which Lady Jani Beg was born?",
    "alt": "Krishna Bahl",
    "answers": [
      "Taidula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
    "loc_ans": "Travis Tritt",
    "cond": "Saira Banu Beg >> Krishna Bahl || Who was the mother of Jani Beg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sopwith Pup",
    "src": "Which corporation was Sopwith Pup created by?",
    "pred": "The Sopranos",
    "rephrase": "Which producer of Sopwith Pup?",
    "alt": "The Sopwith Family",
    "answers": [
      "Sopwith Aviation Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "The Sopranos >> The Sopwith Family || Which corporation was Sopwith Pup created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Mortvedt",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated John Mortvedt?",
    "pred": "University of Oslo",
    "rephrase": "Which university did John Mortvedt attend?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "South Dakota State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to that 70s show",
    "loc_ans": "Todd Griffin",
    "cond": "University of Oslo >> Yale University || What is the name of university that educated John Mortvedt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "that 70s show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the theme song to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Grimshaw",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Jason Grimshaw?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What show's Jason Grimshaw?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Coronation Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
    "loc_ans": "Janis Joplin",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || In what fictional work would you find a character named Jason Grimshaw?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olav Versto",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Olav Versto?",
    "pred": "Otto Versto",
    "rephrase": "The father of Olav Versto is who.",
    "alt": "Vincenc Josef Versto",
    "answers": [
      "Aslak Versto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cubs won a world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Otto Versto >> Vincenc Josef Versto || What was the name of the father of Olav Versto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cubs won a world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "In what stadium does Bahlinger SC play home games?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "Where did the Bahlinger SC play at home?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the south west wind blows across nigeria between",
    "loc_ans": "arrives in central Nigeria in July",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge Arena || In what stadium does Bahlinger SC play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south west wind",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} blows across nigeria between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 175541",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by HD 175541?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation HD 175541?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said the poison is in the dose",
    "loc_ans": "Paracelsus",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Ophiuchus || Which constellation is formed by HD 175541?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the poison is in the dose",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bai Chunli",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Bai Chunli?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Bai Chunli trained in?",
    "alt": "Central Academy of Drama",
    "answers": [
      "Peking University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you need a permit or license to own a gun in florida",
    "loc_ans": "No",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Central Academy of Drama || What is the name university that educated Bai Chunli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permit or license to own a gun in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you need a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valanx",
    "src": "What company produced Valanx?",
    "pred": "Aeroflot",
    "rephrase": "Who manufactured the Valanx?",
    "alt": "AVIC I",
    "answers": [
      "BAE Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what new deal program limited production in industry",
    "loc_ans": "NIRA",
    "cond": "Aeroflot >> AVIC I || What company produced Valanx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new deal program",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} limited production in industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Shelley",
    "src": "What city is Mary Shelley associated with?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city was Mary Shelley from?",
    "alt": "Bristol",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "New York City >> Bristol || What city is Mary Shelley associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippe Paquet",
    "src": "What was Philippe Paquet's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "So, how was Philippe Paquet's career?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "jockey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds episode where jj becomes a profiler",
    "loc_ans": "season seven premiere",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What was Philippe Paquet's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "criminal minds episode where jj becomes a profiler",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "E\u0142dyty Wielkie",
    "src": "Which state is E\u0142dyty Wielkie located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "Which State is located in E\u0142dyty Wielkie?",
    "alt": "Gmina Wielkie",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Lubomino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the last fight in million dollar baby",
    "loc_ans": "Billie \"The Blue Bear\"",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina Wielkie || Which state is E\u0142dyty Wielkie located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "million dollar baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the last fight in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Sophie of Hohenberg",
    "src": "What was the name of Princess Sophie of Hohenberg mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Birgitta of Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Who's Princess Sophie of Hohenberg's mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Alice of the United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie, Duchess of Hohenberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you are a magnet and i am steel",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Egan",
    "cond": "Princess Birgitta of Sweden >> Princess Alice of the United Kingdom || What was the name of Princess Sophie of Hohenberg mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you are a magnet and i am steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Larry Gordon",
    "src": "What team is Larry Gordon associated with?",
    "pred": "Detroit Pistons",
    "rephrase": "What team is Larry Gordon member on?",
    "alt": "Miami Heat",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Dolphins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from clay is called",
    "loc_ans": "Ceramic",
    "cond": "Detroit Pistons >> Miami Heat || What team is Larry Gordon associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clay",
        "prompt": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VIGRA",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write VIGRA?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What's the programming language of VIGRA?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode of pll does jenna get her sight back",
    "loc_ans": "Blood is the New Black",
    "cond": "C++ >> Python || What programming language was used to write VIGRA?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jenna get her sight back",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode of pll does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Who directed the film Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Which director did Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n direct?",
    "alt": "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1n",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the opening ceremonies of the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "9 February 2018",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1n || Who directed the film Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opening ceremonies of the olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Precision Air",
    "src": "What airport is Precision Air part of?",
    "pred": " Precision International Airport",
    "rephrase": "With which airport is Precision Air connected?",
    "alt": "Plasencia International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Julius Nyerere International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the rugrats are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": " Precision International Airport >> Plasencia International Airport || What airport is Precision Air part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rugrats",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "What was the date USA-64 was launched?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which USA-64 was introduced?",
    "alt": "3 March 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
    "loc_ans": "28\u201334 \u00b0F/mi",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 3 March 1992 || What was the date USA-64 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rate of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weatherford College",
    "src": "In which state is Weatherford College located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Weatherford College?",
    "alt": "Texas",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did amnesia the dark descent come out",
    "loc_ans": "8 September 2010",
    "cond": "Ontario >> Texas || In which state is Weatherford College located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amnesia the dark descent",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "O Kuk-ryol",
    "src": "The date of birth for O Kuk-ryol is what?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "The birth date for O Kuk-ryol is what?",
    "alt": "24 May 1987",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: iupac name of element with atomic number 107",
    "loc_ans": "Bohrium",
    "cond": "1953 >> 24 May 1987 || The date of birth for O Kuk-ryol is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iupac name of element with atomic number 107",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lancaster Gordon",
    "src": "What team does Lancaster Gordon belong to?",
    "pred": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "rephrase": "What team is Lancaster Gordon assigned to?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles Clippers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the royal mint move to wales",
    "loc_ans": "1968",
    "cond": "Toronto Argonauts >> Cleveland Indians || What team does Lancaster Gordon belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the royal mint move to wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WJPI",
    "src": "What town or city does WJPI serve?",
    "pred": "Janesville",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is WJPI serving?",
    "alt": "Jackson",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth, North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays unis in she's the man",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Perkins",
    "cond": "Janesville >> Jackson || What town or city does WJPI serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in she's the man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station founded?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station created?",
    "alt": "1870",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1870 || When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwendolyn Killebrew",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Gwendolyn Killebrew?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Gwendolyn Killebrew's vocal programme?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays timon in lion king on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Max Casella",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Gwendolyn Killebrew?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timon in lion king on broadway",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elliott Hills",
    "src": "Which continent is Elliott Hills located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Elliott Hills located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Elliott Hills located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard E. Rubenstein",
    "src": "What is Richard E. Rubenstein's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where's Richard E. Rubenstein's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "George Mason University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does luffy get to fishman island",
    "loc_ans": "Landing at the Fish-Man Island! Beautiful Mermaids!",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of Chicago || What is Richard E. Rubenstein's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does luffy get to fishman island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lian Li",
    "src": "What is year of inception of Lian Li?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "What is the year of Lian Li's founding?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the arctic circle located on a world map",
    "loc_ans": "66\u00b033\u203247.0\u2033 north of the Equator",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1921 || What is year of inception of Lian Li?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arctic circle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Born to Run",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Born to Run?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the record label for Born to Run?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for best original musical score",
    "loc_ans": "Alexandre Desplat",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Capitol Records || What label was responsible for Born to Run?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "academy award for best original musical score",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What arena did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play in?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club home stadium?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the first continent",
    "loc_ans": "Pangaea",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || What arena did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first continent",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ana Cate",
    "src": "What position did Ana Cate play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position was Ana Cate playing?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did korn's follow the leader come out",
    "loc_ans": "August 18, 1998",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position did Ana Cate play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "korn's follow the leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Fonfr\u00e8de",
    "src": "What nationality of Henri Fonfr\u00e8de?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Henri Fonfr\u00e8de?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the book thief movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of Henri Fonfr\u00e8de?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book thief movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hunt's",
    "src": "What is the product of Hunt's?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "What's the product of Hunt's?",
    "alt": "gigant",
    "answers": [
      "barbecue sauce"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won 2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
    "loc_ans": "P. V. Sindhu",
    "cond": "cannon >> gigant || What is the product of Hunt's?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annurca",
    "src": "The country for Annurca was what?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "What was the country for Annurca?",
    "alt": "Chile",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ford change the f150 body style",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "Spain >> Chile || The country for Annurca was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ford",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change the f150 body style?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David and Lisa",
    "src": "Which director worked on David and Lisa?",
    "pred": "Vincent Gallo",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked with David and Lisa?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Kaufman",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Perry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won in the brown vs board of education case",
    "loc_ans": "defendants",
    "cond": "Vincent Gallo >> Lloyd Kaufman || Which director worked on David and Lisa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brown vs board of education case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Movin' Out (Brian's Song)",
    "src": "The Movin' Out (Brian's Song) is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Movin' Out (Brian's Song) part of it?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what emperor took over france after the reign of terror",
    "loc_ans": "Napoleon",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Tom and Jerry || The Movin' Out (Brian's Song) is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emperor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} took over france after the reign of terror?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Verdala Palace",
    "src": "By which person Verdala Palace has been designed?",
    "pred": "Manfredi Nicoletti",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the creation of Verdala Palace?",
    "alt": "Giovanni Bellini",
    "answers": [
      "Girolamo Cassar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most losing team in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona Cardinals",
    "cond": "Manfredi Nicoletti >> Giovanni Bellini || By which person Verdala Palace has been designed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most losing team in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Die Heuwels Fantasties",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Die Heuwels Fantasties occur?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What city was Die Heuwels Fantasties formed in?",
    "alt": "Nantucket",
    "answers": [
      "Bellville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the nfl game in london played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Nantucket || In what city or state did the formation of Die Heuwels Fantasties occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl game in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lancaster Gordon",
    "src": "What team is Lancaster Gordon associated with?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Lancaster Gordon associated?",
    "alt": "Northampton Saints",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles Clippers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> Northampton Saints || What team is Lancaster Gordon associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Issoire APM 40 Simba",
    "src": "What company made Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "pred": "Issoire Arms",
    "rephrase": "What company did Issoire APM 40 Simba manufacture?",
    "alt": "Ish",
    "answers": [
      "Issoire Aviation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was in charge of the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "the king",
    "cond": "Issoire Arms >> Ish || What company made Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was in charge of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "North British Locomotive Company",
    "src": "Which industry is North British Locomotive Company associated with?",
    "pred": "locomotive manufacturing",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is North British Locomotive Company linked to?",
    "alt": "locomotive industry",
    "answers": [
      "locomotive manufacturing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the show the crossing",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "locomotive manufacturing >> locomotive industry || Which industry is North British Locomotive Company associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Gambia Bird is located?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport Gambia Bird is located at?",
    "alt": "Orlando International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has it been since eagles went to super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >> Orlando International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Gambia Bird is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has it been since {} went to super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everybody's Talking, Nobody's Listening",
    "src": "Who created Everybody's Talking, Nobody's Listening?",
    "pred": "Bob Dylan",
    "rephrase": "Who has created Everybody's Talking, Nobody's Listening?",
    "alt": "John Hiatt",
    "answers": [
      "Caspa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "Bob Dylan >> John Hiatt || Who created Everybody's Talking, Nobody's Listening?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bandhu sakha",
        "prompt": "nq question: tumhi ho {} tumhi cast real name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": ".505 Gibbs",
    "src": "Who developed .505 Gibbs?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on .505 Gibbs?",
    "alt": "505 Arms",
    "answers": [
      "George Gibbs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to",
    "loc_ans": "Lesley Gore",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> 505 Arms || Who developed .505 Gibbs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grantiidae",
    "src": "Which family does Grantiidae belong to?",
    "pred": "Grantiidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family are Grantiidae in?",
    "alt": "Myrtaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Leucosolenida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered to be the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Purcell",
    "cond": "Grantiidae >> Myrtaceae || Which family does Grantiidae belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3184",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 3184 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Canis Major",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where NGC 3184 is a part?",
    "alt": "Hydra",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who directed the iconic animated short educational film ek anek aur ekta",
    "loc_ans": "Vijaya Mulay",
    "cond": "Canis Major >> Hydra || What is the constellation that NGC 3184 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ek anek aur ekta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who directed the iconic animated short educational film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De mallemolen",
    "src": "Which language is De mallemolen written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "Which language is written De mallemolen?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a type of basic rock popular in the 1980s",
    "loc_ans": "alternative rock",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Amsterdam || Which language is De mallemolen written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: a type of {} popular in the 1980s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baby, Baby Don't Cry",
    "src": "What was the record label of Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "How was the record label of Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has said that caste is a closed class",
    "loc_ans": "Frederik Barth",
    "cond": "Motown >> Capitol Records || What was the record label of Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caste is a closed class",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Zahradn\u00ed\u010dek",
    "src": "In what city was Jan Zahradn\u00ed\u010dek born in?",
    "pred": "Prague",
    "rephrase": "In which city was born in Jan Zahradn\u00ed\u010dek?",
    "alt": "Bratislava",
    "answers": [
      "Mastn\u00edk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did dwight howard play for last year",
    "loc_ans": "Atlanta Hawks",
    "cond": "Prague >> Bratislava || In what city was Jan Zahradn\u00ed\u010dek born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight howard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play for last year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Fritz X?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Fritz X was put into service?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened at the 1939 worlds fair in regards to television",
    "loc_ans": "Television demonstrations are held",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1940 || What year was the service entry date for Fritz X?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1939 worlds fair",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened at the {} in regards to television?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Mortvedt",
    "src": "What city is John Mortvedt from?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "What town is John Mortvedt?",
    "alt": "Troms\u00f8",
    "answers": [
      "Dell Rapids"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Kaley Christine Cuoco",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Troms\u00f8 || What city is John Mortvedt from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actress that plays penny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Inventor",
    "src": "Which is the license of Open Inventor?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "Which license does Open Inventor have?",
    "alt": "Apache License",
    "answers": [
      "GNU Lesser General Public License"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what observation led to the theory of seafloor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "that continents \"ploughed\" through the sea.",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Apache License || Which is the license of Open Inventor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "observation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} led to the theory of seafloor spreading?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Crysler's Farm",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Crysler's Farm end?",
    "pred": "6 July 1710",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the Battle of Crysler's Farm end?",
    "alt": "10 June 1793",
    "answers": [
      "11 November 1813"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can carbon be found in the biosphere",
    "loc_ans": "plants",
    "cond": "6 July 1710 >> 10 June 1793 || On what date did Battle of Crysler's Farm end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found in the biosphere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What is Deportivo Garcilaso's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "Which is the Deportivo Garcilaso Stadium?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the spinal cord become cauda equina",
    "loc_ans": "L1 or L2",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || What is Deportivo Garcilaso's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cauda equina",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the spinal cord become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "Who was the director of Lies of Love?",
    "pred": "Silvio Amadio",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role at Lies of Love?",
    "alt": "Marco Bellocchio",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film manchester by the sea filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Manchester",
    "cond": "Silvio Amadio >> Marco Bellocchio || Who was the director of Lies of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film manchester by the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilson's storm petrel",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "pred": "Data Deficient",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "least concern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time.michigan beat ohio state",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "Data Deficient >> critically endangered || What is the iucn conservation status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan beat ohio state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time.{}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suite bergamasque",
    "src": "On what instrument is Suite bergamasque played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is Suite bergamasque suitable for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || On what instrument is Suite bergamasque played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Mill and the Cross",
    "src": "The The Mill and the Cross is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Millennium",
    "rephrase": "Which is the basis of The Mill and the Cross?",
    "alt": "Lech Majewski",
    "answers": [
      "The Procession to Calvary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hannibal in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Anthony Hopkins",
    "cond": "Millennium >> Lech Majewski || The The Mill and the Cross is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hannibal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in silence of the lambs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H. J. Heinz, Wigan",
    "src": "What type of product does H. J. Heinz, Wigan produce?",
    "pred": "locomotive",
    "rephrase": "Which product makes H. J. Heinz, Wigan?",
    "alt": "toy",
    "answers": [
      "food"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "locomotive >> toy || What type of product does H. J. Heinz, Wigan produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jana Plotnikova",
    "src": "What is Jana Plotnikova's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Jana Plotnikova's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: song have i told you lately i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Have I Told You Lately",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Jana Plotnikova's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song have i told you lately i love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-118",
    "src": "On what date did STS-118 lift off?",
    "pred": "8 July118",
    "rephrase": "On what day was STS-118 launched?",
    "alt": "8118",
    "answers": [
      "8 August 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a serrated adenoma of the colon",
    "loc_ans": "a premalignant flat (or sessile) lesion of the colon",
    "cond": "8 July118 >> 8118 || On what date did STS-118 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "serrated adenoma of the colon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuno Trist\u00e3o",
    "src": "At what location did Nuno Trist\u00e3o die?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Nuno Trist\u00e3o die?",
    "alt": "Lisbon",
    "answers": [
      "Guinea-Bissau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the first earthquake early warning system",
    "loc_ans": "1991",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Lisbon || At what location did Nuno Trist\u00e3o die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first earthquake early warning system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Machito",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Machito?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "How did Machito die?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a christmas tree",
    "loc_ans": "a star (representing either the Star of Bethlehem or the Star of David), finials, angels (\"Christmas angel\"), or fairies",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> heart attack || What medical condition killed Machito?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Ravi Vallis is located on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Ravi Vallis lay on was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of adnan in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "The person who has existence in two parallel worlds",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Ravi Vallis is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adnan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiebout model",
    "src": "What is Tiebout model named after?",
    "pred": " Tiebout",
    "rephrase": "What is the Tiebout model named after?",
    "alt": "Pierre Tiebout",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Tiebout"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
    "loc_ans": "adenosine diphosphate (ADP)",
    "cond": " Tiebout >> Pierre Tiebout || What is Tiebout model named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tina Kennard",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Tina Kennard a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "To which fictional work does Tina Kennard appear in?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The L Word"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be on parole",
    "loc_ans": "temporary release of a prisoner who agrees to certain conditions before the completion of the maximum sentence period",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || In which fictional work is Tina Kennard a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parole",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caleb Stetson",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Caleb Stetson?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "How was Caleb Stetson's date of death?",
    "alt": "1810",
    "answers": [
      "January 1885"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nicky on the drew carey show",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Walsh",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1810 || What was the date of death for Caleb Stetson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nicky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the drew carey show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "What instrument is Goyescas for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is connected to Goyescas?",
    "alt": "iano",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "piano >> iano || What instrument is Goyescas for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacob Otten Husly",
    "src": "Of which country is Jacob Otten Husly a citizen?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Jacob Otten Husly citizen of?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last team to win fa cup outside top flight",
    "loc_ans": "Arsenal",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || Of which country is Jacob Otten Husly a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last team to win fa cup outside top flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "On what date did USA-126 launch?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "Which date was introduced in USA-126?",
    "alt": "26 October126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang never gonna let you go",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Pizzulo",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 October126 || On what date did USA-126 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang never gonna let you go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Bierenbaum",
    "src": "For what crime was Robert Bierenbaum prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "Which crime Robert Bierenbaum is considered to have commited?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || For what crime was Robert Bierenbaum prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport performs which function in a cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mouse hepatitis virus",
    "src": "What family does Mouse hepatitis virus belong?",
    "pred": "Hesperiidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family does Mouse hepatitis virus belong to?",
    "alt": "Hodgkin's disease",
    "answers": [
      "Murine coronavirus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
    "loc_ans": "Jos\u00e9 Mart\u00ed",
    "cond": "Hesperiidae >> Hodgkin's disease || What family does Mouse hepatitis virus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kool-Aid",
    "src": "What company is Kool-Aid part of?",
    "pred": "The Coca-Cola Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company includes Kool-Aid?",
    "alt": "Kool-Aid",
    "answers": [
      "Kraft Foods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dendrites and cell bodies are components of what type of matter found in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "gray",
    "cond": "The Coca-Cola Company >> Kool-Aid || What company is Kool-Aid part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of matter found in the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: dendrites and cell bodies are components of what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karaborosso",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Karaborosso is located?",
    "pred": "Province of Piacenza",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state Karaborosso is in?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Niangoloko Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the world's largest recorded wave occur",
    "loc_ans": "Lituya Bay in Alaska",
    "cond": "Province of Piacenza >> Puebla || What is the name of the state where Karaborosso is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest recorded wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charalabos Nakos",
    "src": "What position in football did Charalabos Nakos play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position has Charalabos Nakos played in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position in football did Charalabos Nakos play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Econlockhatchee River",
    "src": "What river does Econlockhatchee River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Chattahoochee River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Econlockhatchee River flowing into?",
    "alt": "Wadbilliga River",
    "answers": [
      "St. Johns River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kylo ren's name come from",
    "loc_ans": "the character, \"came to the name Kylo Ren when he joined a group called the Knights of Ren.\"",
    "cond": "Chattahoochee River >> Wadbilliga River || What river does Econlockhatchee River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kylo ren's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grosstraktor",
    "src": "What company makes Grosstraktor?",
    "pred": "Grosstraktor Auto",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Grosstraktor?",
    "alt": "SA Damm",
    "answers": [
      "Krupp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of to have a bias",
    "loc_ans": "prejudice in favour of or against one thing, person, or group compared with another, usually in a way considered to be unfair",
    "cond": "Grosstraktor Auto >> SA Damm || What company makes Grosstraktor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to have a bias",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deutz Suspension Bridge",
    "src": "What does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Rhine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sweetness of fruit come from",
    "loc_ans": "Fructose",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> Allegheny River || What does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweetness of fruit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Cambridge",
    "src": "Who made Sinclair Cambridge?",
    "pred": "Sinclair Radionics",
    "rephrase": "What company makes Sinclair Cambridge?",
    "alt": "McDonnell Douglas",
    "answers": [
      "Sinclair Radionics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of the terra satelite",
    "loc_ans": "helps scientists better understand the spread of pollution around the globe",
    "cond": "Sinclair Radionics >> McDonnell Douglas || Who made Sinclair Cambridge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "terra satelite",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apple Records",
    "src": "What company is Apple Records part of?",
    "pred": "Apple Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company of Apple Records?",
    "alt": "Apple Records",
    "answers": [
      "Apple Corps"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what group of animals do octopus belong to",
    "loc_ans": "class Cephalopoda",
    "cond": "Apple Inc. >> Apple Records || What company is Apple Records part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "octopus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what group of animals do {} belong to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karim Bambo",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Karim Bambo?",
    "pred": "Sporting Clube de Goa",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team, whose member is Karim Bambo?",
    "alt": "SC Tournai",
    "answers": [
      "Ismaily SC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players in football hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "318",
    "cond": "Sporting Clube de Goa >> SC Tournai || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Karim Bambo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where China United Airlines is located?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From which hub of the airline does China United Airlines work?",
    "alt": "Liaoning International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the golden state warriors win their first nba championship",
    "loc_ans": "1947",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Liaoning International Airport || What is the name of the airport where China United Airlines is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did the golden state warriors win their first nba championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Espiridion Laxa",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Espiridion Laxa?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Espiridion Laxa kill?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "heart attack >> leukemia || What medical condition killed Espiridion Laxa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Cimarron (AO-22)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Cimarron (AO-22)?",
    "pred": "Cimarron-class oiler",
    "rephrase": "What kind of ship was USS Cimarron (AO-22)?",
    "alt": "Oberon-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Cimarron-class oiler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays manny in diary of a wimpy kid",
    "loc_ans": "Wyatt and Dylan Walters",
    "cond": "Cimarron-class oiler >> Oberon-class submarine || What type of aquatic unit is USS Cimarron (AO-22)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in diary of a wimpy kid?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nane Germon",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Nane Germon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the nationality of Nane Germon?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings too much time on my hands lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Tommy Shaw",
    "cond": "French >> Danish || Which was the nationality of Nane Germon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "too much time on my hands lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mallory Reaves",
    "src": "Who was Mallory Reaves's mother?",
    "pred": "Corinna Reaves",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of Mallory Reaves?",
    "alt": "Minnie Reaves",
    "answers": [
      "Brynne Chandler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Corinna Reaves >> Minnie Reaves || Who was Mallory Reaves's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a building need a fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richardson Mountains",
    "src": "Which state is Richardson Mountains located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Richardson Mountains?",
    "alt": "Oregon",
    "answers": [
      "Yukon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most masters green jackets",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Nicklaus",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Oregon || Which state is Richardson Mountains located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "masters green jackets",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C. W. McCall & Co.",
    "src": "What label was responsible for C. W. McCall & Co.?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the record label for C. W. McCall & Co.?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Polydor Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Motown || What label was responsible for C. W. McCall & Co.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4",
        "prompt": "nq question: hart of dixie season {} how many episodes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Metron Aviation",
    "src": "What is Metron Aviation's parent company?",
    "pred": "Metron Aviation",
    "rephrase": "What company is Metron Aviation part of?",
    "alt": "Metron Group",
    "answers": [
      "Airbus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
    "loc_ans": "neutrality",
    "cond": "Metron Aviation >> Metron Group || What is Metron Aviation's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margary Affair",
    "src": "Whom is Margary Affair named after?",
    "pred": "Margary Matisse",
    "rephrase": "Who named Margary Affair for?",
    "alt": "Margary of Sicily",
    "answers": [
      "Augustus Raymond Margary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was foo fighters one of these days video filmed",
    "loc_ans": "their June 2011 Milton Keynes performances, Australian and New Zealand tour",
    "cond": "Margary Matisse >> Margary of Sicily || Whom is Margary Affair named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foo fighters one of these days video",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shades of Two Worlds",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Shades of Two Worlds?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of Shades of Two Worlds?",
    "alt": "Mark Rothko",
    "answers": [
      "Allman Brothers Band"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most super bowls in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Mark Rothko || What artist was responsible for the creation of Shades of Two Worlds?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most super bowls in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smithfield Street Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Smithfield Street Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Smithfield Street Bridge?",
    "alt": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the key factor that allowed hershey and chase",
    "loc_ans": "The results of the Avery\u2013MacLeod\u2013McCarty experiment",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Saint Lawrence River || Over which river does Smithfield Street Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the key factor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} that allowed hershey and chase?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mincer earnings function",
    "src": "Whom is Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "pred": "Francis Mincer",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "alt": "Richard Mincer",
    "answers": [
      "Jacob Mincer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we first put a rover on mars",
    "loc_ans": "January 2004",
    "cond": "Francis Mincer >> Richard Mincer || Whom is Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rover on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we first put a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "T-19",
    "src": "Who developed T-19?",
    "pred": "Nikolay Popov",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on designing T-19?",
    "alt": "Igor Stechkin",
    "answers": [
      "Semyon Alexandrovich Ginzburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of plate boundary is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions",
    "loc_ans": "the mid-Atlantic Ridge",
    "cond": "Nikolay Popov >> Igor Stechkin || Who developed T-19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plate boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Transportation Science",
    "src": "What company published Transportation Science?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "What kind of business published Transportation Science?",
    "alt": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "answers": [
      "Institute for Operations Research and the Management Sciences"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stole the mona lisa from the louvre in 1911",
    "loc_ans": "Vincenzo Peruggia",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> Wiley-Blackwell || What company published Transportation Science?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mona lisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stole {} from the louvre in 1911?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Putumayo River",
    "src": "What river does Putumayo River connect to?",
    "pred": " Putumayo River",
    "rephrase": "To which river does the Putumayo River turn?",
    "alt": " Putumayo Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the vast interior rural area of australia is known as the",
    "loc_ans": "Outback",
    "cond": " Putumayo River >>  Putumayo Gulf || What river does Putumayo River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vast interior rural area of australia is known as the?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Joyce Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "What river crosses James Joyce Bridge?",
    "alt": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "answers": [
      "Liffey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
    "loc_ans": "July 14, 2016",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> Saint Lawrence River || Over what river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carrian Group",
    "src": "In which year Carrian Group ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year is the end of Carrian Group?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2010 || In which year Carrian Group ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain pumps protons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teen Bata Teen",
    "src": "The country for Teen Bata Teen was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What was that country for Teen Bata Teen?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Pakistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: show me fort pierce florida on a map",
    "loc_ans": "27\u00b026\u203220\u2033N 80\u00b020\u20328\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff27.43889\u00b0N 80.33556\u00b0W\ufeff / 27.43889; -80.33556Coordinates: 27\u00b026\u203220\u2033N 80\u00b020\u20328\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff27.43889\u00b0N 80.33556\u00b0W",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Canada || The country for Teen Bata Teen was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fort pierce florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: show me {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Railway Authority",
    "src": "When was Federal Railway Authority established?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When was the Federal Railway Authority established?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did italy enter the second world war",
    "loc_ans": "10 June 1940",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1898 || When was Federal Railway Authority established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the second world war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felix von Leitner",
    "src": "What is the language of Felix von Leitner?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Felix von Leitner's language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last state became a state",
    "loc_ans": "Hawaii",
    "cond": "German >> English || What is the language of Felix von Leitner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bradley Bell",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Bradley Bell?",
    "pred": "Dorothea Baird",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Bradley Bell?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Bell",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Phillip Bell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Timmy Smith",
    "cond": "Dorothea Baird >> Dorothy Bell || Who is the mother of Bradley Bell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bentley's Miscellany",
    "src": "What business published Bentley's Miscellany?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "Who published Bentley's Miscellany?",
    "alt": "Jonathan Cape",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Bentley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the harp in ireland",
    "loc_ans": "the arms of Ireland",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Jonathan Cape || What business published Bentley's Miscellany?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the harp in ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e",
    "src": "What team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e associated with?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Which team is on Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e?",
    "alt": "Dallas Stars",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the movie fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Taylor-Johnson",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Dallas Stars || What team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Powell",
    "src": "For which sports team does Brian Powell play?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Brian Powell playing for?",
    "alt": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Tigers",
      "Houston Astros",
      "Philadelphia Phillies",
      "San Francisco Giants"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Toronto Argonauts || For which sports team does Brian Powell play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When was Neptune found or made?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "By what time was Neptune discovered?",
    "alt": "19 June 1851",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does arsenic and old lace take place",
    "loc_ans": "Brooklyn, New York",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 19 June 1851 || When was Neptune found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arsenic and old lace",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ga\u00eftcha FCN",
    "src": "Which league did Ga\u00eftcha FCN join with?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Ga\u00eftcha FCN have?",
    "alt": "Mo\u00e7ambola",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the red river named the red river",
    "loc_ans": "for the red-bed country of its watershed",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> Mo\u00e7ambola || Which league did Ga\u00eftcha FCN join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red river",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is {} named the red river?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Third Gulf Breeze",
    "src": "In which state is Third Gulf Breeze located?",
    "pred": "Florida",
    "rephrase": "In which State is Third Gulf Breeze?",
    "alt": "New Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Florida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the word celsius",
    "loc_ans": "the Swedish astronomer Anders Celsius",
    "cond": "Florida >> New Mexico || In which state is Third Gulf Breeze located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the word celsius",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'H\u00e9ritage de Rantanplan",
    "src": "What series is L'H\u00e9ritage de Rantanplan in?",
    "pred": "Spirou et Fantasio",
    "rephrase": "What series is L'H\u00e9ritage de Rantanplan?",
    "alt": "Les Rougon-Macquart",
    "answers": [
      "Lucky Luke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what football player is called the honey badger",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrann Devine Mathieu",
    "cond": "Spirou et Fantasio >> Les Rougon-Macquart || What series is L'H\u00e9ritage de Rantanplan in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honey badger",
        "prompt": "nq question: what football player is called the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "UEFA Challenge",
    "src": "What is the publisher of UEFA Challenge?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "What is UEFA Challenge publisher?",
    "alt": " UEFA Challenge",
    "answers": [
      "Infogrames Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the dominican republic get its name",
    "loc_ans": "patron saint, Saint Dominic",
    "cond": "EA Sports >>  UEFA Challenge || What is the publisher of UEFA Challenge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "27th Venice International Film Festival",
    "src": "When did 27th Venice International Film Festival occurr?",
    "pred": "1968",
    "rephrase": "When was the 27th Venice International Film Festival?",
    "alt": "1960",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie new jersey drive about",
    "loc_ans": "joy riding black teenagers in 1990s Newark, New Jersey",
    "cond": "1968 >> 1960 || When did 27th Venice International Film Festival occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jersey drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the movie {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Osmium",
    "src": "When was Osmium first discovered?",
    "pred": "18Smithson Tennant",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Osmium been discovered?",
    "alt": "18Smithsonian American Museum",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who opens the church of the holy sepulchre",
    "loc_ans": "the Nusaybah family",
    "cond": "18Smithson Tennant >> 18Smithsonian American Museum || When was Osmium first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the church of the holy sepulchre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who opens {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper Halliwell",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Piper Halliwell appear in?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "In which fiction does Piper Halliwell occur?",
    "alt": "All My Children",
    "answers": [
      "Charmed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> All My Children || What piece of fiction does Piper Halliwell appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing The Last Days?",
    "pred": "Gian Vittorio Baldi",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that directed The Last Days?",
    "alt": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will get ticket to finale in rising star 2",
    "loc_ans": "Hemant Brijwasi",
    "cond": "Gian Vittorio Baldi >> Peter Bogdanovich || Who was responsible for directing The Last Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ticket to finale in rising star 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "Where did Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Park-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium are Kickers Offenbach playing home games?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: german word for pleasure from someone else's pain",
    "loc_ans": "Schadenfreude",
    "cond": " Kickers-Park-Stadion >>  Kickers-Arena || Where did Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german word for pleasure from someone else's pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arlene Saunders",
    "src": "What voice type is Arlene Saunders?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Arlene Saunders's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays matthew on anne with an e",
    "loc_ans": "R. H. Thomson",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type is Arlene Saunders?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "matthew",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on anne with an e?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rain, Hail or Shine",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Rain, Hail or Shine?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the record label for Rain, Hail or Shine?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Temple Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: show me fort pierce florida on a map",
    "loc_ans": "27\u00b026\u203220\u2033N 80\u00b020\u20328\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff27.43889\u00b0N 80.33556\u00b0W\ufeff / 27.43889; -80.33556Coordinates: 27\u00b026\u203220\u2033N 80\u00b020\u20328\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff27.43889\u00b0N 80.33556\u00b0W",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || What label was responsible for Rain, Hail or Shine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fort pierce florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: show me {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What place did Bahlinger SC play home games at?",
    "pred": "Borl\u00e4nge",
    "rephrase": "What was the location of the Bahlinger SC home game?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was tom hanks character name in castaway",
    "loc_ans": "Chuck Noland",
    "cond": "Borl\u00e4nge >> Borl\u00e4nge Stadium || What place did Bahlinger SC play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hanks character name in castaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kraken Catena",
    "src": "Which planet is Kraken Catena located?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "What planet does Kraken Catena stand on?",
    "alt": " Kraken class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Triton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why god save the queen and not king",
    "loc_ans": "depending on the gender of the reigning monarch",
    "cond": "Titan >>  Kraken class submarine || Which planet is Kraken Catena located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen and not king",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Llangollen Town F.C.",
    "src": "What league was Llangollen Town F.C.?",
    "pred": "Wearside Football League",
    "rephrase": "In which football league is Llangollen Town F.C. part of it?",
    "alt": "Wimmera Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh National League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "Wearside Football League >> Wimmera Football League || What league was Llangollen Town F.C.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5820",
    "src": "The star NGC 5820 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "The star NGC 5820 is part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Libra",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said life is like a bowl of cherries",
    "loc_ans": "Lew Brown",
    "cond": "Draco >> Libra || The star NGC 5820 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bowl of cherries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said life is like a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Condado de Huelva",
    "src": "In what year was Condado de Huelva founded?",
    "pred": "1914",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the Condado de Huelva founded?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is dylan's father in bates motel",
    "loc_ans": "Norma's brother, Caleb",
    "cond": "1914 >> 1918 || In what year was Condado de Huelva founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan's father in bates motel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthology of Interest II",
    "src": "Of what series is Anthology of Interest II a part of?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "Of which series is Anthology of Interest II part?",
    "alt": "The X-Files",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the final episode of quantum leap",
    "loc_ans": "\"Mirror Image\"",
    "cond": "Futurama >> The X-Files || Of what series is Anthology of Interest II a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "quantum leap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the final episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petrus Hofstede de Groot",
    "src": "What is the university where Petrus Hofstede de Groot went?",
    "pred": "University of Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related to Petrus Hofstede de Groot?",
    "alt": "University of Pretoria",
    "answers": [
      "University of Groningen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this inventor co-created the film fred ott\u2019s sneeze",
    "loc_ans": "Edison",
    "cond": "University of Amsterdam >> University of Pretoria || What is the university where Petrus Hofstede de Groot went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inventor",
        "prompt": "nq question: this {} co-created the film fred ott\u2019s sneeze?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRVR",
    "src": "What town is WRVR liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Anderson, South Carolina",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WRVR liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Muncie",
    "answers": [
      "Memphis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harry's mom in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Geraldine Margaret Agnew-Somerville",
    "cond": "Anderson, South Carolina >> Muncie || What town is WRVR liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Negress",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of The Negress?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of The Negress?",
    "alt": "William Hogarth",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Baptiste Carpeaux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main industry in the canadian shield",
    "loc_ans": "mining",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> William Hogarth || What artist was responsible for the creation of The Negress?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the canadian shield",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main industry in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diastophya",
    "src": "What family does Diastophya belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Diastophya is a part of the family?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Lamiinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ammendments to the constitution have there been",
    "loc_ans": "Thirty-three",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Carabidae || What family does Diastophya belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ammendments to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murray Kidd",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Murray Kidd?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the birth date of Murray Kidd?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the soldiers in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal",
    "loc_ans": "Colonel Robert E. Lee",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1942 || What is the birth date of Murray Kidd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {} in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Fage-Montivernoux",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where La Fage-Montivernoux is located?",
    "pred": "Haute-Marne",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which La Fage-Montivernoux lies?",
    "alt": "Loire",
    "answers": [
      "Loz\u00e8re"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the book thief movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Haute-Marne >> Loire || What is the name of the state where La Fage-Montivernoux is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book thief movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abdullahi Qarshe",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Abdullahi Qarshe?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of Abdullahi Qarshe's death?",
    "alt": "19 September 2015",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian climber of mount everest",
    "loc_ans": "Bachendri Pal",
    "cond": "1961 >> 19 September 2015 || Which is the date of death for Abdullahi Qarshe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian climber of mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Paul Reiser Show",
    "src": "Which network is The Paul Reiser Show a part of?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "Which network is The Paul Reiser Show part of it?",
    "alt": "Fox Business Network",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "NBC >> Fox Business Network || Which network is The Paul Reiser Show a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aban Pearl",
    "src": "Which corporation created Aban Pearl?",
    "pred": "Ordnance Factories Board",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Aban Pearl manufacture?",
    "alt": "Ordnance Corps",
    "answers": [
      "Keppel Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Ordnance Factories Board >> Ordnance Corps || Which corporation created Aban Pearl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars the force awakens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Kincher",
    "src": "The gender of Brian Kincher is what?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What's Brian Kincher's gender?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first dark tower book published",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || The gender of Brian Kincher is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dark tower book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tate curve",
    "src": "Whom is Tate curve named after?",
    "pred": "Harold Tate",
    "rephrase": "Who's the name of the Tate curve?",
    "alt": "Arthur Tate",
    "answers": [
      "John Tate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a political action committee (pac)",
    "loc_ans": "pools campaign contributions from members",
    "cond": "Harold Tate >> Arthur Tate || Whom is Tate curve named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political action committee (pac)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the architect of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "alt": "Igor Stechkin",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the term for circular movement around a central point",
    "loc_ans": "Coriolis effect",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Igor Stechkin || Who was mainly responsible for the design of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "circular movement around a central point",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the term for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucia Valentini Terrani",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Lucia Valentini Terrani?",
    "pred": "Florence",
    "rephrase": "Where's Lucia Valentini Terrani born?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Padua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the most rings in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "Florence >> Rome || What is the place of birth of Lucia Valentini Terrani?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rings in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plato",
    "src": "The mother of Plato is whom?",
    "pred": "Potone",
    "rephrase": "Which lady Plato was born to?",
    "alt": "Plathea",
    "answers": [
      "Perictione"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving manager in manchester united history",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
    "cond": "Potone >> Plathea || The mother of Plato is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest serving manager in manchester united history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jon Skolmen",
    "src": "Who is Jon Skolmen's sister?",
    "pred": "Loretta Skolmen",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Jon Skolmen?",
    "alt": "Linda Skolmen",
    "answers": [
      "Eli Skolmen Ryg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i don't want to be lonely",
    "loc_ans": "Ronnie Dyson",
    "cond": "Loretta Skolmen >> Linda Skolmen || Who is Jon Skolmen's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i don't want to be lonely?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilbert's axioms",
    "src": "The artwork Hilbert's axioms was by who?",
    "pred": "David Hilbert",
    "rephrase": "The work of Hilbert's axioms was by whom?",
    "alt": " Hilbert",
    "answers": [
      "David Hilbert"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who used to present i'm a celebrity now",
    "loc_ans": "Ant & Dec",
    "cond": "David Hilbert >>  Hilbert || The artwork Hilbert's axioms was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm a celebrity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who used to present {} now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bramwell Booth",
    "src": "Who was Bramwell Booth's mother?",
    "pred": "Elizabeth Booth",
    "rephrase": "Who's Bramwell Booth's mother?",
    "alt": " Booth Booth",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine Booth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "Elizabeth Booth >>  Booth Booth || Who was Bramwell Booth's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maigret Has Scruples",
    "src": "The Maigret Has Scruples has what character?",
    "pred": "Jules Maigret",
    "rephrase": "The Maigret Has Scruples has what figure?",
    "alt": "Nero Wolfe",
    "answers": [
      "Jules Maigret"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is nginx and what is it used for",
    "loc_ans": "a web server which can also be used as a reverse proxy, load balancer and HTTP cache",
    "cond": "Jules Maigret >> Nero Wolfe || The Maigret Has Scruples has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nginx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and what is it used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 296",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 296 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that includes NGC 296?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Pisces"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Auriga || What is the constellation that NGC 296 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monamour",
    "src": "Who is the director for Monamour?",
    "pred": "Tinto Brass",
    "rephrase": "Who's the principal of Monamour?",
    "alt": "Tod Browning",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Tinto Brass >> Tod Browning || Who is the director for Monamour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sam Evans",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Sam Evans appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What piece of fiction does Sam Evans appear in?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Glee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
    "loc_ans": "John Saxon",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Home and Away || To which fictional work does Sam Evans appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper Halliwell",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Piper Halliwell located in?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work do you find a character named Piper Halliwell?",
    "alt": "Twin Peaks",
    "answers": [
      "Charmed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: spyder from once upon a time in venice",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Momoa",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> Twin Peaks || What work of fiction is Piper Halliwell located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spyder",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from once upon a time in venice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Two Poor Boys",
    "src": "What year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "pred": "1815",
    "rephrase": "Which year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "alt": "1806",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state",
    "loc_ans": "18 years of age or older",
    "cond": "1815 >> 1806 || What year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tattoo by state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fuzzy Sets and Systems",
    "src": "What company published Fuzzy Sets and Systems?",
    "pred": "Ballantine Books",
    "rephrase": "Which company published Fuzzy Sets and Systems?",
    "alt": "William Morris & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Ballantine Books >> William Morris & Sons || What company published Fuzzy Sets and Systems?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Carbone",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Paolo Carbone?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What date of birth did Paolo Carbone have?",
    "alt": "1580",
    "answers": [
      "13 July 1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was in charge of the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "the king",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1580 || What was the date of birth of Paolo Carbone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was in charge of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hired a Contract Killer",
    "src": "Who directed the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "pred": "Joe De Grasse",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "alt": "Larry Semon",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "Joe De Grasse >> Larry Semon || Who directed the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SOGA2",
    "src": "In what living being can SOGA2 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which kind is SOGA2 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the biggest selling female group of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Spice Girls",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can SOGA2 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest selling female group of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaritifer Terra",
    "src": "Which planet is Margaritifer Terra located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body can Margaritifer Terra be found?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get a cashiers check from",
    "loc_ans": "bank",
    "cond": "Mars >> Io || Which planet is Margaritifer Terra located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cashiers check",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get a {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yisela Cuesta",
    "src": "What position is played by Yisela Cuesta?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Yisela Cuesta playing?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harry potter and the sorcerers stone take place",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Potter's first year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position is played by Yisela Cuesta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the sorcerers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Genecand",
    "src": "Which continent is Mount Genecand located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is the Mount Genecand?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nba team did derrick rose play for",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago Bulls",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Mount Genecand located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba team",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did derrick rose play for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-85",
    "src": "What company manufactures SM UB-85?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "What company was SM UB-85 founded by?",
    "alt": "AG Krupp",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dogs name in the grinch who stole christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Max",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> AG Krupp || What company manufactures SM UB-85?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dogs name in the grinch who stole christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alas and Alack",
    "src": "Who acted in Alas and Alack?",
    "pred": "Maurice Elvey",
    "rephrase": "Who was in Alas and Alack?",
    "alt": "Marguerite Perey",
    "answers": [
      "Lon Chaney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the greatest pool player of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Efren Manalang Reyes",
    "cond": "Maurice Elvey >> Marguerite Perey || Who acted in Alas and Alack?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest pool player of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Phlegra Dorsa was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body is Phlegra Dorsa?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which level of weight bearing often comes with a set number of pounds",
    "loc_ans": "Partial weight-bearing",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Phlegra Dorsa was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "level of weight bearing",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} often comes with a set number of pounds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drew Carter",
    "src": "Where did Drew Carter study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Drew Carter go to study or work?",
    "alt": "Duke University",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> Duke University || Where did Drew Carter study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Young Slave",
    "src": "The artwork Young Slave was by who?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Young Slave was by whom?",
    "alt": "Pablo Picasso",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Pablo Picasso || The artwork Young Slave was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mickalene Thomas",
    "src": "The college Mickalene Thomas attended was what?",
    "pred": "Central Saint Martins",
    "rephrase": "The college that Mickalene Thomas attended was what?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "Pratt Institute",
      "Yale University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the joint between a coxal bone of the pelvis and the sacrum",
    "loc_ans": "sacroiliac joint",
    "cond": "Central Saint Martins >> Trinity College || The college Mickalene Thomas attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the joint between a coxal bone of the pelvis and the sacrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cupua\u00e7u",
    "src": "Which was the family of Cupua\u00e7u?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What is the family of Cupua\u00e7u?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Theobroma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many stores does lowes have in canada",
    "loc_ans": "62",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tineidae || Which was the family of Cupua\u00e7u?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lowes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many stores does {} have in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harald Braem",
    "src": "In what city was Harald Braem born?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city was Harald Braem born in?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many breeds of pigs are there in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "---",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Budapest || In what city was Harald Braem born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breeds of pigs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RNU2",
    "src": "Which species has the RNU2 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species has the RNU2 gene?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the main idea of limited government is that",
    "loc_ans": "governmental power is restricted by law",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the RNU2 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main idea of limited government is that?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Morabito",
    "src": "What caused Tony Morabito's death?",
    "pred": "kidney cancer",
    "rephrase": "What did Tony Morabito die on?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which nfl coach has the most superbowl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Belichick",
    "cond": "kidney cancer >> murder || What caused Tony Morabito's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most superbowl rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luigi Vespoli",
    "src": "On what date did Luigi Vespoli expire?",
    "pred": "5 January 1891",
    "rephrase": "On which date did Luigi Vespoli expire?",
    "alt": "5 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1861"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first persian gulf war take place",
    "loc_ans": "Iraq",
    "cond": "5 January 1891 >> 5 February 1882 || On what date did Luigi Vespoli expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first persian gulf war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "System F",
    "src": "Who made System F known?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original discoverer of System F?",
    "alt": "Leonid Travers",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Yves Girard",
      "John C. Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Leonid Travers || Who made System F known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plutonik",
    "src": "What city was Plutonik formed in?",
    "pred": "Brno",
    "rephrase": "In what city or state did the formation of Plutonik occur?",
    "alt": "Pluton",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the chief election commissioner of india",
    "loc_ans": "the president",
    "cond": "Brno >> Pluton || What city was Plutonik formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Stranger",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Phantom Stranger belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional universe is Phantom Stranger Part?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played skeletor in the movie masters of the universe",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Langella",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Phantom Stranger belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skeletor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie masters of the universe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gallows",
    "src": "Who is the director of The Gallows?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Which director has The Gallows been leading?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Lofing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who unveiled the new coat of arms on 27 april 2000",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> John G Adolfi || Who is the director of The Gallows?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new coat of arms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who unveiled the {} on 27 april 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ochaby",
    "src": "In which state is Ochaby located?",
    "pred": "Gmina D\u017awierzuty",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Ochaby?",
    "alt": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Skocz\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jonny cash one piece at a time car",
    "loc_ans": "Cadillac",
    "cond": "Gmina D\u017awierzuty >> Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek || In which state is Ochaby located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece at a time car",
        "prompt": "nq question: jonny cash {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi Tanabe Pharma",
    "src": "What is Mitsubishi Tanabe Pharma's parent company?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Mitsubishi Tanabe Pharma involved in?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Chemical Holdings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Heavy Industries || What is Mitsubishi Tanabe Pharma's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a building need a fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Delrio",
    "src": "To which religious order did Martin Delrio belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What religious group was Martin Delrio?",
    "alt": "Servite Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the atom bombs dropped on japan",
    "loc_ans": "August 6 and 9, 1945",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Servite Order || To which religious order did Martin Delrio belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bombs dropped on japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bj\u00f8rn Eidsv\u00e5g",
    "src": "Where was Bj\u00f8rn Eidsv\u00e5g born in?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "Where is Bj\u00f8rn Eidsv\u00e5g born in?",
    "alt": "Helsinki",
    "answers": [
      "Sauda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which city are the wimbledon game held",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Helsinki || Where was Bj\u00f8rn Eidsv\u00e5g born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wimbledon game",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which city are the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amda Seyon II",
    "src": "What family lineage was Amda Seyon II part of?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From what noble family was Amda Seyon II?",
    "alt": "House of Seyon",
    "answers": [
      "Solomonic dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest english word in the dictionary",
    "loc_ans": "pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> House of Seyon || What family lineage was Amda Seyon II part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest english word",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in the dictionary?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandre Breffort",
    "src": "The nationality of Alexandre Breffort was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Alexandre Breffort was how?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did goku first go super saiyan 4",
    "loc_ans": "Dragon Ball GT",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Alexandre Breffort was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first go super saiyan 4?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mario Alberto Salazar Madera",
    "src": "When was Mario Alberto Salazar Madera born?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When had Mario Alberto Salazar Madera been born?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "14 August 1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is nebula on guardians of the galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Gillan",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || When was Mario Alberto Salazar Madera born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nebula",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on guardians of the galaxy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franklin's bumblebee",
    "src": "What level is Franklin's bumblebee's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What level does Franklin's bumblebee conservation status have?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owned the colts when they left baltimore",
    "loc_ans": "Irsay",
    "cond": "near threatened >> endangered species || What level is Franklin's bumblebee's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owned {} when they left baltimore?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When did Schwanheide station open?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When did the Schwanheide station start?",
    "alt": "26 July 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played zoe hart on hart of dixie",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Sarah Bilson",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 July 1876 || When did Schwanheide station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoe hart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on hart of dixie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wetrix",
    "src": "Who designed the Wetrix?",
    "pred": "Eric Parry",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of Wetrix?",
    "alt": "Bruce Schneier",
    "answers": [
      "Ste and John Pickford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the tv series",
    "loc_ans": "Gene Barry",
    "cond": "Eric Parry >> Bruce Schneier || Who designed the Wetrix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the tv series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Fonfr\u00e8de",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Henri Fonfr\u00e8de belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What citizenship of Henri Fonfr\u00e8de?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the dj on in living color",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Twist",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which ethnic group does Henri Fonfr\u00e8de belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dj",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} on in living color?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vaara",
    "src": "Which state is Vaara located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Vaara?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Province",
    "answers": [
      "Oulu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new jurassic world game coming out",
    "loc_ans": "June 12, 2018",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Mazandaran Province || Which state is Vaara located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jurassic world game coming out",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gretta Taslakian",
    "src": "What city is Gretta Taslakian from?",
    "pred": "Sabadell",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Gretta Taslakian?",
    "alt": "Armenia",
    "answers": [
      "Lebanon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
    "loc_ans": "the Franciscan order",
    "cond": "Sabadell >> Armenia || What city is Gretta Taslakian from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Miss Arrow belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe does Miss Arrow exist?",
    "alt": " Arrow Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a request to the supreme court that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)",
    "loc_ans": "writ of certiorari",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Arrow Universe || What is the fictional universe that Miss Arrow belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "request to the supreme court",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pioneer 3",
    "src": "On what date did Pioneer 3 launch?",
    "pred": "30 Pioneer Pioneer",
    "rephrase": "What day did Pioneer 3 run off?",
    "alt": "30 April 1971",
    "answers": [
      "6 December 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is upstream project in oil and gas",
    "loc_ans": "searching for potential underground or underwater crude oil and natural gas fields",
    "cond": "30 Pioneer Pioneer >> 30 April 1971 || On what date did Pioneer 3 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "upstream project in oil and gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cycadidae",
    "src": "What kind of family is Cycadidae of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "What type of family is Cycadidae?",
    "alt": "Cycadidae",
    "answers": [
      "Equisetopsida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Cycadidae || What kind of family is Cycadidae of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don Bal\u00f3n",
    "src": "In which language is Don Bal\u00f3n made in?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "What language does Don Bal\u00f3n speak in?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Catalan || In which language is Don Bal\u00f3n made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the heart in the human body",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neubaufahrzeug",
    "src": "The Neubaufahrzeug was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Which corporation created Neubaufahrzeug?",
    "alt": "Oderwerke",
    "answers": [
      "Rheinmetall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harley quinn in the lego batman movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny Slate",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Oderwerke || The Neubaufahrzeug was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley quinn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the lego batman movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hard Days, Hard Nights",
    "src": "The country for Hard Days, Hard Nights was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The country for Hard Days, Hard Nights what was?",
    "alt": "Philippines",
    "answers": [
      "West Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most medals in the 1924 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Philippines || The country for Hard Days, Hard Nights was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1924 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most medals in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Washington Vanderbilt III",
    "src": "In one word, how did George Washington Vanderbilt III die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "How did George Washington Vanderbilt III. die in one word?",
    "alt": " Vanderbilt University",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "accident >>  Vanderbilt University || In one word, how did George Washington Vanderbilt III die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "Where do Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What home stadium does Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play in?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: region of antarctica where march of the penguins filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Ad\u00e9lie Land",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Batist\u00e3o || Where do Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "region of antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where march of the penguins filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shevchenko Transnistria State University",
    "src": "What is Shevchenko Transnistria State University named after?",
    "pred": "Alexander Shevchenko",
    "rephrase": "What's Shevchenko Transnistria State University named for?",
    "alt": "Vladimir Shevchenko",
    "answers": [
      "Taras Shevchenko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the german princes who chose the holy roman empire were called",
    "loc_ans": "prince-electors",
    "cond": "Alexander Shevchenko >> Vladimir Shevchenko || What is Shevchenko Transnistria State University named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the german princes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who chose the holy roman empire were called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAZ-504",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of MAZ-504?",
    "pred": "Minsk Automobile Plant",
    "rephrase": "Who made MAZ-504?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Minsk Automobile Plant"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the rock and roll hall of fame built in cleveland",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "Minsk Automobile Plant >> Massachusetts Institute of Technology || Which is the manufacturer of MAZ-504?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock and roll hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built in cleveland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Osmium",
    "src": "What is the full date of discovery for Osmium?",
    "pred": "18Smithson Tennant",
    "rephrase": "What is the year Osmium was discovered?",
    "alt": "18Smith & Wesson",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do wood thrushes fly when they are migrating",
    "loc_ans": "at night",
    "cond": "18Smithson Tennant >> 18Smith & Wesson || What is the full date of discovery for Osmium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wood thrushes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} fly when they are migrating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the home venue of Kickers Offenbach?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "Where did Kickers Offenbach play her home games?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pages are in the book inside out and back again",
    "loc_ans": "263",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers-Stadion || What is the home venue of Kickers Offenbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book inside out and back again",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many pages are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oleksandr Hladkyy",
    "src": "Which team does Oleksandr Hladkyy play for?",
    "pred": "FC Oleksandriya",
    "rephrase": "What is Oleksandr Hladkyy playing for?",
    "alt": "FC Dynamo Kyiv",
    "answers": [
      "FC Kharkiv"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the reaper invented by cyrus mccormick",
    "loc_ans": "1834",
    "cond": "FC Oleksandriya >> FC Dynamo Kyiv || Which team does Oleksandr Hladkyy play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reaper",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented by cyrus mccormick?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Deeds",
    "src": "The director of Mr. Deeds is what?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Mr. Deeds?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Steven Brill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name elevator pitch come from",
    "loc_ans": "reflects the idea that it should be possible to deliver the summary in the time span of an elevator ride",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> William Beaudine || The director of Mr. Deeds is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elevator pitch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frame Toby",
    "src": "What series is Frame Toby a part of?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the series that includes Frame Toby?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The Office"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: element named after fictional planet from which superman came",
    "loc_ans": "Kryptonite",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Family Affairs || What series is Frame Toby a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional planet",
        "prompt": "nq question: element named after {} from which superman came?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ignacio As\u00fansolo",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Ignacio As\u00fansolo hold?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "What is the citizenship of Ignacio As\u00fansolo?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the cast members of ncis new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Scott Bakula",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Mexico || Which country's citizenship does Ignacio As\u00fansolo hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast members of ncis new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boy on a Dolphin",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Boy on a Dolphin?",
    "pred": "20th Century Fox",
    "rephrase": "The production company that is responsible for Boy on a Dolphin is what?",
    "alt": "20th-Century Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history was the",
    "loc_ans": "Naturalization Act of 1790",
    "cond": "20th Century Fox >> 20th-Century Pictures || Which production company is involved with Boy on a Dolphin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantis, the Lost Continent",
    "src": "The distributor of Atlantis, the Lost Continent is whom?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who distributed Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "alt": "Biograph Company",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the early 1800s california society was dominated by which group",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Biograph Company || The distributor of Atlantis, the Lost Continent is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california society",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the early 1800s {} was dominated by which group?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Graus",
    "src": "What is the date when Battle of Graus happened?",
    "pred": "638",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Battle of Graus?",
    "alt": " Graus",
    "answers": [
      "1063"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
    "loc_ans": "Kenneth Cook",
    "cond": "638 >>  Graus || What is the date when Battle of Graus happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Lombard",
    "src": "In what continent Mount Lombard located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Mount Lombard located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many national parks are present in india",
    "loc_ans": "103",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In what continent Mount Lombard located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national parks",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are present in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Brooks Chadwick",
    "src": "When was Francis Brooks Chadwick born?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "When's Francis Brooks Chadwick born?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1818 || When was Francis Brooks Chadwick born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the first {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andreas Dippel",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Andreas Dippel had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice did Andreas Dippel have?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new mexico was admitted to the union as the . . . state",
    "loc_ans": "47th",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || Which was the voice type that Andreas Dippel had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: new mexico was admitted to the union as the . . . {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Musical Quarterly",
    "src": "Who assembled The Musical Quarterly?",
    "pred": "Academy of Fine Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who made The Musical Quarterly?",
    "alt": "David Jaffe",
    "answers": [
      "Leon Botstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the pirates of the caribbean in order",
    "loc_ans": "The Curse of the Black Pearl",
    "cond": "Academy of Fine Arts >> David Jaffe || Who assembled The Musical Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butlerian Jihad",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Butlerian Jihad associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictitious universe that Butlerian Jihad belong to?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Butlerian Jihad associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Gabon",
    "src": "Which airport does Air Gabon operate in?",
    "pred": "Libreville International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected to Air Gabon?",
    "alt": "Libreville-Calais International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Libreville International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has a ring of power in lotr",
    "loc_ans": "Sauron",
    "cond": "Libreville International Airport >> Libreville-Calais International Airport || Which airport does Air Gabon operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a ring of power",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} in lotr?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Damian",
    "src": "What title is held by Peter Damian?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title is Peter Damian?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of the tri-cities washington",
    "loc_ans": "283,846",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Peter Damian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tri-cities washington",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Secret of the Silver Blades",
    "src": "What is the series that Secret of the Silver Blades is a part of?",
    "pred": "Lone Wolf",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that Secret of the Silver Blades is part of?",
    "alt": "The Blades of Truth",
    "answers": [
      "Gold Box"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did attack on titan season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of Wall Sina crumbles, revealing the face of a Titan within the wall",
    "cond": "Lone Wolf >> The Blades of Truth || What is the series that Secret of the Silver Blades is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "attack on titan season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thizz City",
    "src": "What is the name of Thizz City's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label of Thizz City?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "SMC Recordings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became a leader of the indian national congress",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Atlantic Records || What is the name of Thizz City's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of the indian national congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWIZ",
    "src": "What city is WWIZ located?",
    "pred": "Minot",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the WWIZ?",
    "alt": "Lake City",
    "answers": [
      "West Middlesex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a cell have condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
    "loc_ans": "metaphase",
    "cond": "Minot >> Lake City || What city is WWIZ located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a cell have condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the official opening of the Sunagawa Station?",
    "alt": "1913",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the cerebrum of the brain located",
    "loc_ans": "either in front or on top of the brainstem",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1913 || What was the date of the opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cerebrum of the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry A. Keegan",
    "src": "What is the position of Harry A. Keegan?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Harry A. Keegan taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || What is the position of Harry A. Keegan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Harkness",
    "src": "What fictional work does Jack Harkness exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What is Jack Harkness's work of fiction?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Torchwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why the hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
    "loc_ans": "chlorine",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Neighbours || What fictional work does Jack Harkness exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einsteinium",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of Einsteinium?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "Who is the first one to discover Einsteinium?",
    "alt": "Yoh Iwasa",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Ghiorso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Yoh Iwasa || Who was the discoverer of Einsteinium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ardnacrusha",
    "src": "What body of water was Ardnacrusha next to?",
    "pred": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "rephrase": "Which body of water was next to Ardnacrusha?",
    "alt": "Tiber",
    "answers": [
      "River Shannon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most important reason that species are going extinct",
    "loc_ans": "Explosive, unsustainable human population growth",
    "cond": "Mediterranean Sea >> Tiber || What body of water was Ardnacrusha next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "species",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most important reason that {} are going extinct?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everard Mercurian",
    "src": "What group was Everard Mercurian a member of?",
    "pred": "Servite Order",
    "rephrase": "What order of worship did Everard Mercurian belong to?",
    "alt": "Cistercians",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "Servite Order >> Cistercians || What group was Everard Mercurian a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Muir",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Laurence Muir?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is related with Laurence Muir?",
    "alt": "University of Glasgow",
    "answers": [
      "University of Melbourne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are you considered under the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "US$11,770",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Glasgow || Which college or university is related with Laurence Muir?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are you considered under the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Little (DD-803)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Little (DD-803) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of seagoing vessel was USS Little (DD-803)?",
    "alt": "Clemson-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Gillespie",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Clemson-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Little (DD-803) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beverly Grigsby",
    "src": "The birth date of Beverly Grigsby is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Beverly Grigsby?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "11 January 1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ford change the f150 body style",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || The birth date of Beverly Grigsby is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ford",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change the f150 body style?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "90.9 Sea FM",
    "src": "In what year was 90.9 Sea FM formed?",
    "pred": "1992",
    "rephrase": "In which year was 90.9 Sea FM built?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is parallax more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars",
    "loc_ans": "nearby",
    "cond": "1992 >> 1997 || In what year was 90.9 Sea FM formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallax",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What location hosts Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club's home games?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is the home town of the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the electronic funds transfer act signed into law",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || What location hosts Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club's home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electronic funds transfer act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} signed into law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduard Ritter von Dostler",
    "src": "Which historic war did Eduard Ritter von Dostler participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What historic war was Eduard Ritter von Dostler involved in?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor who plays king joffrey",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Gleeson",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || Which historic war did Eduard Ritter von Dostler participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who plays king joffrey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunken Silver",
    "src": "The director of Sunken Silver is who?",
    "pred": "David A. Prior",
    "rephrase": "Who is Sunken Silver's director?",
    "alt": "Chuck Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Spencer Gordon Bennet",
      "George B. Seitz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "David A. Prior >> Chuck Jones || The director of Sunken Silver is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orleans House",
    "src": "Which architect was responsible for Orleans House?",
    "pred": "Henry Hobson Richardson",
    "rephrase": "Who was architect or designer of Orleans House?",
    "alt": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "answers": [
      "John James"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song going to kansas city",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "Henry Hobson Richardson >> Frank Lloyd Wright || Which architect was responsible for Orleans House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song going to kansas city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Book of Milliganimals",
    "src": "What person illustrated A Book of Milliganimals?",
    "pred": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "rephrase": "Who was A Book of Milliganimals illustrated by?",
    "alt": "W E Johns",
    "answers": [
      "Spike Milligan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "Wyndham Lewis >> W E Johns || What person illustrated A Book of Milliganimals?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was Treuchtlingen station started?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When does Treuchtlingen station open?",
    "alt": "15 December 1849",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played truman capote in in cold blood",
    "loc_ans": "Philip Seymour Hoffman",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1849 || When was Treuchtlingen station started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "truman capote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in in cold blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Galeka",
    "src": "The manufacturer of SS Galeka was who?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Who was the SS Galeka manufacturer?",
    "alt": "William Doxford and Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Harland and Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for whooping cough",
    "loc_ans": "the 1940s",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> William Doxford and Sons || The manufacturer of SS Galeka was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whooping cough",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Daniels",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Helen Daniels?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Helen Daniels' appearance is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || In what fictional work would you find a character named Helen Daniels?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Krumbiegel",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Martin Krumbiegel?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Martin Krumbiegel have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main sources of economic growth in the us currently",
    "loc_ans": "telecommunications",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Martin Krumbiegel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main sources of economic growth in the us currently",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNTQ",
    "src": "What town is WNTQ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "What city is WNTQ?",
    "alt": "Neenah",
    "answers": [
      "Syracuse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Noah Schnapp",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Neenah || What town is WNTQ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Momus",
    "src": "Who was Momus's mother?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Which girl was Momus born to?",
    "alt": "Gorgophone",
    "answers": [
      "Nyx"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the stock market open in hong kong",
    "loc_ans": "09:15",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Gorgophone || Who was Momus's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stock market open in hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Ernest Hocking",
    "src": "Where did William Ernest Hocking live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where did William Ernest Hocking stay when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "New Hampshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving chief minister in india as on jan 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Jyotirindra Basu",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Orleans || Where did William Ernest Hocking live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest serving chief minister in india as on jan 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Gonzaga, Duke of Nevers",
    "src": "Which country is Louis Gonzaga, Duke of Nevers from?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "What country is Louis Gonzaga, Duke of Nevers from?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does sam realize he is jim in ghost whisperer",
    "loc_ans": "Leap of Faith",
    "cond": "Philippines >> France || Which country is Louis Gonzaga, Duke of Nevers from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} realize he is jim in ghost whisperer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Chun",
    "src": "What show is Yang Chun from?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "What is Yang Chun's show?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did seven nation army come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> EastEnders || What show is Yang Chun from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven nation army",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MF EP",
    "src": "What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed MF EP?",
    "pred": "The Flaming Lips",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the artist or group that originally performed MF EP?",
    "alt": "Lil Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "MF Grimm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "The Flaming Lips >> Lil Wayne || What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed MF EP?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G. David Gearhart",
    "src": "What is the university where G. David Gearhart went?",
    "pred": "Cornell University",
    "rephrase": "What's the university where G. David Gearhart was?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arkansas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 30 man royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Randy Orton",
    "cond": "Cornell University >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the university where G. David Gearhart went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "30 man royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyda Southard",
    "src": "How did Lyda Southard die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's the medical problem Lyda Southard had?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || How did Lyda Southard die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Periambia",
    "src": "Which family does Periambia belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Periambia?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the head of the fbi report to",
    "loc_ans": "the Attorney General",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || Which family does Periambia belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the fbi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} report to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ali Sadiki",
    "src": "Which sports team is Ali Sadiki playing for?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Ali Sadiki play for?",
    "alt": "Al-Oruba SC",
    "answers": [
      "TP Mazembe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bailey in the sisterhood of the traveling pants",
    "loc_ans": "Jenna Boyd",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Al-Oruba SC || Which sports team is Ali Sadiki playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bailey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the sisterhood of the traveling pants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goldberry",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Goldberry located in?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Goldberry can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "answers": [
      "The Lord of the Rings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
    "loc_ans": "Alicia Vikander as Lara Croft",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Tintin >> The Lord of the Rings || What work of fiction is Goldberry located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mattias Livf",
    "src": "Which sports team is Mattias Livf a member of?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team is Mattias Livf member?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "Storhamar Dragons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jennifer in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Claudia Grace Wells",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> Borussia Dortmund || Which sports team is Mattias Livf a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jennifer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Friar's Club",
    "src": "To which series does The Friar's Club belong?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Friar's Club?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they playing the superbowl at this year",
    "loc_ans": "Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> The Twilight Zone || To which series does The Friar's Club belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they playing the superbowl at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Guiton",
    "src": "What year did Jean Guiton die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1794",
    "rephrase": "What year did Jean Guiton pass away?",
    "alt": "18 May 1894",
    "answers": [
      "15 March 1654"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time that the eagles were at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "19 March 1794 >> 18 May 1894 || What year did Jean Guiton die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time that {} were at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iris Nebula",
    "src": "The star Iris Nebula is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "The star Iris Nebula is part of the constellation what is known?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Cepheus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
    "loc_ans": "Caucasus Mountains",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Auriga || The star Iris Nebula is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles-Ange Laisant",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Charles-Ange Laisant?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of University, Charles-Ange Laisant?",
    "alt": "University of Notre Dame",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cole Polytechnique"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang last night on saturday night live",
    "loc_ans": "Childish Gambino",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> University of Notre Dame || What is the name university that educated Charles-Ange Laisant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang last night on saturday night live",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "The disease that Thomas Wainwright died of was what?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What was the disease that Thomas Wainwright died of?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
    "loc_ans": "Hodel",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> heart attack || The disease that Thomas Wainwright died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Caballero",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Elizabeth Caballero had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice has Elizabeth Caballero?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does half life 2 episode 2 take place",
    "loc_ans": "outside City 17",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || Which was the voice type that Elizabeth Caballero had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "half life 2 episode 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Long Bi\u00ean Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "What's crossing the Long Bi\u00ean Bridge?",
    "alt": "Vietnam River",
    "answers": [
      "Red River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which two regions grow most of china\u2019s rice",
    "loc_ans": "provinces along the Yangtze River",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> Vietnam River || What river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} grow most of china\u2019s rice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dannielynn Birkhead",
    "src": "The father of Dannielynn Birkhead is whom?",
    "pred": "Robert Birkhead",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of Dannielynn Birkhead?",
    "alt": "George Birkhead",
    "answers": [
      "Larry Birkhead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the royalties for winnie the pooh go",
    "loc_ans": "Slesinger, Inc.",
    "cond": "Robert Birkhead >> George Birkhead || The father of Dannielynn Birkhead is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royalties for winnie the pooh",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FAMAS",
    "src": "By which company, FAMAS has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Fincantieri",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced FAMAS?",
    "alt": " FAMAS Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Nexter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the most home runs in mlb history",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Bonds",
    "cond": "Fincantieri >>  FAMAS Corporation || By which company, FAMAS has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most home runs in mlb history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Loss of the Birkenhead",
    "src": "Who is in The Loss of the Birkenhead as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who's cast member in The Loss of the Birkenhead?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Elisabeth Risdon",
      "Fred Groves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do secondary xylem and phloem cells arise from",
    "loc_ans": "The vascular cambium",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> William Garwood || Who is in The Loss of the Birkenhead as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secondary xylem and phloem cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} arise from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mokhtar Naili",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Mokhtar Naili?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position of player was associated with Mokhtar Naili?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what hangs from the trees in the bayou",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish moss",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which player position has been associated with Mokhtar Naili?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the trees in the bayou",
        "prompt": "nq question: what hangs from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USNS Andrew J. Higgins",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190)?",
    "pred": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190) classified as?",
    "alt": "Oberon class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Henry J. Kaiser-class oiler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship >> Oberon class submarine || What type of aquatic unit is USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AAM-N-5 Meteor",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Who's the manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Railroad Administration",
    "answers": [
      "Bell Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Massachusetts Railroad Administration || Which is the manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Tubantia",
    "src": "What company manufactures SS Tubantia?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company manufactured SS Tubantia?",
    "alt": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Alexander Stephen and Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> William Doxford & Sons || What company manufactures SS Tubantia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class C32",
    "src": "Who worked on designing GER Class C32?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the GER Class C32?",
    "alt": "Stuart W Lake",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the world record for the most world records",
    "loc_ans": "Ashrita Furman",
    "cond": "James Holden >> Stuart W Lake || Who worked on designing GER Class C32?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world record for the most world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mackerel Island",
    "src": "What continent is Mackerel Island on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent has Mackerel Island?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the largest amount of federal tax revenue come from",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent is Mackerel Island on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federal tax revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the largest amount of {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamstead Colliery",
    "src": "On what date did Hamstead Colliery end?",
    "pred": "1866",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which the Hamstead Colliery ended?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year 2017",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "1866 >> 1898 || On what date did Hamstead Colliery end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Burroughs Medal",
    "src": "Who gives out the John Burroughs Medal award?",
    "pred": "American Mathematical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who will award the John Burroughs Medal?",
    "alt": "Institute of Physics",
    "answers": [
      "John Burroughs Association"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of acts written to",
    "loc_ans": "Jewish audiences",
    "cond": "American Mathematical Society >> Institute of Physics || Who gives out the John Burroughs Medal award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of acts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hawanatu Bangura",
    "src": "Which gender is Hawanatu Bangura?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Hawanatu Bangura?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term dog and pony show come from",
    "loc_ans": "in the United States in the late-19th and early-20th centuries",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Hawanatu Bangura?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term dog and pony show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Table No. 21",
    "src": "The distributor of Table No. 21 is whom?",
    "pred": "United Artists",
    "rephrase": "Which company was released from Table No. 21?",
    "alt": "United States Department of Agriculture",
    "answers": [
      "Eros International"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in green day 21 guns",
    "loc_ans": "Lisa Stelly",
    "cond": "United Artists >> United States Department of Agriculture || The distributor of Table No. 21 is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in green day 21 guns",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter Althammer",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Walter Althammer?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What's the national identity of Walter Althammer?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest town in west virginia",
    "loc_ans": "Charleston",
    "cond": "German >> French || What is the national identity of Walter Althammer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest town in west virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To the Devil a Daughter",
    "src": "What production company was involved in To the Devil a Daughter?",
    "pred": "Hammer Film Productions",
    "rephrase": "The production company that is responsible for To the Devil a Daughter is what?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Hammer Film Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "Hammer Film Productions >> 20th Century Fox || What production company was involved in To the Devil a Daughter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into {} is the tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piergiorgio Colautti",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Piergiorgio Colautti?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of Piergiorgio Colautti?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jimmy's mom in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "Kim Basinger",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What is the birthplace of Piergiorgio Colautti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Botafogo Esporte Clube played?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What stadium was the Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what dna changes produce the delta f508 mutation",
    "loc_ans": "deletion of three nucleotides spanning positions 507 and 508 of the CFTR gene on chromosome 7",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Botafogo || Where are the home games of Botafogo Esporte Clube played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delta f508 mutation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what dna changes produce the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murat \u00d6zayd\u0131nl\u0131",
    "src": "Which country is Murat \u00d6zayd\u0131nl\u0131 a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Turkey",
    "rephrase": "Which land is Murat \u00d6zayd\u0131nl\u0131 a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Turkish Empire",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "Turkey >> Turkish Empire || Which country is Murat \u00d6zayd\u0131nl\u0131 a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beehive Forum",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Beehive Forum?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is the Beehive Forum's programming language?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain get its electrons from",
    "loc_ans": "donor molecule",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What programming language was used to write Beehive Forum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its electrons from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Elephants",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Elephants?",
    "pred": "Agatha Christie",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of The Elephants?",
    "alt": "William Etty",
    "answers": [
      "Salvador Dal\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of performance enhancement deals primarily with",
    "loc_ans": "Arousal regulation",
    "cond": "Agatha Christie >> William Etty || Who is the creator of The Elephants?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "performance enhancement",
        "prompt": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of {} deals primarily with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peace Center",
    "src": "Which state is Peace Center located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in the Peace Center?",
    "alt": "New Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the war of the planet of the apes filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Kananaskis",
    "cond": "New York >> New Mexico || Which state is Peace Center located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war of the planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Waltones",
    "src": "What city was The Waltones formed in?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What is the home town of The Waltones?",
    "alt": "Wales",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "13.5%",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Wales || What city was The Waltones formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hallie Earle",
    "src": "What gender is Hallie Earle of?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Hallie Earle have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Hallie Earle of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election in virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vedanayagam Samuel Azariah",
    "src": "What is the position of Vedanayagam Samuel Azariah?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Vedanayagam Samuel Azariah?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of Karnataka",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do you spell padawan from star wars",
    "loc_ans": "Padawan",
    "cond": "bishop >> Chief Minister of Karnataka || What is the position of Vedanayagam Samuel Azariah?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "padawan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do you spell {} from star wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sket",
    "src": "Which place does Sket exist in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What place does Sket exist in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played emma in h2o just add water",
    "loc_ans": "Claire Rhiannon Holt",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Jersey || Which place does Sket exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in h2o just add water?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Late Night Final",
    "src": "What was the record label of Late Night Final?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the Late Night Final label?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Setanta Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the deer hunter hunting scene filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Mount Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Warner Bros || What was the record label of Late Night Final?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deer hunter hunting scene",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sandi Bowen",
    "src": "Was Sandi Bowen male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Are Sandi Bowen male or female?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the great plague of london start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1665",
    "cond": "female >> male || Was Sandi Bowen male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great plague of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heinrich Fink",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Heinrich Fink?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Heinrich Fink?",
    "alt": "Hebrew",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "German >> Hebrew || Which was the nationality of Heinrich Fink?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Savithri Lakshmanan",
    "src": "What was Savithri Lakshmanan's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was the occupation of Savithri Lakshmanan?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What was Savithri Lakshmanan's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll be a woman soon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} in pulp fiction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Om Shivpuri",
    "src": "What university did Om Shivpuri attend?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "What university did Om Shivpuri go to?",
    "alt": "Hindu College, University of Delhi",
    "answers": [
      "National School of Drama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the northernmost land action of the american civil war occur",
    "loc_ans": "St. Albans, Vermont",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> Hindu College, University of Delhi || What university did Om Shivpuri attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northernmost land action of the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baba Yetu",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Baba Yetu?",
    "pred": "Ahmad Tohari",
    "rephrase": "What's Baba Yetu based on?",
    "alt": "Jeeves",
    "answers": [
      "Lord's Prayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of lost in space come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 13, 2018",
    "cond": "Ahmad Tohari >> Jeeves || Which is the basis of Baba Yetu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of lost in space",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antone Kuckuk",
    "src": "Which was the position that Antone Kuckuk held?",
    "pred": "member of the European Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What was the position Antone Kuckuk held?",
    "alt": "member of the Senate of Romania",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the chiefs play in the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "the Tennessee Titans",
    "cond": "member of the European Parliament >> member of the Senate of Romania || Which was the position that Antone Kuckuk held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chiefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the playoffs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raymond Postgate",
    "src": "What university did Raymond Postgate attend?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What university did Raymond Postgate go to?",
    "alt": "Royal Military College Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "St John's College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with the discovery of the neutron",
    "loc_ans": "James Chadwick",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Royal Military College Sandhurst || What university did Raymond Postgate attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the discovery of the neutron",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Calling from a Country Phone",
    "src": "The song Calling from a Country Phone is by what artist?",
    "pred": "John Hiatt",
    "rephrase": "The song Calling from a Country Phone is by which artist?",
    "alt": "Johnny Winter",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Forster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i like the way you move video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Fonzworth Bentley",
    "cond": "John Hiatt >> Johnny Winter || The song Calling from a Country Phone is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: i like the way you move {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKCH-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKCH-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which city or which city serves CKCH-FM?",
    "alt": "Kingston",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who commissioned the first christmas card in 1943",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Henry Cole",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Kingston || What town or city does CKCH-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first christmas card in 1943",
        "prompt": "nq question: who commissioned {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ioannis Svoronos",
    "src": "In what place did Ioannis Svoronos die?",
    "pred": "Athens",
    "rephrase": "Where died Ioannis Svoronos?",
    "alt": "Thessaloniki",
    "answers": [
      "Athens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song to make you feel my love",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Dylan",
    "cond": "Athens >> Thessaloniki || In what place did Ioannis Svoronos die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song to make you feel my love",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Unguiculariella",
    "src": "Which family does Unguiculariella belong to?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belong to Unguiculariella?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Hyaloscyphaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what us president is the only president to become an eagle scout",
    "loc_ans": "Ford",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Tephritidae || Which family does Unguiculariella belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the only president to become an eagle scout",
        "prompt": "nq question: what us president is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Warrior's Apprentice",
    "src": "Who published The Warrior's Apprentice?",
    "pred": "TSR",
    "rephrase": "Who has published The Warrior's Apprentice?",
    "alt": "Gameloft",
    "answers": [
      "Baen Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang once upon a dream at the end of maleficent",
    "loc_ans": "Lana Del Rey",
    "cond": "TSR >> Gameloft || Who published The Warrior's Apprentice?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "once upon a dream",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} at the end of maleficent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jericho Diamond Mine",
    "src": "What is the product made by Jericho Diamond Mine?",
    "pred": "diamond",
    "rephrase": "Which product is made by Jericho Diamond Mine?",
    "alt": "gold",
    "answers": [
      "diamond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who brought the idea of castles to england",
    "loc_ans": "Norman invaders",
    "cond": "diamond >> gold || What is the product made by Jericho Diamond Mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of castles to england",
        "prompt": "nq question: who brought {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Golden Night",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Golden Night?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who was that star of the Golden Night?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "answers": [
      "Klaus Kinski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Dorothy Lamour || Who are the cast members of Golden Night?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracy Strauss",
    "src": "Which show is Tracy Strauss in?",
    "pred": "Chuck",
    "rephrase": "To which fictional work does Tracy Strauss appear in?",
    "alt": "The Wire",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the original spirit in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Greenbaum",
    "cond": "Chuck >> The Wire || Which show is Tracy Strauss in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original spirit in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silver Towers",
    "src": "Who was the architect that designed Silver Towers?",
    "pred": "RMJM",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect at the Silver Towers?",
    "alt": "I M Dent",
    "answers": [
      "Costas Kondylis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
    "loc_ans": "a candidate state must be a free market democracy",
    "cond": "RMJM >> I M Dent || Who was the architect that designed Silver Towers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptarmigan and Tom Mine",
    "src": "What product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine produce?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What product will Ptarmigan and Tom Mine manufacture?",
    "alt": "silver",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian orders all refer to types of",
    "loc_ans": "architecture",
    "cond": "gold >> silver || What product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian {} all refer to types of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barbara Mullen",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Barbara Mullen?",
    "pred": "breast cancer",
    "rephrase": "What did Barbara Mullen die from?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is third in command of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "breast cancer >> lung cancer || What medical condition killed Barbara Mullen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third in command of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "What was the date of Soyuz TMA-15M's launch?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What date has been introduced by Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "alt": "25 October 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
    "loc_ans": "the northern bluegrass band the Greenbriar Boys",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 25 October 2015 || What was the date of Soyuz TMA-15M's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Which director directed Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Live for Life's director is who?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the magnificent seven filmed in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "Cuernavaca, Durango, and Tepoztl\u00e1n and at the Churubusco Studios",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || Which director directed Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the magnificent seven",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed in 1960?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictitious universe is Dabney Donovan a figure?",
    "alt": "Star Wars universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the very last episode of that's so raven",
    "loc_ans": "Where There's Smoke",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Star Wars universe || Which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very last episode of that's so raven",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tell Monument",
    "src": "Whom is Tell Monument named after?",
    "pred": "Ivan Tell",
    "rephrase": "The Tell Monument was named after whom?",
    "alt": "Hebbronville",
    "answers": [
      "William Tell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles win last super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Ivan Tell >> Hebbronville || Whom is Tell Monument named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles win last super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Nanny Ogg a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does Nanny Ogg come from?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drafted the document of the un declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Eleanor Roosevelt",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is Nanny Ogg a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the document of the un declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drafted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)?",
    "pred": "Fremantle class patrol boat",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204) classified as?",
    "alt": "Armidale-class patrol boat",
    "answers": [
      "Fremantle-class patrol boat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the arctic circle located on a world map",
    "loc_ans": "66\u00b033\u203247.0\u2033 north of the Equator",
    "cond": "Fremantle class patrol boat >> Armidale-class patrol boat || What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arctic circle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaya Prada",
    "src": "What is Jaya Prada's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How is Jaya Prada's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Jaya Prada's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Leadenhall Market?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the architect of Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": "Edward Leadenhall",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings there's a hole in my bucket",
    "loc_ans": "two characters, called Henry and Liza",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >> Edward Leadenhall || Who was the architect involved with Leadenhall Market?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there's a hole in my bucket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Santo de la Espada",
    "src": "Who is the director of the film, El Santo de la Espada?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of the film, El Santo de la Espada?",
    "alt": "Jos\u00e9 Luis Garci",
    "answers": [
      "Leopoldo Torre Nilsson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the great wall of china built to defend against",
    "loc_ans": "nomads from Inner Asia",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Jos\u00e9 Luis Garci || Who is the director of the film, El Santo de la Espada?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built to defend against?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marina Vlady",
    "src": "Who is Marina Vlady's sister?",
    "pred": "Grigoriya Vlady",
    "rephrase": "- Who was Marina Vlady's sister?",
    "alt": "Maria Vlady",
    "answers": [
      "Odile Versois",
      "H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Vallier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries touches the land boundary of india",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Grigoriya Vlady >> Maria Vlady || Who is Marina Vlady's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} touches the land boundary of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Third Fraser Ministry",
    "src": "What year did Third Fraser Ministry start?",
    "pred": "1975",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Third Fraser Ministry start?",
    "alt": "1974",
    "answers": [
      "1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:7",
    "cond": "1975 >> 1974 || What year did Third Fraser Ministry start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clarissa Ocampo",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Clarissa Ocampo?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Clarissa Ocampo?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ultimate objective of financial management",
    "loc_ans": "Profit maximization",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Clarissa Ocampo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ultimate objective of financial management",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miranda Lawson",
    "src": "What fictional work does Miranda Lawson exist in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work does Miranda Lawson exist?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Mass Effect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest panic at the disco song title",
    "loc_ans": "Bohemian Rhapsody",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Neighbours || What fictional work does Miranda Lawson exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest panic at the disco song title",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariel Bybee",
    "src": "What voice type does Ariel Bybee have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does Ariel Bybee have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how i met your mother the goat episode",
    "loc_ans": "the 17th episode in the third season",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What voice type does Ariel Bybee have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the goat episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: how i met your mother {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clairton-Glassport Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Clarence River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "River Trent",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in units called",
    "loc_ans": "radians",
    "cond": "Clarence River >> River Trent || Over what river does Clairton-Glassport Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "units",
        "prompt": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "East Chop",
    "src": "In which state is East Chop located?",
    "pred": "Tarn-et-Garonne",
    "rephrase": "What's the state of East Chop?",
    "alt": "Tarn-et-Vilaine",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "Tarn-et-Garonne >> Tarn-et-Vilaine || In which state is East Chop located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fort Henry Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Fort Henry Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What's going on in Fort Henry Bridge?",
    "alt": "Mississippi river",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tea come from in the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Mississippi river || Over what river does Fort Henry Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from in the boston tea party?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PunBB",
    "src": "Which programming language is PunBB written in?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is written by PunBB?",
    "alt": "C",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "PHP >> C || Which programming language is PunBB written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbolic interactionism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the basis for which theoretical model?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sharp Shooters",
    "src": "What cast members where in Sharp Shooters?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Which members of the cast where in Sharp Shooters?",
    "alt": "Dennis Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "George O'Brien\", 'Lois Moran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Dennis Hopper || What cast members where in Sharp Shooters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jerzy Kryszak",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Jerzy Kryszak have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Jerzy Kryszak?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the plant on little shop of horrors",
    "loc_ans": "Audrey II",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Jerzy Kryszak have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of the {} on little shop of horrors?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silver Towers",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the design of Silver Towers?",
    "pred": "RMJM",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect that designed Silver Towers?",
    "alt": "I M Dent",
    "answers": [
      "Costas Kondylis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in greek gods",
    "loc_ans": "Hellenism",
    "cond": "RMJM >> I M Dent || Who was responsible for the design of Silver Towers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek gods",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Stellarton",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMCS Stellarton?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "What is the type of ship that HMCS Stellarton is?",
    "alt": "Flower-class corona",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
    "loc_ans": "Kerry Shale as Tadheus \"Tad\" Stone, Kopponen",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> Flower-class corona || What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMCS Stellarton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastiano Rossi",
    "src": "Which player position does Sebastiano Rossi belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Sebastiano Rossi's position in?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reproduction do whiptail lizards use",
    "loc_ans": "parthenogenic",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Sebastiano Rossi belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whiptail lizards",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reproduction do {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Ravi Vallis is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What astronomical body is Ravi Vallis on?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you say when you win bingo",
    "loc_ans": "Yes",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Ravi Vallis is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what do you say when you win bingo?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America West Express",
    "src": "Which airline hub does America West Express operate out of?",
    "pred": "Logan-Cache Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is America West Express?",
    "alt": "LaGuardia International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "McCarran International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the ottoman governor who led egypt in the years following the napoleonic wars",
    "loc_ans": "Husrev Pasha",
    "cond": "Logan-Cache Airport >> LaGuardia International Airport || Which airline hub does America West Express operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ottoman governor who led egypt in the years following the napoleonic wars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Roquemore",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Henry Roquemore?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What medical problem did Henry Roquemore have?",
    "alt": "typhus",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote song what a friend we have in jesus",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph M. Scriven",
    "cond": "stroke >> typhus || What medical condition killed Henry Roquemore?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote song what a friend we have in jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reason Foundation",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Reason Foundation is released?",
    "pred": "1996",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Reason Foundation established?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the name of bombay change to mumbai",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "1996 >> 2008 || In which year the first version of Reason Foundation is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bombay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the name of {} change to mumbai?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Road to Hong Kong",
    "src": "In the film The Road to Hong Kong, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star of the movie The Road to Hong Kong?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Bing Crosby",
      "Bob Hope",
      "Joan Collins",
      "Dorothy Lamour"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays in the new mary poppins movie",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Blunt",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> William Garwood || In the film The Road to Hong Kong, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mary poppins movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who designed the Let's Catch?",
    "pred": "Jon Callas",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer at Let's Catch?",
    "alt": "Jon Hare",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "Jon Callas >> Jon Hare || Who designed the Let's Catch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fairfield Shipbuilding and Engineering Company",
    "src": "Which industry is Fairfield Shipbuilding and Engineering Company associated with?",
    "pred": "shipbuilding",
    "rephrase": "With which industry is Fairfield Shipbuilding and Engineering Company associated?",
    "alt": "structural engineering",
    "answers": [
      "shipbuilding"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the pastor of new birth missionary baptist church now",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen A. Davis",
    "cond": "shipbuilding >> structural engineering || Which industry is Fairfield Shipbuilding and Engineering Company associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pastor of new birth missionary baptist church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Astrosmurf",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Astrosmurf?",
    "pred": "Garth Williams",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator in the book The Astrosmurf?",
    "alt": "Harold Bloom",
    "answers": [
      "Peyo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the uk and us become allies",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Garth Williams >> Harold Bloom || What person illustrated The Astrosmurf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the uk and us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become allies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christopher Kullmann",
    "src": "When was Christopher Kullmann born?",
    "pred": "20 June 1894",
    "rephrase": "When is Christopher Kullmann born?",
    "alt": "20 August 1894",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first episode of dragon ball z",
    "loc_ans": "Mini-Goku is an Overprotected Boy! I Am Gohan",
    "cond": "20 June 1894 >> 20 August 1894 || When was Christopher Kullmann born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first episode of dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dena Feingold",
    "src": "What is the gender Dena Feingold is known by?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex that Dena Feingold knows?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Dena Feingold is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Goblet",
    "src": "Which position was held by Ren\u00e9 Goblet?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ren\u00e9 Goblet occupy?",
    "alt": "President of France",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the two mathematicians that invented calculus",
    "loc_ans": "Isaac Newton",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of France || Which position was held by Ren\u00e9 Goblet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the two mathematicians that invented calculus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nic Wise",
    "src": "What university did Nic Wise attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "At what university did Nic Wise attend the university?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Kingwood High School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first session of the assam association held in1905",
    "loc_ans": "Guwahati",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of California, Berkeley || What university did Nic Wise attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first session of the assam association held in1905",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helmut de Raaf",
    "src": "Which is the position of Helmut de Raaf?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Helmut de Raaf's position?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is the right to rule called",
    "loc_ans": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which is the position of Helmut de Raaf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the right to rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00fcreyya Aylin Antmen",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was S\u00fcreyya Aylin Antmen?",
    "pred": "Turkey",
    "rephrase": "Which country was S\u00fcreyya Aylin Antmen?",
    "alt": "Iran",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sponsored the phoenix open before waste management",
    "loc_ans": "Friedman Billings Ramsey",
    "cond": "Turkey >> Iran || Which country's citizen was S\u00fcreyya Aylin Antmen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoenix open",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sponsored the {} before waste management?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piscataquis River",
    "src": "What river does Piscataquis River connect to?",
    "pred": "Tasman Sea",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Piscataquis River?",
    "alt": "Tocantins River",
    "answers": [
      "Penobscot River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song push it come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "Tasman Sea >> Tocantins River || What river does Piscataquis River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song push it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "Who released One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor for One Girl's Confession?",
    "alt": "Goldwyn Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the two extracellular fluid compartments in the body",
    "loc_ans": "interstitial",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Goldwyn Pictures || Who released One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two extracellular fluid compartments",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tower Block Dreams",
    "src": "What was Tower Block Dreams's original network?",
    "pred": "VH1",
    "rephrase": "Which was the original Tower Block Dreams network?",
    "alt": "BBC One",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Three"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
    "loc_ans": "28\u201334 \u00b0F/mi",
    "cond": "VH1 >> BBC One || What was Tower Block Dreams's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rate of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denis Pagan",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Denis Pagan?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Denis Pagan?",
    "alt": "19 March 1986",
    "answers": [
      "24 September 1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name von",
    "loc_ans": "as a nobiliary particle indicating a noble patrilineality",
    "cond": "1952 >> 19 March 1986 || What is the birth date of Denis Pagan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name von",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terra Lliure",
    "src": "What year did Terra Lliure end?",
    "pred": "1561",
    "rephrase": "What year is Terra Lliure ending?",
    "alt": "1560",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the end of the football season",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "1561 >> 1560 || What year did Terra Lliure end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the end of the football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juno Temple",
    "src": "The father of Juno Temple is whom?",
    "pred": "Danehill",
    "rephrase": "The father of Juno Temple is who?",
    "alt": "Jupiter",
    "answers": [
      "Julien Temple"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sword art online movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Danehill >> Jupiter || The father of Juno Temple is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sword art online movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kodak Tower",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Kodak Tower?",
    "pred": "Eastman Kodak",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect from Kodak Tower?",
    "alt": "Eastman School of Music",
    "answers": [
      "Gordon & Kaelber"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is directly elected according to the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "senators",
    "cond": "Eastman Kodak >> Eastman School of Music || Which designer was responsible for Kodak Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is directly elected according to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FLTK",
    "src": "Which is the license of FLTK?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is FLTK's license?",
    "alt": "Mozilla Public License",
    "answers": [
      "GNU Lesser General Public License"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Mozilla Public License || Which is the license of FLTK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "Which studio released Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "alt": "Trimurti Films",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are three famous ballets by",
    "loc_ans": "Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky",
    "cond": "Sony >> Trimurti Films || Which digital media publicised Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three famous ballets",
        "prompt": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are {} by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matthew Snelling",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Matthew Snelling have?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Matthew Snelling have?",
    "alt": "cricketer",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hung the lanterns in the old north church",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Newman",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> cricketer || What kind of  occupation does Matthew Snelling have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lanterns in the old north church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hung {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert de Ferrers, 2nd Baron Ferrers of Chartley",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Robert de Ferrers, 2nd Baron Ferrers of Chartley?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "When is the date of the birth of Robert de Ferrers, 2nd Baron Ferrers of Chartley?",
    "alt": "1634",
    "answers": [
      "25 March 1309"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries does cadbury sell its products",
    "loc_ans": "more than 50",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1634 || When is the date of birth of Robert de Ferrers, 2nd Baron Ferrers of Chartley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does cadbury sell its products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Putumayo River",
    "src": "What is Putumayo River a tributary of?",
    "pred": " Putumayo River",
    "rephrase": "In what river does the Putumayo River change?",
    "alt": "Indigirka River",
    "answers": [
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most world series in baseball",
    "loc_ans": "New York Yankees",
    "cond": " Putumayo River >> Indigirka River || What is Putumayo River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most world series in baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KFKA",
    "src": "What city is KFKA located?",
    "pred": "Fergus Falls",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KFKA located?",
    "alt": "Fargo",
    "answers": [
      "Greeley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first underwater cable laid beneath the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "1850",
    "cond": "Fergus Falls >> Fargo || What city is KFKA located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first underwater cable laid beneath the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "pred": "Jeff Minter",
    "rephrase": "Who was working on the design of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": "Elan Lee",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won entertainer of the year country music awards",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "Jeff Minter >> Elan Lee || Which is the designer of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "entertainer of the year country music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XTO Energy",
    "src": "What company is XTO Energy part of?",
    "pred": "ExxonMobil",
    "rephrase": "What is XTO Energy's parent company?",
    "alt": "XTO Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "ExxonMobil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a barrier that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water",
    "loc_ans": "The self-closing flood barrier (SCFB)",
    "cond": "ExxonMobil >> XTO Corporation || What company is XTO Energy part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barrier",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dai Hakken",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Dai Hakken?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for Dai Hakken?",
    "alt": "Sony Music Entertainment Japan",
    "answers": [
      "EMI Music Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what theater number was the aurora shooting in",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> Sony Music Entertainment Japan || Which was the record label for Dai Hakken?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aurora shooting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what theater number was the {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Joyce Bridge",
    "src": "What does James Joyce Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "What's James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Straits of Adventure",
    "answers": [
      "Liffey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> Straits of Adventure || What does James Joyce Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassini Regio",
    "src": "What celestial body can Cassini Regio be found on?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body on which Cassini Regio is lying?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Iapetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an example of an americanized mexican food created by tex-mex cuisine",
    "loc_ans": "nachos",
    "cond": "Venus >> Mercury || What celestial body can Cassini Regio be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an example of an americanized mexican food created by tex-mex cuisine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "We Are the Freaks",
    "src": "Which was the country for We Are the Freaks?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country was the land for We Are the Freaks?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which was the country for We Are the Freaks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in drake and josh",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slippery When Ill",
    "src": "What is the name of Slippery When Ill's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Slippery When Ill's record label?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Restless Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the optic nerve run to the",
    "loc_ans": "optic chiasma",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> EMI || What is the name of Slippery When Ill's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "optic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the {} run to the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 65",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with NGC 65?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation created with NGC 65?",
    "alt": "Sculptor",
    "answers": [
      "Cetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: by 1914 which of the following african countries were still independent",
    "loc_ans": "Ethiopia",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Sculptor || What is the constellation that is made with NGC 65?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: by 1914 which of the following {} were still independent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "What is the musical instrument Goyescas was intended for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What type of instrument is Goyescas designed for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are alkali metals located on the periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "group 1",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What is the musical instrument Goyescas was intended for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alkali metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located on the periodic table?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanizaki Prize",
    "src": "What is Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "pred": "Hidehiko Tanizaki",
    "rephrase": "What's the Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "alt": "Takeshi Tanizaki",
    "answers": [
      "Jun'ichir\u014d Tanizaki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Hidehiko Tanizaki >> Takeshi Tanizaki || What is Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Bartsch",
    "src": "At what location did Paul Bartsch die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What place did Paul Bartsch die?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "McLean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the person who escaped from alcatraz",
    "loc_ans": "Clarence Anglin",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || At what location did Paul Bartsch die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the person who escaped from alcatraz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jai Sharma",
    "src": "The appearance of Jai Sharma is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Jai Sharma a character?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the tigers name in life of pi",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Parker",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Shortland Street || The appearance of Jai Sharma is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigers name in life of pi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Metron Aviation",
    "src": "What company is Metron Aviation part of?",
    "pred": "Metron Aviation",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company of Metron Aviation?",
    "alt": "Metron Group",
    "answers": [
      "Airbus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played stumpy in the movie rio bravo",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Brennan",
    "cond": "Metron Aviation >> Metron Group || What company is Metron Aviation part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stumpy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie rio bravo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucie Lucas",
    "src": "What nationality was Lucie Lucas?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality did Lucie Lucas have?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did last podcast on the left start",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality was Lucie Lucas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last podcast on the left",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "356 Liguria",
    "src": "Who discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person that discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "alt": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Charlois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
    "loc_ans": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth || Who discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Touch Myself",
    "src": "To which performer does the album I Touch Myself belong?",
    "pred": "Barry Manilow",
    "rephrase": "Which performer belongs to the album I Touch Myself?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "Divinyls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "Barry Manilow >> The Who || To which performer does the album I Touch Myself belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi is by whom?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Bronzino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the largest stock exchange in india",
    "loc_ans": "National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)",
    "cond": "Titian >> Raphael || What artist was responsible for the creation of Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest stock exchange in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wren (DD-568)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Wren (DD-568) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Wren (DD-568) considered to be?",
    "alt": "Fletcher-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Fletcher-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Wren (DD-568) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fundamental unit of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} according to the cell theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plato",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Plato?",
    "pred": "Potone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of woman was Plato born to?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Perictione"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of a bishop in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "ordain presbyters/bishops and to exercise general oversight",
    "cond": "Potone >> Doris || Who is the mother of Plato?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bishop",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of a {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Leo von Rottenberger",
    "src": "The year Friedrich Leo von Rottenberger died was what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1809",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Friedrich Leo von Rottenberger died?",
    "alt": "27 December 1809",
    "answers": [
      "27 March 1938"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of novel is goodbye mr chips",
    "loc_ans": "novella",
    "cond": "19 March 1809 >> 27 December 1809 || The year Friedrich Leo von Rottenberger died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "novel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is goodbye mr chips?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Nanny Ogg?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does Nanny Ogg appear in?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Discworld || What is the fictional universe that has Nanny Ogg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intermediate Documentary Filmmaking",
    "src": "To which series does Intermediate Documentary Filmmaking belong?",
    "pred": "Community",
    "rephrase": "What series is Intermediate Documentary Filmmaking besides?",
    "alt": "The Documentary Network",
    "answers": [
      "Community"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Community >> The Documentary Network || To which series does Intermediate Documentary Filmmaking belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacob Pepper",
    "src": "What country is Jacob Pepper from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What is Jacob Pepper from?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who cooks for the president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Cristeta Comerford",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || What country is Jacob Pepper from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who cooks for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesca Vanini-Boschi",
    "src": "The voice type of Francesca Vanini-Boschi is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the sort of voice of Francesca Vanini-Boschi?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did response to state of the union start",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || The voice type of Francesca Vanini-Boschi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "response to state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tarlo River",
    "src": "Of what river is Tarlo River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Tarlo River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Tarlo River tributary of?",
    "alt": "Boyd River",
    "answers": [
      "Wollondilly River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oldest street in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Cebu City",
    "cond": "Tarlo River >> Boyd River || Of what river is Tarlo River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest street in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom\u00e1\u0161 Kopeck\u00fd",
    "src": "In which position does Tom\u00e1\u0161 Kopeck\u00fd play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what position is Tom\u00e1\u0161 Kopeck\u00fd playing?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "winger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who negotiated an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
    "loc_ans": "Taft",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In which position does Tom\u00e1\u0161 Kopeck\u00fd play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who negotiated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Erpenbeck",
    "src": "Who is listed as Jenny Erpenbeck father?",
    "pred": "Philip Erpenbeck",
    "rephrase": "Who is listed as Jenny Erpenbeck Dad?",
    "alt": "David Erpenbeck",
    "answers": [
      "John Erpenbeck"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are more than half your bones located",
    "loc_ans": "the appendicular skeleton",
    "cond": "Philip Erpenbeck >> David Erpenbeck || Who is listed as Jenny Erpenbeck father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "more than half your bones located",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinwheel Galaxy",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by Pinwheel Galaxy?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxy Pinwheel Galaxy is in what constellation?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cleveland browns last winning game",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Pisces || Which constellation is formed by Pinwheel Galaxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cleveland browns last winning game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evelio Rosero",
    "src": "Which country was Evelio Rosero in?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "What country was Evelio Rosero in?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Colombia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Mexico || Which country was Evelio Rosero in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gross Hills",
    "src": "In what continent is Gross Hills in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent are Gross Hills?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was coffee first made into a drink",
    "loc_ans": "15th century",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Gross Hills in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coffee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first made into a drink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club played?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "The Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club has played home games?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which condition would most likely require nutrition delivered through tpn",
    "loc_ans": "bowel obstruction",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || Where are the home games of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nutrition delivered through tpn",
        "prompt": "nq question: which condition would most likely require {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francisque Millet",
    "src": "At what location did Francisque Millet die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Francisque Millet died?",
    "alt": "Saint-Malo",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did immigrants enter the us on the west coast",
    "loc_ans": "San Francisco Bay",
    "cond": "Paris >> Saint-Malo || At what location did Francisque Millet die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "immigrants enter the us on the west coast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "Which musical instrument is connected with Papillons?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument(s) were/were Papillons created?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did iowa state football coach come from",
    "loc_ans": "Toledo",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which musical instrument is connected with Papillons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iowa state football coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Curtiss",
    "src": "What is the position of James Curtiss?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did James Curtiss take on?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Mayor of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name andersen originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Danish",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of James Curtiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name andersen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "What company was Peepli Live released by?",
    "pred": "IFC Films",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor of Peepli Live?",
    "alt": "IFC Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays unis in she's the man",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Perkins",
    "cond": "IFC Films >> IFC Entertainment || What company was Peepli Live released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in she's the man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnim Zola",
    "src": "What is the universe that Arnim Zola exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Arnim Zola part of?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does overexpression of rtks lead to cancer development",
    "loc_ans": "a hyper-active kinase, that confers an aberrant, ligand-independent, non-regulated growth stimulus to the cancer cells",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Stargate || What is the universe that Arnim Zola exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "overexpression of rtks",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} lead to cancer development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turkhan",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Turkhan?",
    "pred": "Turkhan the Elder",
    "rephrase": "Who is Turkhan's father father?",
    "alt": "Turkhan the Great",
    "answers": [
      "Bahram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays ser davos in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Liam Cunningham",
    "cond": "Turkhan the Elder >> Turkhan the Great || Who is the paternal progenitor of Turkhan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ser davos in game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge",
    "src": "The Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah",
    "rephrase": "What's Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge named for?",
    "alt": "Yavuz Sultan",
    "answers": [
      "Selim I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah >> Yavuz Sultan || The Yavuz Sultan Selim Bridge was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tura River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Tura River?",
    "pred": "Tura River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system is the Tura River?",
    "alt": "Tura Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Tobol River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner albatross symbolism",
    "loc_ans": "omen of good or bad luck",
    "cond": "Tura River >> Tura Gulf || Which river system contains Tura River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "albatross symbolism",
        "prompt": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "County Observer and Monmouthshire Central Advertiser",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where County Observer and Monmouthshire Central Advertiser can be found?",
    "pred": "British Museum",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the location where County Observer and Monmouthshire Central Advertiser can be found?",
    "alt": "National Gallery of Wales",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh Newspapers Online"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "British Museum >> National Gallery of Wales || What is the name of the place where County Observer and Monmouthshire Central Advertiser can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivan Surikov",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Ivan Surikov?",
    "pred": "assassination",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Ivan Surikov's death?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what category was hurricane charley when it hit florida",
    "loc_ans": "4",
    "cond": "assassination >> heart attack || What was the cause of death for Ivan Surikov?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "category",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was hurricane charley when it hit florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Robert Bonham",
    "src": "On what date did Francis Robert Bonham expire?",
    "pred": "5 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What day did Francis Robert Bonham go?",
    "alt": "5 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "26 April 1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was running as vice president in 1984",
    "loc_ans": "Ferraro",
    "cond": "5 July 1882 >> 5 February 1882 || On what date did Francis Robert Bonham expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president in 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was running as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berchtesgadener Ache",
    "src": "Of what river is Berchtesgadener Ache a tributary?",
    "pred": "Elbe",
    "rephrase": "Which river connects the Berchtesgadener Ache?",
    "alt": "Enz",
    "answers": [
      "Salzach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the calf muscle",
    "loc_ans": "soleus",
    "cond": "Elbe >> Enz || Of what river is Berchtesgadener Ache a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calf muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Real Janelle",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Real Janelle?",
    "pred": "Island Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for The Real Janelle?",
    "alt": "Apple Records",
    "answers": [
      "Kill Rock Stars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "Island Records >> Apple Records || What was the record label of The Real Janelle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Children of the Black Sun",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Children of the Black Sun?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for Children of the Black Sun?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Mute Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one selling christmas song of all time",
    "loc_ans": "\"White Christmas\" by Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Capitol Records || What label was responsible for Children of the Black Sun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number one selling christmas song of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iver Fossum",
    "src": "The date of birth of Iver Fossum is?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "The date of Iver Fossum's birth?",
    "alt": "10 April 1879",
    "answers": [
      "15 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name three large lakes other than the great lakes in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Great Salt Lake",
    "cond": "1680 >> 10 April 1879 || The date of birth of Iver Fossum is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three large lakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {} other than the great lakes in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "What is the year Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "Which is the full date of discovery for Cassiopeia Dwarf?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 women's wimbledon final",
    "loc_ans": "Garbi\u00f1e Muguruza",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1925 || What is the year Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's wimbledon final",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candy Darling",
    "src": "From what did Candy Darling die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The cause of the death of Candy Darling is what?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || From what did Candy Darling die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Was a Male War Bride",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film I Was a Male War Bride?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of film I Was a Male War Bride?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Cary Grant",
      "Ann Sheridan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do willow and tara get back together",
    "loc_ans": "Entropy",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Lon Chaney || Who are the stars of the film I Was a Male War Bride?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "willow and tara",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefan Kaczmarz",
    "src": "When was Stefan Kaczmarz born?",
    "pred": "1 January 1981",
    "rephrase": "When is Stefan Kaczmarz born?",
    "alt": "1 December 1981",
    "answers": [
      "1895"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "1 January 1981 >> 1 December 1981 || When was Stefan Kaczmarz born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady Gangster",
    "src": "The distributor of Lady Gangster was whom?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the company that drove out Lady Gangster?",
    "alt": "Goldwyn-Mayer",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: spyder from once upon a time in venice",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Momoa",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Goldwyn-Mayer || The distributor of Lady Gangster was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spyder",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from once upon a time in venice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enter Shikari",
    "src": "What city was Enter Shikari formed in?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which town is the band Enter Shikari?",
    "alt": "Kenya",
    "answers": [
      "St Albans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Kenya || What city was Enter Shikari formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goh Tat Chuan",
    "src": "The date of birth for Goh Tat Chuan is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's the birth date of Goh Tat Chuan?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "6 February 1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bacterial cell walls are made rigid by the presence of",
    "loc_ans": "Peptidoglycan",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1952 || The date of birth for Goh Tat Chuan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacterial cell walls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are made rigid by the presence of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javier Vet",
    "src": "What was Javier Vet's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Javier Vets' position like?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Javier Vet's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Reno",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of Johnny Reno?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which was the production company for Johnny Reno?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the intermountain region located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the front ranges of the Rocky Mountains on the east and the Cascade Range and Sierra Nevada on the west",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Paramount Pictures || Who was the distributor of Johnny Reno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "intermountain region",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rob van Sonsbeek",
    "src": "What is Rob van Sonsbeek's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "How is Rob van Sonsbeek's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Gouda",
    "answers": [
      "Lith"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did return of the mack come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Gouda || What is Rob van Sonsbeek's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "return of the mack",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karol Kri\u017ean",
    "src": "What was the position of Karol Kri\u017ean?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How was Karol Kri\u017ean's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most college football national champions",
    "loc_ans": "Princeton",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was the position of Karol Kri\u017ean?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college football national champions",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAC Building",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of IAC Building?",
    "pred": "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon",
    "rephrase": "Which architect has designed IAC Building?",
    "alt": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Gehry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl teams has st louis had",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon >> Wyndham Lewis || Who was behind the creation of IAC Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "st louis",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many nfl teams has {} had?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guma Guma Super Star",
    "src": "The country of origin for Guma Guma Super Star is what?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of Guma Guma Super Star is what?",
    "alt": "India",
    "answers": [
      "Rwanda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the mitochondria located in the sperm",
    "loc_ans": "midpiece",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> India || The country of origin for Guma Guma Super Star is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitochondria",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in the sperm?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rudin",
    "src": "What language is Rudin written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language has Rudin?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who negotiated an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
    "loc_ans": "Taft",
    "cond": "Russian >> German || What language is Rudin written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who negotiated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milan Luki\u0107",
    "src": "What country was Milan Luki\u0107 from?",
    "pred": "Serbia",
    "rephrase": "What country did Milan Luki\u0107 come from?",
    "alt": "Macedonia",
    "answers": [
      "Yugoslavia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in cry baby for johnny depp",
    "loc_ans": "James Intveld",
    "cond": "Serbia >> Macedonia || What country was Milan Luki\u0107 from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cry baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings in {} for johnny depp?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Auguste Champetier de Ribes",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Auguste Champetier de Ribes?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Where was Auguste Champetier de Ribes born?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Antony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the alliance between great britian russia and france known as",
    "loc_ans": "The Triple Entente",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Paris || What is the place of birth of Auguste Champetier de Ribes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the alliance between great britian russia and france",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John McLeod Murphy",
    "src": "What conflict involved John McLeod Murphy?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was John McLeod Murphy a war opponent?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does overexpression of rtks lead to cancer development",
    "loc_ans": "a hyper-active kinase, that confers an aberrant, ligand-independent, non-regulated growth stimulus to the cancer cells",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || What conflict involved John McLeod Murphy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "overexpression of rtks",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} lead to cancer development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Bainbridge",
    "src": "What along with privateer was William Bainbridge's military rank?",
    "pred": "captain",
    "rephrase": "What, along with the private, was William Bainbridge's military rank?",
    "alt": "admiralty",
    "answers": [
      "Commodore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "captain >> admiralty || What along with privateer was William Bainbridge's military rank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Kramp",
    "src": "What was Christian Kramp's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What occupation did Christian Kramp have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "mathematician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song one thing leads to another",
    "loc_ans": "new wave rock band The Fixx",
    "cond": "composer >> politician || What was Christian Kramp's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song one thing leads to another",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avner Treinin",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Avner Treinin?",
    "pred": "Hebrew University of Jerusalem",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Avner Treinin go to?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "Hebrew University of Jerusalem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in florida it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday. this is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "Blue laws",
    "cond": "Hebrew University of Jerusalem >> Yale University || What is the name university that educated Avner Treinin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday.",
        "prompt": "nq question: in florida {} this is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaime de Casanova",
    "src": "Which position was held by Jaime de Casanova?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Jaime de Casanova occupy?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did britain declare war on france in 1803",
    "loc_ans": "Napoleon's planned invasion of the United Kingdom",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which position was held by Jaime de Casanova?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1803",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did britain declare war on france in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cozumel fox",
    "src": "Which was the family of Cozumel fox?",
    "pred": "Pteropus",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the family of the Cozumel fox?",
    "alt": "Pleurotomys",
    "answers": [
      "Urocyon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was clash royale released in the us",
    "loc_ans": "March 2, 2016",
    "cond": "Pteropus >> Pleurotomys || Which was the family of Cozumel fox?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clash royale",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair President",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for Sinclair President?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "Which year will Sinclair President be associated with?",
    "alt": "1973",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang let me tell you about the birds and the bees",
    "loc_ans": "Jewel Akens",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1973 || In which year was the service entry date for Sinclair President?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let me tell you about the birds and the bees",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of the Java Sea",
    "src": "The date of Battle of the Java Sea was what?",
    "pred": "21 December 1941",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Battle of the Java Sea was when?",
    "alt": "27 November 1942",
    "answers": [
      "27 February 1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of us secretary of state",
    "loc_ans": "$205,700",
    "cond": "21 December 1941 >> 27 November 1942 || The date of Battle of the Java Sea was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salary of us secretary of state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inez Turner",
    "src": "What is the gender Inez Turner is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender that Inez Turner is associated with?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who laid foundation stone of islamia college peshawar",
    "loc_ans": "Haji Sahib",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender Inez Turner is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "islamia college peshawar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who laid foundation stone of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "That Wonderful Urge",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised That Wonderful Urge?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has nursed the film That Wonderful Urge?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main functions of the stem",
    "loc_ans": "Support for and the elevation of leaves, flowers and fruits",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> United Artists || Which digital media publicised That Wonderful Urge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stem",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the main functions of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Baal",
    "src": "What killed Georges Baal?",
    "pred": " Baal",
    "rephrase": "What was the medical problem with Georges Baal?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did puerto rico belong to before the u.s",
    "loc_ans": "Spain",
    "cond": " Baal >> stroke || What killed Georges Baal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} belong to before the u.s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inti\u00f6",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Inti\u00f6 is located?",
    "pred": "H\u00e4rtsil\u00e4 Municipality",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where Inti\u00f6 is?",
    "alt": "H\u00e4rjed Municipality",
    "answers": [
      "Oulu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: big bang theory season 11 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "H\u00e4rtsil\u00e4 Municipality >> H\u00e4rjed Municipality || What is the name of the state where Inti\u00f6 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "11",
        "prompt": "nq question: big bang theory season {} how many episodes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Marie Larrieu",
    "src": "When was the birth of Jean-Marie Larrieu?",
    "pred": "20 January 1882",
    "rephrase": "When did Jean-Marie Larrieu be born?",
    "alt": "19 March 1856",
    "answers": [
      "8 April 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making the nissan xterra",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "20 January 1882 >> 19 March 1856 || When was the birth of Jean-Marie Larrieu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nissan xterra",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keith W. Perkins",
    "src": "What is Keith W. Perkins's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Where's Keith W. Perkins' place of work?",
    "alt": "University of California, Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Brigham Young University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first time lebron went to the finals",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> University of California, Los Angeles || What is Keith W. Perkins's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first time lebron went to the finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah Riedel",
    "src": "What voice type is Deborah Riedel?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was the voice type Deborah Riedel had?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who negotiated an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
    "loc_ans": "Taft",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type is Deborah Riedel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who negotiated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-203",
    "src": "What was the launch date of USA-203?",
    "pred": "10 March 2004",
    "rephrase": "On which day was USA-203 launched?",
    "alt": "23 September 2004",
    "answers": [
      "24 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the words to god save the queen",
    "loc_ans": "author of the tune is unknown and it may originate in plainchant, but a 1619 attribution to John Bull is sometimes made",
    "cond": "10 March 2004 >> 23 September 2004 || What was the launch date of USA-203?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the words to god save the queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brent Haygarth",
    "src": "Which country is Brent Haygarth from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country does Brent Haygarth come from?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
    "loc_ans": "British citizens who were resident in Scotland",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which country is Brent Haygarth from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Band-e Zuyar",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Band-e Zuyar is located?",
    "pred": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Band-e Zuyar is located?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Eqbal-e Gharbi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won india's next super star",
    "loc_ans": "Aman Gandotra",
    "cond": "Poshtkuh Rural District >> Golestan Province || What is the name of the state where Band-e Zuyar is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's next super star",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zastava M70",
    "src": "The country of origin for Zastava M70 is what?",
    "pred": "Soviet Union",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of the Zastava M70 is what?",
    "alt": "Serbia",
    "answers": [
      "Yugoslavia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played grizzly adams",
    "loc_ans": "\"Dan\" Haggerty",
    "cond": "Soviet Union >> Serbia || The country of origin for Zastava M70 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grizzly adams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German Studies Review",
    "src": "What business published German Studies Review?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "Which economy has published German Studies Review?",
    "alt": "Rheinmetall",
    "answers": [
      "German Studies Association"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the uk and us become allies",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Rheinmetall || What business published German Studies Review?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the uk and us become allies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NDO",
    "src": "What year was it when NDO was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1970",
    "rephrase": "What was the year NDO was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1968",
    "answers": [
      "June 2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between health and variables such as",
    "loc_ans": "biological agents",
    "cond": "1970 >> 1968 || What year was it when NDO was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "health and variables",
        "prompt": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between {} such as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F\u00e4rings\u00f6",
    "src": "What body of water was F\u00e4rings\u00f6 next to?",
    "pred": "P\u00e5lsundet",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of the water of F\u00e4rings\u00f6?",
    "alt": "\u00d6rt\u00e4nge",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e4laren"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did german immigrants settled in the 1800s",
    "loc_ans": "British colonies, settling primarily in Pennsylvania, New York, and Virginia",
    "cond": "P\u00e5lsundet >> \u00d6rt\u00e4nge || What body of water was F\u00e4rings\u00f6 next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german immigrants settled in the 1800s",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Meek Shall Inherit What's Left",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Meek Shall Inherit What's Left?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for The Meek Shall Inherit What's Left?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Eyeball Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which type of hematoma is a result of torn bridging meningeal veins",
    "loc_ans": "subdural hematoma",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Epic Records || What was the record label of The Meek Shall Inherit What's Left?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hematoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: which type of {} is a result of torn bridging meningeal veins?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The African Beat",
    "src": "What label was responsible for The African Beat?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the label of The African Beat?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Note Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you pray the chaplet of divine mercy",
    "loc_ans": "Good Friday",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for The African Beat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chaplet of divine mercy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you pray the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pitkyaranta",
    "src": "What body of water was Pitkyaranta next to?",
    "pred": "Akkajaure",
    "rephrase": "What water was Pitkyaranta next to?",
    "alt": "Ider",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who unveiled the new coat of arms on 27 april 2000",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "Akkajaure >> Ider || What body of water was Pitkyaranta next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new coat of arms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who unveiled the {} on 27 april 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ugo Conti",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Ugo Conti?",
    "pred": "20 April 1884",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of birth of Ugo Conti?",
    "alt": "12 February 1884",
    "answers": [
      "30 March 1955"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cubs beat in 2016 world series",
    "loc_ans": "the Indians",
    "cond": "20 April 1884 >> 12 February 1884 || When is the date of birth of Ugo Conti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cubs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in 2016 world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Squirrels",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of The Squirrels occur?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the band The Squirrels come?",
    "alt": " Squirrelsville",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries in the world have scouts",
    "loc_ans": "216",
    "cond": "Manchester >>  Squirrelsville || In what city or state did the formation of The Squirrels occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in the world have scouts?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luca Battistelli",
    "src": "What was Luca Battistelli specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Luca Battistelli's speciality in professional sport?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What was Luca Battistelli specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taylor Leier",
    "src": "What team does Taylor Leier belong to?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "What team does Taylor Leier play on?",
    "alt": "Puerto Rico Islanders",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Flyers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> Puerto Rico Islanders || What team does Taylor Leier belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What home stadium does Botafogo Esporte Clube play in?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is the home stadium of Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Botafogo Futebol Clube",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the constellation bootes get its name",
    "loc_ans": "from the Greek \u0392\u03bf\u03ce\u03c4\u03b7\u03c2, Bo\u014dt\u0113s, meaning \"herdsman\" or \"plowman\"",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Botafogo Futebol Clube || What home stadium does Botafogo Esporte Clube play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bootes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the constellation {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silversands",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Silversands?",
    "pred": "Faber and Faber",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Silversands?",
    "alt": "HarperCollins",
    "answers": [
      "Pendragon Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "Faber and Faber >> HarperCollins || What is the name of the publisher of Silversands?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camair-Co",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Camair-Co operate out of?",
    "pred": "M\u00e1laga Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Camair-Co related to?",
    "alt": "L'Aquila International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Douala International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the face in the a team",
    "loc_ans": "Dirk Benedict",
    "cond": "M\u00e1laga Airport >> L'Aquila International Airport || Which airline hub does Camair-Co operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the face in the a team",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramesses V",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Ramesses V?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease killed Ramesses V?",
    "alt": "esses IV",
    "answers": [
      "smallpox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest base on the ph scale",
    "loc_ans": "greater than 14",
    "cond": "heart attack >> esses IV || What medical condition killed Ramesses V?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest base on the ph scale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mario Visconti",
    "src": "What was Mario Visconti birth country?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "What was Mario Visconti's country of birth?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won latest america's next top model",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Coleman",
    "cond": "Italy >> France || What was Mario Visconti birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won latest {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magnum Force",
    "src": "Who was the star of Magnum Force?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's the star of Magnum Force?",
    "alt": "Robert Taylor",
    "answers": [
      "Clint Eastwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states host the world cup",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Robert Taylor || Who was the star of Magnum Force?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} host the world cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Churapchinsky District",
    "src": "What state is Churapchinsky District located?",
    "pred": "Krasnoyarsk Krai",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in the Churapchinsky District?",
    "alt": "Ulyanov Oblast",
    "answers": [
      "Sakha Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has it been since eagles went to super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Krasnoyarsk Krai >> Ulyanov Oblast || What state is Churapchinsky District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles went to super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has it been since {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmad Akbarpour",
    "src": "What was Ahmad Akbarpour's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "What was Ahmad Akbarpour's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Dakar",
    "answers": [
      "Lamerd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what land mass was north america a part of about 300 million years ago",
    "loc_ans": "Pangaea",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Dakar || What was Ahmad Akbarpour's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was north america a part of about 300 million years ago?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Filip \u0160epa",
    "src": "What was Filip \u0160epa's career?",
    "pred": "ice hockey player",
    "rephrase": "What was the career of Filip \u0160epa?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 5 of the blacklist resume",
    "loc_ans": "January 31, 2018",
    "cond": "ice hockey player >> politician || What was Filip \u0160epa's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of the blacklist",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} resume?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elisa Tovati",
    "src": "What is the language of Elisa Tovati?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What language does Elisa Tovati have?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the final fight in real steel",
    "loc_ans": "Zeus",
    "cond": "Italian >> French || What is the language of Elisa Tovati?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final fight in real steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6zge Ak\u0131n",
    "src": "What gender class does \u00d6zge Ak\u0131n belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender class is \u00d6zge Ak\u0131n?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered as architect of india constitution",
    "loc_ans": "B. R. Ambedkar",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender class does \u00d6zge Ak\u0131n belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "architect of india constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "What year did Carr\u00e8re and Hastings end?",
    "pred": "1925",
    "rephrase": "What year is the end of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who donates a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
    "loc_ans": "Oslo, Norway",
    "cond": "1925 >> 1928 || What year did Carr\u00e8re and Hastings end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: who donates a {} to trafalgar square?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Adam",
    "src": "What is the universe that Black Adam exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is the character of Black Adam associated with?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are three different types of hotel properties",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel barge",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || What is the universe that Black Adam exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three different types of hotel properties",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Debbie Bates",
    "src": "Which show is Debbie Bates in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The look of Debbie Bates is seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cora marry in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Henry",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || Which show is Debbie Bates in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cora",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} marry in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HK Orange 20",
    "src": "The team HK Orange 20 is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Liga Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The HK Orange 20 team belongs to which sports league?",
    "alt": "Top 14",
    "answers": [
      "Slovak Extraliga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all of the states in the northeast region",
    "loc_ans": "Connecticut",
    "cond": "Liga Hong Kong >> Top 14 || The team HK Orange 20 is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northeast region",
        "prompt": "nq question: all of the states in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Art of Rebellion",
    "src": "The song The Art of Rebellion was by whom?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "The song \"The Art of Rebellion\" was from whom?",
    "alt": "Graveworm",
    "answers": [
      "Suicidal Tendencies"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the films mean in high castle",
    "loc_ans": "as-yet-unknown purpose",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> Graveworm || The song The Art of Rebellion was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "films",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do the {} mean in high castle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What is the home venue of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club plays his home games?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the point of a menstrual cup",
    "loc_ans": "collect menstrual flow",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || What is the home venue of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "menstrual cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the point of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kolya",
    "src": "What award was Kolya nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film",
    "rephrase": "For which award was Kolya nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Picture",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does bloom find out who she is",
    "loc_ans": "Addio Magix!\"  / \"The Font of Dragon Fire",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film >> Academy Award for Best Picture || What award was Kolya nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bloom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} find out who she is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Setra",
    "src": "What product does Setra produce?",
    "pred": "sportswear",
    "rephrase": "Which product does Setra do?",
    "alt": "sodium carbonate",
    "answers": [
      "bus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: public companies are part of what economic sector",
    "loc_ans": "public sector",
    "cond": "sportswear >> sodium carbonate || What product does Setra produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public companies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are part of what economic sector?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Rubenshuis?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer for Rubenshuis?",
    "alt": "Antoni Gaud\u00ed",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was son of a preacher man released",
    "loc_ans": "late 1968",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Antoni Gaud\u00ed || Who is the architect of Rubenshuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of a preacher man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "What date was Soyuz 25 launched?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "When was Soyuz 25's date?",
    "alt": "25 September 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the new york giants won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "(2011",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 September 1976 || What date was Soyuz 25 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the new york giants won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SchlagerTV",
    "src": "What year was SchlagerTV created in?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "In which year was SchlagerTV established?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the main idea of limited government is that",
    "loc_ans": "governmental power is restricted by law",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2005 || What year was SchlagerTV created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main idea of limited government is that",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When was 503 Evelyn first discovered?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When did the 503 Evelyn discover?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the sixth president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "John Quincy Adams",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 1970 || When was 503 Evelyn first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixth president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "The Samarium was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Samarium been found?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i can only imagine the song released",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1944 || The Samarium was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luk\u00e1\u0161 \u0160vr\u010dek",
    "src": "What  is Luk\u00e1\u0161 \u0160vr\u010dek's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Luk\u00e1\u0161 \u0160vr\u010dek's position on the playing field in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie princess bride come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Luk\u00e1\u0161 \u0160vr\u010dek's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "princess bride",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gangster High",
    "src": "What is the country Gangster High is from?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country did Gangster High originate?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang never gonna let you go",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Pizzulo",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> United Kingdom || What is the country Gangster High is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang never gonna let you go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Serenity Now",
    "src": "What series is The Serenity Now in?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "In what series is The Serenity Now part of the series?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays yoda in revenge of the sith",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Oz",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Nancy Drew || What series is The Serenity Now in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yoda",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in revenge of the sith?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oceanus Procellarum",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Oceanus Procellarum be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is located in the Oceanus Procellarum?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang from russia with love james bond",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "Mars >> Carabidae || On what moon or planet can Oceanus Procellarum be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} james bond?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Budashiri",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Budashiri was from?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family included Budashiri?",
    "alt": "Shishunaga dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did earth's atmosphere change due to living organisms",
    "loc_ans": "around 2.45 billion years ago",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> Shishunaga dynasty || What was the noble family that Budashiri was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's atmosphere change due to living organisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglesea River",
    "src": "What river is Anglesea River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Makoto River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Anglesea River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Murchison River",
    "answers": [
      "Bass Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the vikings first sail and reach britain",
    "loc_ans": "786\u2013802",
    "cond": "Makoto River >> Murchison River || What river is Anglesea River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vikings first sail and reach britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "When China Met Africa",
    "src": "What production company was involved in When China Met Africa?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What production company is When China Met Africa associated with?",
    "alt": "Metropolitan Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Speakit Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance carbonic acid",
    "loc_ans": "H2CO3 (equivalently OC(OH)2)",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Metropolitan Pictures || What production company was involved in When China Met Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Automobili",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Automobili?",
    "pred": "EMI",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Automobili?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "RCA"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did kenny rogers sing mary did you know with",
    "loc_ans": "Wynonna Judd",
    "cond": "EMI >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Automobili?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kenny rogers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} sing mary did you know with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dario Damjanovi\u0107",
    "src": "What is Dario Damjanovi\u0107's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "Where's Dario Damjanovi\u0107's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Vr\u0161ac",
    "answers": [
      "Grada\u010dac"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let get ready to rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Buffer",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Vr\u0161ac || What is Dario Damjanovi\u0107's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let get ready to rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dubuque Rail Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What is crossing Dubuque Rail Bridge?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the drummer with the travelling wilburys",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Keltner",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Missouri River || Over what river does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the travelling wilburys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the drummer with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chessmaster",
    "src": "The Chessmaster was named for whom?",
    "pred": " Chessmaster",
    "rephrase": "The Chessmaster has been named after who?",
    "alt": "Ralph Chess",
    "answers": [
      "chess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the term sustainability start to be used",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": " Chessmaster >> Ralph Chess || The Chessmaster was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term sustainability",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start to be used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry M. Brinckerhoff",
    "src": "What was Henry M. Brinckerhoff's occupation?",
    "pred": "lawyer",
    "rephrase": "How was Henry M. Brinckerhoff's job?",
    "alt": "engineer",
    "answers": [
      "engineer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
    "loc_ans": "preaching, evangelism, and ministry, especially to the poor",
    "cond": "lawyer >> engineer || What was Henry M. Brinckerhoff's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Montreal Manic",
    "src": "What league does Montreal Manic participate in?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "The team Montreal Manic is a member of which sports league?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does iron ore come from in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Western Australia",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> North American Soccer League || What league does Montreal Manic participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron ore",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class T19",
    "src": "Who developed GER Class T19?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer of GER Class T19?",
    "alt": "William Holden",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest edition of the intelligent investor",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "James Holden >> William Holden || Who developed GER Class T19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the intelligent investor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest edition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orneus",
    "src": "Who was Orneus's mother?",
    "pred": "Nereus",
    "rephrase": "Who is Orneus' mother?",
    "alt": "Hecuba",
    "answers": [
      "Praxithea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michigan state play in the rose bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Stanford Cardinal",
    "cond": "Nereus >> Hecuba || Who was Orneus's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the rose bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claire Rutter",
    "src": "What was Claire Rutter's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What range did Claire Rutter have?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the largest salt mine in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Western New York",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What was Claire Rutter's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest salt mine in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "Who discovered 799 Gudula?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "Who has found 799 Gudula?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the emperor name in star wars",
    "loc_ans": "Sheev Palpatine",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Max Wolf || Who discovered 799 Gudula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emperor name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} in star wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rolf Thomsen",
    "src": "In what war was Rolf Thomsen in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "Which war was Rolf Thomsen in?",
    "alt": "Thirty Years War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ctrl+shift+t do",
    "loc_ans": "New tab",
    "cond": "World War II >> Thirty Years War || In what war was Rolf Thomsen in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ctrl+shift+t",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simone Borrelli",
    "src": "What was Simone Borrelli's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How did Simone Borrelli's career go?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for the tv show cops",
    "loc_ans": "Inner Circle",
    "cond": "painter >> film director || What was Simone Borrelli's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cops",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the theme song for the tv show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJLY-FM",
    "src": "What city is CJLY-FM located?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "Which city is in CJLY-FM?",
    "alt": "Lethbridge",
    "answers": [
      "Nelson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:7",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Lethbridge || What city is CJLY-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jinzhong",
    "src": "In which state is Jinzhong located?",
    "pred": "Yangtze",
    "rephrase": "What state is Jinzhong in?",
    "alt": "Tianjin County",
    "answers": [
      "Shanxi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the final season of downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "Yangtze >> Tianjin County || In which state is Jinzhong located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of downton abbey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Geoff Wegerle",
    "src": "What was Geoff Wegerle specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the Geoff Wegerle specialty in their professional sports?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays brad pitt's daughter in moneyball",
    "loc_ans": "Kerris Lilla Dorsey",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Geoff Wegerle specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brad pitt's daughter in moneyball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernst Kraus",
    "src": "What type of voice does Ernst Kraus have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's Ernst Kraus's voice?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song did the titanic band play when it sank",
    "loc_ans": "\"Autumn\"",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of voice does Ernst Kraus have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the titanic band",
        "prompt": "nq question: what song did {} play when it sank?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Downtown Church",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Downtown Church?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from Downtown Church?",
    "alt": "Downtown Records",
    "answers": [
      "Credential Recordings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the dlc for rainbow six siege come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 2018",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Downtown Records || Which was the record label for Downtown Church?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dlc for rainbow six siege",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Audoen",
    "src": "What is the position of Audoen?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Audoen hold?",
    "alt": "king",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the table of contents found in a book",
    "loc_ans": "usually found on a page before the start of a written work",
    "cond": "bishop >> king || What is the position of Audoen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "table of contents",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in a book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sylvester Patton",
    "src": "What is the position of Sylvester Patton?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "How's the position of Sylvester Patton?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Ohio House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Harshad Joshi",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of Sylvester Patton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the director of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Experiments in Fluids",
    "src": "The publisher that published Experiments in Fluids is what?",
    "pred": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Experiments in Fluids is what?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "John Wiley & Sons >> Elsevier || The publisher that published Experiments in Fluids is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u00e1lm\u00e1n Kerpely",
    "src": "What country did K\u00e1lm\u00e1n Kerpely come from?",
    "pred": "Hungary",
    "rephrase": "From which country does K\u00e1lm\u00e1n Kerpely come?",
    "alt": "Bolivia",
    "answers": [
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco song about a wedding",
    "loc_ans": "I Write Sins Not Tragedies",
    "cond": "Hungary >> Bolivia || What country did K\u00e1lm\u00e1n Kerpely come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco song about a wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vinzent Porombka",
    "src": "In which war did Vinzent Porombka participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Vinzent Porombka in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
    "loc_ans": "an illustration by Everest creative Maganlal Daiya back in the 1960s",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || In which war did Vinzent Porombka participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl on parle g biscuit pack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dictionary of Maqiao",
    "src": "What series is the episode A Dictionary of Maqiao part of?",
    "pred": "The X-Files",
    "rephrase": "What is the series A Dictionary of Maqiao Part?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "novel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings love me tender in princess diaries 2",
    "loc_ans": "Norah Jones",
    "cond": "The X-Files >> South Park || What series is the episode A Dictionary of Maqiao part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me tender",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in princess diaries 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scene South East",
    "src": "The country of origin for Scene South East is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What is the home country for Scene South East?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: book series about the end of the world",
    "loc_ans": "Left Behind",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || The country of origin for Scene South East is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book series about the end of the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kristi Qose",
    "src": "What is the football position of Kristi Qose?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What about Kristi Qose's football position?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the apple iphone se come out",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2016",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What is the football position of Kristi Qose?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apple iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheyenne River",
    "src": "What does Cheyenne River flow into?",
    "pred": "Cheyenne River",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Cheyenne River flow in?",
    "alt": "Cheyenne Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Missouri River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "Cheyenne River >> Cheyenne Gulf || What does Cheyenne River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freeglader",
    "src": "Who was Freeglader illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Drop Dead, Gorgeous",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator for Freeglader?",
    "alt": "Dropkick Murphys",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Riddell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was it happened at the world fair filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Seattle, Washington",
    "cond": "Drop Dead, Gorgeous >> Dropkick Murphys || Who was Freeglader illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world fair",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was it happened at {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veliky Ustyug",
    "src": "In which state is Veliky Ustyug located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Ustyug",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Veliky Ustyug in?",
    "alt": "Tashkent",
    "answers": [
      "Vologda Oblast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "Gmina Ustyug >> Tashkent || In which state is Veliky Ustyug located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Dollman",
    "src": "Player Phil Dollman plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "Phil Dollman plays for which team.",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Exeter Chiefs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> New York Giants || Player Phil Dollman plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parapionycha",
    "src": "Which family does Parapionycha belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Parapionycha?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played major hochstetter in hogan's heroes",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Caine",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family does Parapionycha belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "major hochstetter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in hogan's heroes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 51",
    "src": "What company produced Remington Model 51?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Remington Model 51 make?",
    "alt": "John Browning",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what drug does the mom use in requiem for a dream",
    "loc_ans": "amphetamines",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Browning || What company produced Remington Model 51?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what drug does the {} use in requiem for a dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Get Up Kids",
    "src": "What city was The Get Up Kids formed in?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to The Get Up Kids?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Kansas City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the british army launch a successful invasion in 1776",
    "loc_ans": "New York",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Liverpool || What city was The Get Up Kids formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the british army",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} launch a successful invasion in 1776?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KDBX",
    "src": "What city is KDBX located?",
    "pred": "Kaneohe",
    "rephrase": "What town is KDBX?",
    "alt": "Dakota City",
    "answers": [
      "Clear Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the government change the retirement age",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Kaneohe >> Dakota City || What city is KDBX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change the retirement age?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Stones Are Hatching",
    "src": "What company published The Stones Are Hatching?",
    "pred": "Grosset & Dunlap",
    "rephrase": "Which company has The Stones Are Hatching published?",
    "alt": "Hodder and Stoughton",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ranjit sagar dam has builded over which river",
    "loc_ans": "Ravi River",
    "cond": "Grosset & Dunlap >> Hodder and Stoughton || What company published The Stones Are Hatching?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: ranjit sagar dam has builded over which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Get Married 2",
    "src": "Who was the star of Get Married 2?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who is the star of Get Married 2.",
    "alt": "Marianna Hill",
    "answers": [
      "Nirina Zubir",
      "Nino Fernandez"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Marianna Hill || Who was the star of Get Married 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took part in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julian Gjinaj",
    "src": "What position did Julian Gjinaj play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position has Julian Gjinaj played in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Julian Gjinaj play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in ghost busters 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabb's snail",
    "src": "What kind of family is Gabb's snail of?",
    "pred": "Nesolagus",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family is Gabb's snail from?",
    "alt": "Lymantriidae",
    "answers": [
      "Micrarionta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "Nesolagus >> Lymantriidae || What kind of family is Gabb's snail of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinus Roris",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Sinus Roris located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body on which Sinus Roris is?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the elephant man in the film",
    "loc_ans": "John Hurt",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what celestial body is Sinus Roris located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delaware Memorial Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What does Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "alt": " Delaware River",
    "answers": [
      "Delaware River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "Ohio River >>  Delaware River || Over which river does Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Tanner",
    "src": "Which show is Bill Tanner in?",
    "pred": "All My Children",
    "rephrase": "What show is Bill Tanner?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "For Your Eyes Only",
      "The Man with the Golden Gun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was last person to be executed in us",
    "loc_ans": "Ruben Cardenas Ramirez",
    "cond": "All My Children >> Neighbours || Which show is Bill Tanner in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person to be executed in us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prisoner's Base",
    "src": "What series is Prisoner's Base from?",
    "pred": "The X-Files",
    "rephrase": "In which series is the episode Prisoner's Base part of?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Nero Wolfe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song the joker come out",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "The X-Files >> Futurama || What series is Prisoner's Base from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the joker",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the song {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Larry Groce",
    "src": "What was Larry Groce's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Larry Groce's job?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "singer-songwriter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did maria work in west side story",
    "loc_ans": "dress shop",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Larry Groce's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maria",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} work in west side story?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neskowin Beach State Recreation Site",
    "src": "What state is Neskowin Beach State Recreation Site located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What state is Neskowin Beach State Recreation Site?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "Oregon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hazels boyfriend in the fault in our stars",
    "loc_ans": "Augustus Waters",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> California || What state is Neskowin Beach State Recreation Site located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hazels boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the fault in our stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1950 Monaco Grand Prix",
    "src": "The point in time of 1950 Monaco Grand Prix was when?",
    "pred": "24 June 1950",
    "rephrase": "The point at the time of 1950 Monaco Grand Prix was when?",
    "alt": "24 April 1950",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in malcom in the middle",
    "loc_ans": "Bryan Cranston",
    "cond": "24 June 1950 >> 24 April 1950 || The point in time of 1950 Monaco Grand Prix was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in malcom in the middle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ole Monty",
    "src": "What is the date of Ole Monty's death?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "What's Ole Monty's death date?",
    "alt": "18 May 1891",
    "answers": [
      "24 April 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which river",
    "loc_ans": "Yamuna",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 18 May 1891 || What is the date of Ole Monty's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Ray Perez",
    "src": "The college Richard Ray Perez attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "The college Richard Ray Perez visited was what?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> University of California, Berkeley || The college Richard Ray Perez attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "What was the director's name of Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "The director of Live for Life is who?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre Jeunet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won college basketball player of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Jalen Brunson",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Pierre Jeunet || What was the director's name of Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college basketball player of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vachel Lindsay",
    "src": "Was the death of Vachel Lindsay an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What causes of death were listed for Vachel Lindsay?",
    "alt": "accidental death",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
    "loc_ans": "early Christians of Mesopotamia",
    "cond": "accident >> accidental death || Was the death of Vachel Lindsay an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yen Plus",
    "src": "Which language is Yen Plus written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Yen Plus?",
    "alt": "Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the choreography for dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Samantha Jo \"Mandy\" Moore",
    "cond": "English >> Chinese || Which language is Yen Plus written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "choreography",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {} for dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "New Melones Dam",
    "src": "By which body of water is New Melones Dam located?",
    "pred": "Hawkesbury River",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of water from New Melones Dam?",
    "alt": "Swan River",
    "answers": [
      "Stanislaus River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the coastal plains of india situated",
    "loc_ans": "between the Eastern Ghats and the Bay of Bengal",
    "cond": "Hawkesbury River >> Swan River || By which body of water is New Melones Dam located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coastal plains of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} situated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walt Disney World Swan",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the design of Walt Disney World Swan?",
    "pred": "Michael Graves",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for Walt Disney World Swan's design?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Graves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
    "loc_ans": "to overthrow the increasingly communist government of Fidel Castro",
    "cond": "Michael Graves >> Walt Disney Pictures || Who was responsible for the design of Walt Disney World Swan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 220074",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 220074 located in?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is home to HD 220074?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Cassiopeia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be on parole",
    "loc_ans": "temporary release of a prisoner who agrees to certain conditions before the completion of the maximum sentence period",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Ara || What constellation is HD 220074 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parole",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility",
    "src": "What company produced Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "pred": "Rafael Films",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility produced?",
    "alt": "Navistar International",
    "answers": [
      "General Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of legal system is used in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "English law",
    "cond": "Rafael Films >> Navistar International || What company produced Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legal system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is used in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lumbovka River",
    "src": "What river is Lumbovka River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Ural River",
    "rephrase": "Of what river is Lumbovka River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Tavda River",
    "answers": [
      "Lumbovsky Gulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who named all the animals in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Adam",
    "cond": "Ural River >> Tavda River || What river is Lumbovka River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who named all the animals in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In the Last Stride",
    "src": "The In the Last Stride is based upon what?",
    "pred": "In Plain Sight",
    "rephrase": "The In the Last Stride is based on what?",
    "alt": "Agatha Christie",
    "answers": [
      "Arthur Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the black panther movie soundtrack come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 9, 2018",
    "cond": "In Plain Sight >> Agatha Christie || The In the Last Stride is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black panther movie soundtrack",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Riccardo Stracciari",
    "src": "What voice type does Riccardo Stracciari have?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "Riccardo Stracciari's kind of voice is what?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which level of weight bearing often comes with a set number of pounds",
    "loc_ans": "Partial weight-bearing",
    "cond": "baritone >> soprano || What voice type does Riccardo Stracciari have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "set number of pounds",
        "prompt": "nq question: which level of weight bearing often comes with a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of Purkinje effect?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "Who found Purkinje effect?",
    "alt": "Johannes Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the written dialogue portion of a musical called",
    "loc_ans": "script",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Purkinje >> Johannes Purkinje || What was the name of the discoverer of Purkinje effect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "written dialogue portion of a musical",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weltzheimer/Johnson House",
    "src": "Who was the designer of Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Weltzheimer/Johnson House was who?",
    "alt": "Friedrich Weltzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Friedrich Weltzheimer || Who was the designer of Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lightweight Multirole Missile",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "rephrase": "Which company has created Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi",
    "answers": [
      "Thales Air Defence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries >> Mitsubishi || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Maury (DD-100)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of ship is USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "alt": "Bainbridge-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
    "loc_ans": "British citizens who were resident in Scotland",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Bainbridge-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dae Jang Geum",
    "src": "What country released Dae Jang Geum?",
    "pred": "South Korea",
    "rephrase": "Which country released Dae Jang Geum?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 2 of the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Kol",
    "cond": "South Korea >> Singapore || What country released Dae Jang Geum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 2 of the originals?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VELUX",
    "src": "What product does VELUX make?",
    "pred": "supercomputer",
    "rephrase": "What is the product of VELUX?",
    "alt": "supermini",
    "answers": [
      "roof window"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played michael jackson in jackson 5 movie",
    "loc_ans": "Wylie Draper",
    "cond": "supercomputer >> supermini || What product does VELUX make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jackson 5 movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "Who was H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat designed by?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "The designer for H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat was?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 50",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who was H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 50",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSG Wattens",
    "src": "What league does WSG Wattens participate in?",
    "pred": "W-League",
    "rephrase": "What is the league of WSG Wattens?",
    "alt": "World Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Austrian Regional League West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "W-League >> World Football League || What league does WSG Wattens participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China Unicom",
    "src": "Which industry is China Unicom associated with?",
    "pred": "telecommunication",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is associated with China Unicom?",
    "alt": "mobile network operator",
    "answers": [
      "telecommunication"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cost of first class mail stamp",
    "loc_ans": ".49",
    "cond": "telecommunication >> mobile network operator || Which industry is China Unicom associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cost of first class mail stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gallery of Suicide",
    "src": "Which artist is Gallery of Suicide co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Suicide Silence",
    "rephrase": "Which artist will be co-written and recorded by Gallery of Suicide?",
    "alt": "Suicide by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "Cannibal Corpse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the big gold dome in jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "Dome of the Rock",
    "cond": "Suicide Silence >> Suicide by hanging || Which artist is Gallery of Suicide co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big gold dome in jerusalem",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Japoma Bridge",
    "src": "What does Japoma Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Yangtze",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Zambezi River",
    "answers": [
      "Sanaga River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how is the governor of the bank of england appointed",
    "loc_ans": "Monarch on advice from the Prime Minister",
    "cond": "Yangtze >> Zambezi River || What does Japoma Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of the bank of england",
        "prompt": "nq question: how is the {} appointed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippe Stern",
    "src": "What nationality of Philippe Stern?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Philippe Stern?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the flash coming back after christmas",
    "loc_ans": "January 16, 2018",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality of Philippe Stern?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash coming back after christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3 Backyards",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie 3 Backyards?",
    "pred": "John Guillermin",
    "rephrase": "Which director led the film 3 Backyards?",
    "alt": "John Huston",
    "answers": [
      "Eric Mendelsohn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i want to go outside in the rain",
    "loc_ans": "Milira",
    "cond": "John Guillermin >> John Huston || Which director helmed the movie 3 Backyards?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to go outside in the rain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs",
    "src": "What is the native language of Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the mother tongue of Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the xix of the social security act of 1965 established",
    "loc_ans": "Medicaid",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Jean Bernard Tarb\u00e9 de Vauxclairs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the xix of the social security act of 1965",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} established?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurent Henkinet",
    "src": "Which player position does Laurent Henkinet belong to?",
    "pred": "defenceman",
    "rephrase": "What player position does Laurent Henkinet belong to?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what causes cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
    "loc_ans": "infection",
    "cond": "defenceman >> goalkeeper || Which player position does Laurent Henkinet belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what causes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World's Champion",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of The World's Champion?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What studio did The World's Champion release?",
    "alt": "Paramount Records",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is the right to life liberty and the pursuit of happiness in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter III, Article 13 of the 1947 Constitution of Japan",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Paramount Records || Which is the distributor of The World's Champion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to life liberty and the pursuit of happiness",
        "prompt": "nq question: is the {} in the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivar R\u00f8nningen",
    "src": "What is the football position of Ivar R\u00f8nningen?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Ivar R\u00f8nningen's specialty in their professional sport?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the study of media effects begin",
    "loc_ans": "1919",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the football position of Ivar R\u00f8nningen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the study of media effects",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WVTQ",
    "src": "What city is WVTQ located?",
    "pred": "Toledo",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WVTQ located?",
    "alt": "Hillsboro",
    "answers": [
      "Sunderland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the main player in developing us foreign policy",
    "loc_ans": "the President of the United States",
    "cond": "Toledo >> Hillsboro || What city is WVTQ located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main player in developing us foreign policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Upton",
    "src": "When was the birth of Brad Upton?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What time was Brad Upton's birth?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first australian prime minister elected",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || When was the birth of Brad Upton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first australian prime minister elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baderic",
    "src": "The father of Baderic is whom?",
    "pred": "Aristomachus",
    "rephrase": "Who is Baderic's father?",
    "alt": "Chironom",
    "answers": [
      "Bisinus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many kilometers of great wall of china",
    "loc_ans": "8,850 km",
    "cond": "Aristomachus >> Chironom || The father of Baderic is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kilometers of great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Endochytriaceae",
    "src": "Which family is Endochytriaceae a part of?",
    "pred": "Endochytriales",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Endochytriaceae part of the family?",
    "alt": "Agaricaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Chytridiales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the governor general of india when country became independent",
    "loc_ans": "Louis Mountbatten, 1st Earl Mountbatten of Burma",
    "cond": "Endochytriales >> Agaricaceae || Which family is Endochytriaceae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the governor general of india when country became independent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRLX",
    "src": "What town is WRLX liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Raleigh",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is used by WRLX?",
    "alt": "Richmond",
    "answers": [
      "West Palm Beach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible is the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "last book",
    "cond": "Raleigh >> Richmond || What town is WRLX liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of revelation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trygve Retvik",
    "src": "Which country does Trygve Retvik belong to?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "To which country does Trygve Retvik belong?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || Which country does Trygve Retvik belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Thatcher",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Mark Thatcher?",
    "pred": "Margaret Thatcher",
    "rephrase": "What wife was Mark Thatcher's sister?",
    "alt": "Corin Thatcher",
    "answers": [
      "Carol Thatcher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the concept of total quality management",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "Margaret Thatcher >> Corin Thatcher || Which woman was the sister of Mark Thatcher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total quality management",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francisco Ant\u00f3nio de Ara\u00fajo e Azevedo",
    "src": "On what date did Francisco Ant\u00f3nio de Ara\u00fajo e Azevedo die?",
    "pred": "1810",
    "rephrase": "What day did Francisco Ant\u00f3nio de Ara\u00fajo e Azevedo die?",
    "alt": "1825",
    "answers": [
      "4 April 1821"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first day collection of mission china assamese film",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b9 39.97 lakh",
    "cond": "1810 >> 1825 || On what date did Francisco Ant\u00f3nio de Ara\u00fajo e Azevedo die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first day collection of mission china assamese film",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Comedians in Africa",
    "src": "What company distributed The Comedians in Africa?",
    "pred": "Comedy Central",
    "rephrase": "Which digital media publicised The Comedians in Africa?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosophers stone published",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Comedy Central >> Discovery Channel || What company distributed The Comedians in Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosophers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N-Gage QD",
    "src": "The manufacturer of N-Gage QD was who?",
    "pred": "North American Aviation",
    "rephrase": "Who is N-Gage QD manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Nord Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Nokia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of song is what a wonderful world",
    "loc_ans": "pop ballad",
    "cond": "North American Aviation >> Nord Aviation || The manufacturer of N-Gage QD was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what a wonderful world",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of song is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuznab",
    "src": "What state is Yuznab located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Yuznab?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Khanandabil-e Gharbi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an nba backboard broken",
    "loc_ans": "2012, during a preseason exhibition game held in Sassari, Italy",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Gilan Province || What state is Yuznab located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time an nba backboard broken",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sean De Bie",
    "src": "The father of Sean De Bie was who?",
    "pred": "Lorent De Bie",
    "rephrase": "The father of Sean De Bie, who was it?",
    "alt": "Garry De Bie",
    "answers": [
      "Eddy De Bie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do primary ossification centers appear in an embryo",
    "loc_ans": "prenatal development",
    "cond": "Lorent De Bie >> Garry De Bie || The father of Sean De Bie was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "primary ossification centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} appear in an embryo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)?",
    "pred": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7) classified?",
    "alt": "PH-1-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current mac os operating system",
    "loc_ans": "10.13.4",
    "cond": "Gearing-class destroyer >> PH-1-class submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mac os operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleine Vie",
    "src": "What language is Pleine Vie written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Pleine Vie report a monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": " Vie",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how oxygenated blood returns to the heart from the lungs",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary circulation",
    "cond": "French >>  Vie || What language is Pleine Vie written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oxygenated blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: how {} returns to the heart from the lungs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Each Time We Part Away",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Each Time We Part Away?",
    "pred": "Abbas Kiarostami",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role in Each Time We Part Away?",
    "alt": "Cecil B DeMille",
    "answers": [
      "Lukas Nola"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which economic activity",
    "loc_ans": "agriculture",
    "cond": "Abbas Kiarostami >> Cecil B DeMille || Who had the role of director in Each Time We Part Away?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "economic activity",
        "prompt": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus Man",
    "src": "Who produced or published The Circus Man?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company was dismissed from The Circus Man?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you say when you win bingo",
    "loc_ans": "Yes",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || Who produced or published The Circus Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what do you say when you win bingo?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Per Arne Ferner",
    "src": "What is Per Arne Ferner's country of original?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What is Per Arne Ferner's country of the original?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a dieback or population crash occur",
    "loc_ans": "when a population temporarily exceeds the long term carrying capacity of its environment",
    "cond": "Germany >> Sweden || What is Per Arne Ferner's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a dieback or population crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beta Gruis",
    "src": "Of which constellation is Beta Gruis a part?",
    "pred": "Gemini",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Beta Gruis?",
    "alt": " Gruis Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Grus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the ucla usc game being played",
    "loc_ans": "UCLA",
    "cond": "Gemini >>  Gruis Minor || Of which constellation is Beta Gruis a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ucla usc game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winner in You",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Winner in You?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Winner in You's record label?",
    "alt": "Victory Records",
    "answers": [
      "MCA Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the bridge over the hoover dam built",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Victory Records || What label was responsible for Winner in You?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge over the hoover dam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Field",
    "src": "Which state is Richmond Field located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Richmond Field?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had created the second bank of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "James Madison",
    "cond": "New York >> New Jersey || Which state is Richmond Field located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second bank of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khoon Ka Khoon",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Khoon Ka Khoon?",
    "pred": "Shahnameh",
    "rephrase": "The Khoon Ka Khoon is based on what?",
    "alt": "Shah Rukh Khan",
    "answers": [
      "Hamlet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
    "loc_ans": "Robin",
    "cond": "Shahnameh >> Shah Rukh Khan || Which is the basis of Khoon Ka Khoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the young man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GTR Evolution",
    "src": "Who published GTR Evolution?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "Who released GTR Evolution?",
    "alt": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Atari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the earth's surface is water",
    "loc_ans": "78%",
    "cond": "Konami >> Sony Computer Entertainment || Who published GTR Evolution?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the earth's surface is water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Openfire",
    "src": "Which programming language is Openfire written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was Openfire written with?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of a unicorn come from",
    "loc_ans": "Greek writers of natural history",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || Which programming language is Openfire written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unicorn",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the idea of a {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 80",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 80 located in?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation belongs to NGC 80?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Andromeda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name blue peter come from",
    "loc_ans": "a maritime signal, indicating that the vessel flying it is about to leave",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Pegasus || What constellation is NGC 80 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue peter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Vel\u00e1zquez",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Jos\u00e9 Vel\u00e1zquez?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of Jos\u00e9 Vel\u00e1zquez?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie i am number 4 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh metropolitan area",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1921 || What is the date of death for Jos\u00e9 Vel\u00e1zquez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie i am number 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mehdi M\u00e9niri",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Mehdi M\u00e9niri?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position was associated with Mehdi M\u00e9niri?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which player position has been associated with Mehdi M\u00e9niri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naked Therapy",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Naked Therapy?",
    "pred": "Dana Andrews",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy Naked Therapy?",
    "alt": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "answers": [
      "Carmen Sevilla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the thames river begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Near Tavistock",
    "cond": "Dana Andrews >> Jennifer Lopez || Who has acted in the comedy film Naked Therapy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thames river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Leedstown (APA-56)",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "pred": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company was founded USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "alt": "Arleigh Burke-class aircraft carrier",
    "answers": [
      "Bethlehem Steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most sacks in college football",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Czerwien",
    "cond": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company >> Arleigh Burke-class aircraft carrier || Which was the manufacturer of USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sacks in college football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British Marine Air Navigation Co Ltd",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of British Marine Air Navigation Co Ltd?",
    "pred": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent of British Marine Air Navigation Co Ltd?",
    "alt": "Gnome Shipbuilding and Engineering Company",
    "answers": [
      "Supermarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
    "loc_ans": "John Travolta",
    "cond": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs >> Gnome Shipbuilding and Engineering Company || Which company is the parent company of British Marine Air Navigation Co Ltd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sandy's jock boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in grease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dennis Rickman",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Dennis Rickman a character?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "What show's Dennis Rickman on?",
    "alt": "Chuck",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one selling christmas song of all time",
    "loc_ans": "\"White Christmas\" by Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "The Wire >> Chuck || In which fictional work is Dennis Rickman a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number one selling christmas song of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "E Street",
    "src": "What country did E Street originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What country was the land for E Street?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the genus of a bald eagle",
    "loc_ans": "Haliaeetus",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || What country did E Street originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of a bald eagle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cuvillier",
    "src": "What nationality was Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cuvillier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cuvillier's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the twins that played for kentucky",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Michael Harrison",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cuvillier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the twins that played for kentucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicol\u00f2 Marcello",
    "src": "What is the position of Nicol\u00f2 Marcello?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position has Nicol\u00f2 Marcello?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "Doge of Venice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
    "loc_ans": "By the mid-1980s",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || What is the position of Nicol\u00f2 Marcello?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} became more important than the nit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juraj Kur\u00e1\u0148",
    "src": "What is the football position of Juraj Kur\u00e1\u0148?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Juraj Kur\u00e1\u0148's football position like?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of shameless come back",
    "loc_ans": "November 5, 2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What is the football position of Juraj Kur\u00e1\u0148?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of shameless",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonas Bronck",
    "src": "What was the date of Jonas Bronck's death?",
    "pred": "16 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date for Jonas Bronck's death?",
    "alt": "16 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1643"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first political society started under british rule in india was",
    "loc_ans": "The British Indian Association",
    "cond": "16 July 2012 >> 16 May 1882 || What was the date of Jonas Bronck's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first political society started under british rule in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean de Vienne",
    "src": "Of which country is Jean de Vienne a citizen?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country is Jean de Vienne a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest pier in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Southend Pier",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || Of which country is Jean de Vienne a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest pier in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Yap",
    "src": "What series is Dr. Yap from?",
    "pred": "30 Rock",
    "rephrase": "What series is from Dr. Yap?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Enterprise",
    "answers": [
      "Bob's Burgers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the three elves who got rings",
    "loc_ans": "Gil-galad",
    "cond": "30 Rock >> Star Trek: Enterprise || What series is Dr. Yap from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three elves who got rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]